<twitter><tweet><created_at>Sun Apr 29 19:04:13 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Thinking we&apos;re only one signature away from ending the war in Iraq. 
Learn more at http://www.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 01 18:12:21 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Wondering why, four years after President Bush landed on an aircraft carrier and declared &#x2018;Mission Accomplished,&#x2019; we are still at war?</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 07 15:52:28 +0000 2007</created_at><text>At the Detroit Economic Club &#x2013; Talking about the need to reduce our dependence on foreign oil.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 08 21:01:32 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Thinking we can cut oil consumption by 2.5 million barrels of oil per day and take 50 million cars&#x2019; worth of pollution off the road by 2020</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 11 01:15:18 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Indianola, Iowa and heading to Des Moines</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 14 17:25:24 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Trenton, NJ at AFL-CIO Town Hall Meeting</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed May 16 19:47:37 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Thinking the President&#x2019;s word is not the last word on Iraq.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat May 19 17:57:28 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Speaking at Southern New Hampshire University Commencement</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 25 01:05:27 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In DC voting No...  &quot;We should not give the President a blank check to continue down this same, disastrous path.&#x201d;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 29 15:32:16 +0000 2007</created_at><text>At the University of Iowa envisioning affordable universal healthcare by end of first term.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu May 31 20:46:37 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Looking forward to watching Michelle&apos;s interview on NBC nightly news tonight.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jun 03 19:49:52 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Heading to Democratic presidential debate at St. Anselm College in New Hampshire.  Debate starts at 7pm EST and will air live on CNN.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 08 23:58:23 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Preparing for our big &quot;Walk for Change&quot; national canvass - Heading to Dubuque, Iowa for tomorrow&apos;s walk.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 14 01:44:34 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Being featured on YouTube &quot;Candidate Spotlight&quot; asking how can we make this country better?</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jun 16 00:56:49 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Traveling to Jackson, Mississippi - excited after rallying with over 3500 supporters in Greenville, South Carolina.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 20 01:53:08 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Launching Obama Mobile text messaging; text &apos;GO&apos; to OBAMA (62262) to get a free bumper sticker.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 26 20:46:47 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In DC: Asking you to share what inspires you on the front page of www.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 28 23:49:22 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In DC heading to Howard University for the presidential debate @ 9pm EDT on PBS stations. Txt your thoughts on the debate to OBAMA (62262)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jul 09 18:57:25 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Heading to Alabama for the Birmingham kick-off rally.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jul 16 19:53:04 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Chicago, walking picket line with hotel workers at the Congress Hotel. For more info visit http://www.congresshotelstrike.info</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 19 21:00:13 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Enjoying an ice cream social with residents of Sunapee, New Hampshire.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 26 19:43:39 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Addressing the College Democrats of America at their national convention in Columbia, SC.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 07 20:30:54 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Chicago - heading to the AFL-CIO Presidential Forum.  It is on MSNBC tonight live at 7pm EDT, moderated by Keith Olbermann.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 16 16:53:43 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa this week and heading to the Iowa State Fair later this afternoon- Visit http://iowa.barackobama.com/roadtochange for full schedule.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Aug 17 20:03:56 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Tama, IA for a Rural Policy Summit @ South Tama County High School.  Heading to Cedar Rapids and Waverly tomorrow.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 22 19:45:01 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In New York - heading to The Daily Show with Jon Stewart.  Be sure to watch it on Comedy Central tonight.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 29 20:43:11 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Thinking on this 2nd anniversary of Katrina that New Orleans should become an example of what America can do when we come together.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 05 21:52:06 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Speaking at town halls in Sac City and Storm Lake, Iowa today. Heading to Nevada tomorrow.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 12 00:52:40 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Giving a major Iraq policy speech tomorrow in Iowa and will also be live on the Today Show tomorrow morning at 7:00am.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 18 14:34:52 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Washington DC, talking about reforming America&#x2019;s tax code so that it works for the middle class. Visit www.barackobama.com for details.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 21 02:34:47 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Atlanta: had a great event with Usher and Dominique Wilkins. Fired Up!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 27 00:42:15 +0000 2007</created_at><text>At Dartmouth College at the DNC debate.  It airs live from 9-11pm ET on MSNBC  text your thoughts on the debate to 62262.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 27 22:01:22 +0000 2007</created_at><text>At rally in Washington Square Park, NYC  - Watch full event live now at http://www.barackobama.com/nyc</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 02 15:47:15 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Chicago, at DePaul University speaking about the need to eliminate the world&apos;s nuclear weapons. Watch live now http://www.cnn.com/video</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 08 21:08:41 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Portsmouth, NH -just announced a visionary plan to make America a global leader on energy. For details visit www.barackobama.com/speeches</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 17 22:04:27 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Los Angeles, CA.  Going to be on NBC&apos;s Tonight Show with Jay Leno tonight. Check local listings for exact time.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 18 21:03:32 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Nevada today and excited to be on the Tavis Smiley Show tonight on PBS. Check your listings for what time it airs locally.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 23 19:17:00 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Boston with Governor Deval Patrick for a rally starting at 5:30PM at Parkman Bandstand on Boston Common  http://my.barackobama.com/bos</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 29 15:02:49 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Cedar Rapids, IA at Coe College for the MySpace MTV Presidential Dialogue. It will stream live at 1:30pm ET www.myspace.com/election2008</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 08 02:50:36 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa this week.  Just announced plan today to &quot;Reclaim the American Dream&quot;  Learn more about the plan at http://my.barackobama.com/dream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 14 22:42:43 +0000 2007</created_at><text>At Google&apos;s Town Hall in Mountain View,CA  Speaking about the need for network neutrality!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 15 23:00:26 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Las Vegas, NV for the presidential debate. It will be broadcast live tonight at 8pm ET on CNN.  Txt your thoughts throughout to 62262.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 27 16:04:07 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Portsmouth, NH holding a foreign policy forum.  Watch it live stream at http://my.barackobama.com/page/content/fpforum</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Dec 01 19:45:58 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa at two presidential forums today: The Heartland Forum at 3:30pm ET on C-SPAN &amp; The Brown &amp; Black Forum at 8pm ET on HDNet.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 04 17:41:05 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa and heading to today&apos;s NPR/Iowa Public Radio Presidential Debate. Watch it live at 2pm ET by visiting http://www.npr.org</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 07 22:35:28 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Chicago, heading to Change Rocks Concert with Macy Gray, Jeff Tweedy, Stephan Jenkins &amp; Jill Sobule http://my.barackobama.com/gochicago</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Dec 09 17:49:05 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Columbia, SC with Oprah - watch the webcast live now at http://my.barackobama.com/page/content/oprahwebcast</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 13 17:44:08 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa and heading to DSM Register debate, the last one before the Iowa Caucuses. Watch at 2pm ET on CNN, C-SPAN3 &amp; http://www.iptv.org.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Dec 16 20:09:06 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa  - travelling to Algona, Emmetsburg, Estherville, and Spirit Lake.  More info at http://iowa.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 18 00:45:58 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa - campaigning in Spencer, Storm Lake, Cherokee, Le Mars, and Sioux City.  More info at http://iowa.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 19 18:29:55 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In New Hampshire - meeting people at 5pm at the Radisson Manchester &amp; 7pm at Elm Street Middle School in Nashua. http://nh.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 20 20:06:52 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In New Hampshire -holding events at 5pm at the Frank Jones Center in Portsmouth and 7pm at the American Legion Post No. 7 in Rochester.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 27 00:20:41 +0000 2007</created_at><text>In Iowa this week.  Campaigning today in Mason City, Webster City, Fort Dodge, and Carroll.  More info at http://iowa.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Dec 30 04:58:02 +0000 2007</created_at><text>Will be on NBC&apos;s Meet the Press tomorrow live from Des Moines, IA.  To find your local air times visit: http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/3080248/</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 03 23:44:30 +0000 2008</created_at><text>is Fired Up!.. And Ready to Go!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jan 06 00:04:32 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Manchester, NH - heading to the ABC Facebook Debate. Watch it live on your ABC station at 9pm ET. Text your thoughts to 62262 after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 10 17:17:37 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Charleston, SC at a &quot;Rally for Change&quot; event at the College of Charleston. Yes, we can!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 14 02:39:45 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Pahrump, NV at a Stand for Change Rally.  Heading to Reno, Fallon &amp; Carson City tomorrow. For info visit http://nevada.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 16 00:04:10 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Las Vegas, heading to Nevada Democratic Party/MSNBC Debate. Watch it live at 9pm ET on MSNBC.  Text your thoughts to 62262 after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jan 19 16:23:50 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Las Vegas, Nevada.  Fired Up &amp; Ready to Go!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 21 23:25:16 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Myrtle Beach heading to tonight&apos;s debate at 8pm on CNN. Please visit http://barackobama.com to watch my speech from Dr. King&apos;s church.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 22 23:28:59 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At &quot;Stand for Change&quot; events across South Carolina this week. Visit http://sc.barackobama.com for more info.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 23 23:31:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Meeting folks in South Carolina today. Excited to have received Columbia&apos;s The State, Rock Hill Herald  &amp; Greenville News endorsements.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 25 03:09:22 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In North Charleston,SC at a &quot;Stand for Change&quot; rally.  Watch Letterman&apos;s Top 10 tonight. The Late Show is on CBS at 11:35pm ET/PT.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 29 04:01:20 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Washington, DC at the State of the Union.  To watch my response visit http://youtube.com/barackobama</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 31 23:31:53 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In California, heading to the last debate before Super Tuesday. Watch it tonight at 8pm ET/5pm PT on CNN. Text your thoughts to 62262 after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 04 15:54:25 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Hartford, CT, East Rutherford, NJ, and Boston, MA at Stand for Change Rallies.  For info visit http://barackobama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 05 20:15:04 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Yes We Can! Please tell all your friends in the Feb 5th States to vote today.  To find polling info visit: http://my.barackobama.com/polling</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Feb 10 03:33:26 +0000 2008</created_at><text>in Virginia, speaking at VA Democratic Party Jefferson-Jackson Dinner. Watch his speech live on CNN.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 12 23:03:32 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Encouraging everyone in DC, MD and VA to vote today. Heading to Madison, WI for a Rally for Change event at the Kohl Center (6:15pm tonight)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 19 18:21:20 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Is encouraging everyone to tell friends in Wisconsin to vote until 8pm tonight. And tell friends in Hawaii to get to their caucus by 6:30pm!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 21 23:41:01 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Excited to learn about winning the Dems Abroad primary today. Getting ready for the Texas debate.  It will be live tonight at 8pm ET on CNN.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 26 22:10:14 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Heading to Cleveland State University for tonight&apos;s debate.  Watch it live at 9pm ET on MSNBC or streamed at http://cleveland.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 01 22:00:22 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Just left a rally in Providence, RI &amp; heading to Parma, OH for a Town Hall. Remind all your friends in OH, RI, TX &amp; VT to vote this Tuesday.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 04 17:30:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Texas getting out the vote! Tell friends in Ohio, Rhode Island, Texas &amp; Vermont to vote today. More info at: http://barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 06 19:59:37 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Chicago, hoping you will help Bill Foster win Cong. Dist. 14 in this Saturday&apos;s Special Election. Visit: http://my.barackobama.com/foster</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 07 19:25:44 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Casper, WY at a town hall meeting &amp; heading to Laramie. Remind all your friends in Wyoming to caucus tomorrow. http://WY.BarackObama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Mar 09 00:28:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Excited by winning the Wyoming Caucus and looking forward to Mississippi&apos;s Democratic Primary on Tuesday. Visit http://MS.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 10 17:46:00 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Columbus,MS &amp; wondering how somebody who&apos;s in second place is offering the vice presidency to the person who&apos;s in first place. Vote Tues!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 11 18:58:08 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Learning about alternative energy in Fairless Hills, PA and encouraging everyone to vote in today&apos;s Mississippi Democratic Primary.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 12 00:21:40 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Energized by the news of winning Mississippi. We&apos;ve won the most states, the most votes and the most delegates.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 12 17:38:13 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Grateful to be with distinguished generals &amp; admirals. Between them, they&apos;ve served 9 Commanders-in-Chief. Honored to draw on their counsel.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 12 22:47:45 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Launching &quot;Artists for Obama&quot; items in Store.BarackObama.com with a limited Shepard Fairey print. Direct link: http://tinyurl.com/297j99</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 13 21:26:38 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Joining Chris Dodd, Chair of Senate Banking Committee, to address the housing crisis that is affecting millions of American families.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 19 22:49:36 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Fayetteville, NC on the 5th Anniv. of the Iraq War, stating, &quot;I will set a new goal on Day One: I will end this war.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 20 16:06:32 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Charleston, WV talking about how we need to end the war in Iraq &amp; invest here at home. Learn more: http://my.barackobama.com/iraqburden</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 20 21:22:47 +0000 2008</created_at><text>After 5 years, it&apos;s time to bring our soldiers home. Watch my discussion with eight Iraq veterans tonight at 6pm ET/PT on all MTV stations.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 21 14:12:19 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Visiting Portland, Salem and Eugene, Oregon today. Honored to have Governor Bill Richardson&apos;s endorsement.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 26 17:04:13 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall meeting at the War Memorial Auditorium in Greensboro, NC.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 27 16:10:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Just spoke at Cooper Union in NYC, called for immediate relief for the housing crisis &amp; an additional $30 billion to jumpstart the economy.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Mar 30 19:46:36 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a rally at Penn State University and a Town Hall in Harrisburg, PA today Learn more at http://PA.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 31 20:05:40 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Reminding everyone to donate by midnight tonight and you could be chosen to dine with me and a few supporters. http://barackobama.com/dine.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 02 20:36:14 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At West Chester University of Pennsylvania, will be appearing live on MSNBC at 5PM ET today for the Chris Matthews Hardball College Tour.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 03 17:48:01 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Troubled by today&apos;s unemployment figures, the latest indicator of how badly America needs fundamental change from Bush-McCain policies.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 04 16:29:30 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Indiana on the 40th anniv. of Dr. King&apos;s assassination. Asking everyone to continue his lifelong pursuit of social &amp; economic justice.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 08 21:15:14 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Talked with Communications Workers of America about getting America back to work. Watch my full speech at: http://tinyurl.com/5mmlrv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 11 16:00:39 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Campaigning in Indiana today. Going from Indianapolis to Columbus and on to Terre Haute. For more info visit http://IN.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 14 15:12:12 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In PA at the Alliance for American Manufacturing, stating that any trade agreement must contain real, enforceable standards for workers.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 15 14:47:04 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At the Building Trades National Legislative Conference, stating that we need to strengthen the long-term competitiveness of our economy.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 16 22:17:51 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Philadelphia, PA. Debating tonight on ABC. Watch the debate at 8pm ET/PT and 7pm CT/MT. Text your thoughts to 62262 after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 18 22:33:08 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At Independence National Historical Park (Philly, PA) kicking off the &quot;On Track for Change&quot; tour.  For more info: http://PA.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Apr 19 20:21:37 +0000 2008</created_at><text>On the &quot;On Track for Change&quot; tour through Pennsylvania.  Heading to Harrisburg for a rally tonight on the State Capitol&apos;s South Steps.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Apr 20 18:48:02 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Reading &amp; Scranton, PA today. Honored to be campaigning with Senator Bob Casey and Caroline Kennedy. Visit http://PA.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 21 19:01:35 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In McKeesport &amp; Pittsburgh, PA today finishing the &quot;On Track for Change&quot; tour and reminding everyone in PA to vote tomorrow!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 22 02:25:33 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Going to be on The Daily Show with Jon Stewart tonight. 11:00pm ET on Comedy Central.  Hope you watch &amp; reply with your thoughts after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 22 15:15:08 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Traveling through PA today &amp; asking folks to vote for change! If you are in PA &amp; need polling location info visit http://pa.barackobama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 23 18:37:05 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In New Albany, IN at a town hall meeting at Indiana University Southeast.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 29 00:07:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a One-Stop Early Vote Rally at The University of North Carolina, Dean E. Smith Center. More info: http://my.barackobama.com/chapelhill.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 29 16:01:50 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Chapel Hill, Winston-Salem &amp; Hickory, NC today.  Also, on the Rachael Ray Show today. For show times visit: http://rachaelrayshow.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 30 18:15:18 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Having lunch with Michelle &amp; talking with working families in Indianapolis, then heading to Bloomington for a rally at Indiana University.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu May 01 21:43:05 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Campaigning today in South Bend, IN and will be on Letterman tonight at 11pm ET/PT on CBS.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 02 21:06:23 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Campaigned in Indianapolis &amp; Munster, IN and then Charlotte, NC. Now heading to the NC Jefferson-Jackson Dinner in Raleigh, NC.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat May 03 19:51:59 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Indiana today &amp; will be on Meet the Press for the full hour from Indianapolis tomorrow. Check airtimes: http://msnbc.msn.com/id/3080248/</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 05 19:54:31 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding get out the vote events in both IN and NC.  To find your polling locations for tomorrow&apos;s elections visit http://barackobama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 06 18:08:46 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Getting Out The Vote! Polls open until 6:00pm in IN &amp; until 7:30pm in NC. For polling info: IN.BarackObama.com or NC.BarackObama.com.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat May 10 18:58:58 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Launching &quot;Vote for Change&quot; an unprecedented 50-state voter registration &amp; mobilization drive. Visit: http://barackobama.com/voteforchange.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 12 17:36:15 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Charleston, WV urging America to serve our returning heroes as well as they&apos;ve served us. http://barackobama.com/issues/veterans/</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 13 18:25:15 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Encouraging people to vote today in West Virginia. Polls open until 7:30pm. Visit http://WV.BarackObama.com for more info.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed May 14 17:21:38 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In MI, unveiling my manufacturing agenda. It&apos;s time to recapture the spirit of innovation that has always fueled America&apos;s economic success.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 19 21:28:49 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Campaigning in Montana today.  Holding rallies in Billings, Crow Agency and Bozeman.  Learn more at http://MT.Barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed May 21 02:43:46 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Des Moines, IA. Our movement will have secured the majority of pledged delegates tonight. Change is coming! http://barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 23 21:38:16 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Had a great three days in Florida.  Watch videos from Florida as well as our amazing stops in OR &amp; IA at http://www.youtube.com/barackobama</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun May 25 17:19:34 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Middletown, CT. Pinch-hitting for Senator Kennedy and delivering the commencement address for Wesleyan University.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon May 26 18:23:29 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Las Cruces, NM, honoring the generations of American patriots this Memorial Day at a Veterans Town Hall with Gov. Bill Richardson.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed May 28 00:04:51 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In North Las Vegas. Addressed our housing crisis. In Las Vegas, 1 out of every 44 households is facing foreclosure. It is time for a change.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat May 31 17:47:36 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In South Dakota. Visited Mt. Rushmore last night, Rapid City this morning.  Watch the video from Rapid City at http://my.barackobama.com/RC</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jun 01 19:11:49 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Mitchell, South Dakota.  Heading to a rally at the Mitchell Corn Palace. Visit http://SD.BarackObama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 03 18:56:08 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Reminding everyone in South Dakota &amp; Montana to vote! For polling locations visit http://SD.BarackObama.com or http://MT.BarackObama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 04 02:07:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>IN St Paul, MN speaking after securing the nomination.  Watch the speech live on TV tonight or streamed http://my.barackobama.com/nominee</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jun 07 17:54:27 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Thanking Hillary. Our party &amp; our country are stronger because of the work she has done. Visit http://my.BarackObama.com/thanks</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 09 20:18:34 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Kicking-off a two week tour focusing on the current economic crisis &amp; the need for new economic policy: http://my.barackobama.com/NCspeech</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 12 23:48:51 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Pleased with today&apos;s Supreme Court decision to bring terrorists to justice while also protecting our core values. http://www.barackobama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jun 15 19:31:57 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Wishing everyone a Happy Father&apos;s Day. Spoke today at the Apostolic Church of God in Chicago. Read remarks at http://my.barackobama.com/dad</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 16 16:57:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Flint, MI discussing my competitiveness agenda built upon education and energy, innovation and infrastructure, fair trade and reform.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 16 23:48:28 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Honored to be endorsed by Al Gore in Michigan tonight.  Watch live streaming video at 8:30pm EST at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 19 00:26:51 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Earlier today in Washington DC, announced the formation of my Senior Working Group on National Security. http://my.barackobama.com/security</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 19 15:33:19 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Made an important decision today and wanted to share it with you. Visit http://my.barackobama.com/mydecision</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 20 14:26:30 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Chicago,holding an economic discussion with the Democratic governors.  Watch it live now at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 24 17:09:44 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a discussion on energy policy in Las Vegas, NV.  Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 26 12:56:42 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At Carnegie Mellon in Pittsburgh, PA.  Holding an &quot;Economic Competitiveness Summit.&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 27 17:18:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Unity, NH. Heading to a rally with Senator Clinton.  Watch this event live now on cable news or at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 27 21:09:16 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Excited by the over 4000 &quot;Unite for Change&quot; events happening tomorrow.  Visit http://my.barackobama.com/united to find an event near you.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 30 16:03:37 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Independence, MO.  Speaking about what patriotism means to me. Watch live at: http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 01 21:42:02 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Talked about faith-based initiatives in Zanesville, OH. The challenges we face today are simply too big for government to solve alone.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 04 18:05:29 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Hosting a 4th of July family picnic in Butte, MT and celebrating Malia&apos;s 10th Birthday!  Watch it live: http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 08 01:12:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Announced we are opening the DNC acceptance speech to the public. Learn how you could be chosen to go: http://my.barackobama.com/open</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 08 13:37:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Atlanta, GA. Discussing economic security for American families.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 08 20:32:58 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Washington, DC. Speaking to the League of United Latin American Citizens (LULAC). Watch it live at: http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 09 23:56:53 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In New York, NY.  At an event with Senator Clinton and Caroline Kennedy.  Watch it live stream at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 10 17:14:24 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Fairfax, VA at Robinson Secondary School discussing economic security.  Watch live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jul 14 02:05:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Spoke in San Diego, CA today at the National Council of La Raza&apos;s Annual Conference.  Full video at: http://youtube.com/watch?v=M6LuA_S5sP4</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 15 14:50:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Washington, DC. Delivering an address on Iraq &amp; national security. Watch it live: http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 16 15:47:02 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In West Lafayette, IN at Purdue University. Holding a summit on 21st century threats.  Watch it at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 22 23:15:24 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Landed at Ben Gurion Airport in Israel. Spoke earlier today in Amman, Jordan.  View the video at http://tinyurl.com/5euks9</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 24 16:16:52 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Berlin, Germany. Speaking at approx 1pm ET.  Watch the speech on CNN or streaming live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 25 16:01:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Paris, France with President Nicolas Sarkozy.  Watch the press conference live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jul 26 19:06:26 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Commemorating the Anniv of the Americans with Disabilities Act. Let us recommit ourselves to building a world free of unnecessary barriers.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jul 27 19:53:20 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Back home in Chicago. Spoke at Unity 08 Convention for Journalists of Color at  McCormick Place.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 30 15:04:15 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall on economic security in Springfield, MO this morning.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 30 20:30:44 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall in Rolla, MO.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Aug 01 14:13:32 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall on economic security in St. Petersburg, FL.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Aug 01 22:12:59 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a working for change organizing meeting in Orlando, FL.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 02 14:26:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a Working for Change town hall in Titusville, FL.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 04 15:48:06 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In MI. Announcing a New Energy for America plan. Watch it live: http://my.barackobama.com/livestream More at: http://scribd.com/barackobama</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 05 18:40:39 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a New Energy for America town hall meeting in Berea, OH.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 06 14:03:07 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a New Energy for America town hall meeting in Elkhart, IN.  Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Aug 10 22:00:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Announcing the VP candidate sometime between now &amp; the Convention by txt msg &amp; email. Text VP to 62262 or visit http://my.barackobama.com/vp</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Aug 17 00:22:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Lake Forest, CA at the Saddleback Leadership and Compassion Forum.  Watch it live at CNN or streamed at http://cnn.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Aug 17 22:32:31 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Held a town hall event at Earl Wooster High School in Reno, NV earlier today.  Watch it at: http://tinyurl.com/6dn543</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 18 16:38:43 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Albuquerque, New Mexico. Discussing the need for equal pay.  Watch this discussion live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 18 18:52:40 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall at Rio Grande High School in Albuquerque, NM. Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 19 22:11:19 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall in Raleigh, NC. Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 20 15:29:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Martinsville, VA.  Holding a discussion on protecting American jobs.  Watch it live http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 20 22:48:20 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a town hall meeting In Lynchburg, VA.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 21 14:47:07 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Holding a discussion on the Economy in Chester, VA.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 23 09:22:53 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Announcing Senator Joe Biden as our VP nominee.  Watch the first Obama-Biden rally live at 3pm ET on http://BarackObama.com</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 23 18:51:25 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Springfield, IL.  Holding first campaign event with Senator Joe Biden.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 25 16:58:28 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Davenport, IA. Holding a &quot;One Nation&quot; town hall. Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 26 16:30:38 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Kansas City, MO.  Holding a discussion on &quot;Renewing America&apos;s Promise.&quot;   Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 27 16:11:47 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Billings, MT. Holding a discussion on &quot;Securing America&apos;s Future.&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 30 00:45:49 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Beaver, PA.  At an &quot;On The Road To Change&quot; event.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 30 23:09:45 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Dublin, OH.  At an &quot;On The Road To Change&quot; rally with Joe Biden.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Aug 31 17:32:47 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Toledo, OH.  Holding a discussion on the economy.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 01 22:07:57 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking everyone to give to the Red Cross: give $5 by texting GIVE to 24357 or  by calling 1-800-435-7669 or at http://redcross.org/donate</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 01 22:43:51 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Milwaukee, WI. At a Labor Day Rally for America&apos;s Workers.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 03 16:56:34 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In New Philadelphia, OH. Holding a discussion on &quot;Women And The Economy&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 05 01:45:38 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Campaigning in Pennsylvania. Spoke at the Siemans Hydro Power Plant in York, PA  Watch it at: http://tinyurl.com/65q2xn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 06 16:45:16 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Terre Haute, IN. Holding a &quot;Change We Need&quot; discussion with Indiana families.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 08 18:25:03 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Flint, MI. Holding a discussion on the economy.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 08 22:41:48 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Farmington Hills, MI.  Holding a &quot;Change We Need&quot; town hall.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 09 14:32:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Speaking in Dayton, OH. Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 09 21:32:04 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Lebanon, VA. Holding a  &quot;Change We Need&quot; town hall.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 10 14:16:58 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Norfolk,VA.  Holding a discussion on education.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 12 16:04:25 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Dover, NH. Holding a discussion on &quot;Tax Relief for the Middle Class.&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 12 23:33:02 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Concord, NH at a &quot;Change We Need&quot; event.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 15 22:31:39 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Pueblo, CO.  Holding a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 16 14:58:48 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Speaking in Golden, CO.  Watch the event live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 17 18:45:13 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Elko, NV.  Holding a &quot;Change We Need&quot; community event.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 19 16:27:56 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Coral Gables, FL.  At a &quot;Women&apos;s Rally for the Change We Need.&quot; Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 20 15:00:23 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Daytona Beach, FL. At a &quot;Women for the Change We Need&quot; event.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 20 19:54:07 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally in Jacksonville, FL.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Sep 21 22:25:44 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Spoke in Charlotte, NC today.  Watch part of the speech at http://tinyurl.com/3w2x57</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 23 23:26:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Encouraging everyone to register &amp;amp; vote.  Visit http://VoteForChange.com for registration, absentee &amp;amp; early vote info. Please fo ...</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 24 17:44:52 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Dunedin, FL.  Speaking at a &amp;quot;Change We Need&amp;quot; rally.  Watch it live now at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 26 17:24:44 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Just launched a &quot;Next Generation Veterans for Obama&quot; video on YouTube.  Watch it at http://tinyurl.com/4bfrc4</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 27 00:22:24 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Oxford, Mississippi. Getting ready to debate John McCain.  Watch the debate live at 9pm ET.  Reply with your thoughts after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 27 16:40:03 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At a &#x201c;Change We Need&#x201d; rally with Joe Biden in Greensboro, NC.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Sep 27 23:03:18 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Fredericksburg, VA.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally with Joe Biden.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Sep 28 17:10:52 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Detroit, MI.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally. Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 29 18:10:39 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Denver CO. Speaking at Mountain Range High School.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 30 17:07:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Reno, NV.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 01 14:59:55 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In La Crosse, WI. At a  &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 01 23:16:26 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking you to work on behalf of democracy and register at least 1 or 2 more people to vote. http://tinyurl.com/4hny2a</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 02 14:09:40 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Grand Rapids, MI.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live now at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 02 16:23:33 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Launching an official iPhone App. Tell iPhone users to visit http://barackobama.com/iphone to download the free app &amp; start making calls.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 03 00:52:57 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Watch the VP debate at 9pm ET tonight and cheer on Joe.  Also remind your friends to visit http://voteforchange.com &amp; register to vote.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 03 15:25:12 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Abington, PA.  At a community gathering.  Watch it live now at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Oct 05 02:28:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Spoke early today in Virginia about changing our health care system.  Watch the full speech at http://tinyurl.com/43vzzf</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Oct 05 18:28:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Asheville, NC at a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 07 02:54:25 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking you to get your family involved in this year&apos;s election. Watch http://tinyurl.com/4xu4xj &amp; talk with your family!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 07 23:53:43 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At Belmont University in Nashville, Tenn.  Watch the debate tonight at 9pm ET. Reply with your thoughts after.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 08 16:30:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>With Senator Evan Bayh at a &quot;Change We Need&quot; Rally in Indianapolis, Indiana.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 10 13:52:56 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Chillicothe, OH.  At an &quot;American Jobs Tour&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 10 22:53:23 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Watch Michelle Obama address the DNC Women&apos;s Leadership Forum from Chicago, IL..  Watch it now at http://my.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Oct 11 17:25:10 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In West Philadelphia, PA. At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it now at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 13 17:46:05 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Toledo, OH. Unveiling an &quot;Economic Rescue Plan for the Middle Class&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 13 18:22:05 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Just finished a major policy address in Toledo, OH.  Read my full &quot;Economic Rescue Plan for the Middle Class&quot; at http://tinyurl.com/4nvlyl</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 14 23:30:06 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Launching a tax calculator at http://Taxcut.BarackObama.com. See how much of a tax cut you&apos;ll receive under my tax plan.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 16 00:59:43 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At Hofstra University in Hempstead, NY.  Watch the last presidential debate tonight live at 9pm Eastern.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 17 16:04:10 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Roanoke, VA at a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My/BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Oct 18 17:09:40 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In St. Louis, MO.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.BarackObama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Oct 18 22:56:25 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Kansas City, MO.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Oct 19 22:38:34 +0000 2008</created_at><text>I am beyond honored.  I am deeply humbled to have the support of Gen. Colin Powell.  Learn more at http://tinyurl.com/6fovqf</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 20 17:13:56 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Tampa, FL at an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/LiveStream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 20 22:06:33 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Orlando, FL.  At an &quot;Early Vote for Change Rally&quot; with Hillary Clinton.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 21 15:11:33 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Florida at Palm Beach Community College, Lake Worth Campus.  Watch the event live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 21 22:02:21 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Miami, FL. At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 22 16:52:14 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Richmond, VA.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally at the Richmond Coliseum.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 23 14:47:05 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Indianapolis, IN at the American Legion Mall.  Watch our &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Oct 25 17:11:58 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Reno, NV.  At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Oct 26 18:02:46 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Denver, CO. At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Oct 26 21:22:41 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Fort Collins, CO. At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 27 17:18:11 +0000 2008</created_at><text>At an event at the Canton Memorial Civic Center in Canton, OH. Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 27 21:28:00 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Pittsburgh, PA. At a &quot;Change We Need Rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 28 03:57:23 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Delivered my closing argument earlier today in Canton, Ohio. Watch the full speech at http://tinyurl.com/67pymg</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 28 14:03:47 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Chester, PA.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 28 20:13:45 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Harrisonburg, VA.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch this event live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 29 22:38:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Sunrise Fl. At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 30 03:21:06 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Kissimmee, FL. At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally with President Bill Clinton.  Watch it live: http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 30 15:15:22 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Sarasota, FL. At an &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 31 16:32:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Des Moines, IA &quot;Early Vote for Change&quot; rally. Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 01 16:25:45 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Henderson, NV.  &quot;Change We Need Rally&quot;  Watch it live at http://my.barackobama.com/livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 01 21:31:02 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Pueblo, CO.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally. Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 02 02:31:58 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Springfield, MO. At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally. Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 02 22:44:23 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking you to help in these last few critical days of our campaign for change. Visit http://my.barackobama.com/finaldrive to get involved.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Nov 03 02:14:32 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Cincinnati, OH. At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Nov 03 15:58:54 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Jacksonville, FL. At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 04 03:38:43 +0000 2008</created_at><text>In Manassas, VA.  At a &quot;Change We Need&quot; rally.  Watch it live at http://My.BarackObama.com/Livestream</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 04 04:50:12 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking you to vote Nov. 4th. Visit http://VoteForChange.com, call 877-874-6226 or text VOTE to 62262 to find your polling locations.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 04 19:49:57 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking for your vote today. For polling location info visit http://VoteForChange.com or call 877-874-6226. Make sure everyone votes!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 04 22:42:12 +0000 2008</created_at><text>Asking you to help Get Out the Vote in these last few critical hours of our campaign for change. Visit http://my.barackobama.com/finaldrive</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 05 19:34:59 +0000 2008</created_at><text>We just made history. All of this happened because you gave your time, talent and passion. All of this happened because of you. Thanks</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 16 03:52:31 +0000 2009</created_at><text>To participate in the Inauguration visit http://pic2009.org or text HISTORY to 56333. Follow the Inauguration on Twitter @obamainaugural</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 19 23:01:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>is asking you to honor Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr by volunteering in your area. Visit http://USAservice.org or text SERVE to 56333 for info.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 25 18:04:00 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Question about the economy? Ask President Obama: http://whitehouse.gov/OpenForQuestions</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 28 20:30:52 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Check out the progress made in President Obama&#x2019;s first 100 days: http://tiny.cc/AHwBb</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 30 23:10:21 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Check out what President Obama had to say on his 100th day of office:  http://tinyurl.com/c4pegw</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 01 19:37:12 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The White House just joined Twitter. Follow @whitehouse to get updates on the H1N1 flu and other top issues.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 12 23:26:00 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Declare your support for the President&apos;s 3 core healthcare principles: http://bit.ly/TBxqY Please RT using #obamahealthcare</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 19 15:52:49 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The President will deliver remarks on new auto emission and efficiency standards at 12:15 ET. Watch the live stream: http://bit.ly/19qtmw</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu May 21 01:12:25 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama needs you to tell Congress why health care reform can&apos;t wait: http://bit.ly/5Ahqi   #obamahealthcare</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri May 22 21:56:03 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The fight for real health care reform begins in your neighborhood June 6. Attend a kickoff event: http://bit.ly/15kxp6    #obamahealthcare</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue May 26 20:16:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Video: President Obama announces his Supreme Court nominee: http://bit.ly/1UUPj9</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu May 28 19:42:50 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Join Organizing for America to fight for real health care reform. Host or attend a Health Care Organizing Kickoff: http://bit.ly/cSMlF  #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 03 23:44:30 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Obama lays out health care vision to Senate leaders &amp; reaffirms commitment to a public insurance plan. Build support: http://bit.ly/AenGP</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 04 16:27:06 +0000 2009</created_at><text>&#x201c;I&apos;ve come here to Cairo to seek a new beginning between the United States and Muslims&#x201d; &#x2013; watch the President&#x2019;s speech: http://bit.ly/3lWLt</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 09 16:23:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Thanks to the thousands of people who went to an #OFA Health Care Organizing Kickoff last weekend. Watch the video: http://bit.ly/Aj9hw</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 10 14:48:48 +0000 2009</created_at><text>On Monday Supreme Court Nominee Judge Sotomayor fractured her ankle. Sign her virtual cast: http://bit.ly/nBsg0</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 10 22:37:23 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Check out the #OFA Health Care Action Center - call Congress, display your support, submit a question and more http://bit.ly/fAu60</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 15 22:34:37 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Organize an event for our National Health Care Day of Service on June 27 in your community: http://bit.ly/7AEra #OFA #healthcare</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 18 16:42:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @whitehouse WH Facebook page exclusive: President Obama backstage before ordering Colbert&#x2019;s head-shave http://bit.ly/19UuAB</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 19 20:33:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Just finished a Town Hall discussion on responsibility and fatherhood with five remarkable fathers. #fathersday</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 22 17:30:27 +0000 2009</created_at><text>About to sign the historic Family Smoking Prevention and Tobacco Control Act: http://bit.ly/6y8A8</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 22 20:51:31 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Great news-- pharmaceuticals agree to reduce the price of prescription drugs for millions of America&#x2019;s seniors. http://bit.ly/UCkZS</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 23 16:27:30 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Press conference at 12:30 on energy legislation, Iran, health care and the economy. Watch it live: http://bit.ly/duw9t</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jun 24 20:39:43 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Hosting a town hall on health care reform at the White House today. Watch on ABC tonight at 10pm ET #healthcare09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 25 20:41:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Help pass the American Clean Energy and Security Act -- crucial to creating a clean energy economy: http://bit.ly/aWcDK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jun 25 22:54:22 +0000 2009</created_at><text>These stories show why affordable health care for every American can&apos;t wait: http://bit.ly/13Bm5M #healthcare09 PLS RT</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jun 26 16:06:42 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The House is voting on a historic clean energy bill today. Have you called your representative about it? http://bit.ly/aWcDK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jun 27 00:43:10 +0000 2009</created_at><text>House passes historic clean energy and climate bill today, thanks to your grassroots support.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jun 28 00:02:31 +0000 2009</created_at><text>1 in 5 Americans with HIV doesn&apos;t know it. Please share this National HIV Testing Day video: http://bit.ly/8h7p1 #NHTD09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jun 29 18:43:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Holding online town hall on health care reform this Weds. Watch the vid &amp; submit your q&apos;s: http://bit.ly/U3pgV #healthcare09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 30 16:37:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The @WhiteHouse is unveiling new government transparency tool today. Join the live chat at 5pm ET: http://bit.ly/duw9t</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jun 30 19:55:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Exciting celebration of LGBT Pride Month at the @WhiteHouse yesterday. http://bit.ly/Ac3g0</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 01 16:10:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Don&apos;t forget -- online town hall on health care reform today at 1:15pm ET http://bit.ly/zOtW6 #WHHCQ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 02 18:09:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Meeting with business leaders from both small and large companies this afternoon to discuss innovation and job creation</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 10 15:08:03 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Congress in crucial health care reform negotiations. More than ever, your reps need to hear from you: http://bit.ly/1StOJ3</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jul 13 18:04:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Watch Judge Sotomayor&apos;s opening statement at 2:30pm on any cable news channel, or stream it here: http://bit.ly/uS90Q</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 14 23:14:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Wrapping up day two of Sotomayor hearings. Direct &amp; precise, her words speak for themselves: http://bit.ly/3svnCn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 15 13:55:39 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Launched American Graduation Initiative to help additional 5 mill. Americans graduate college by 2020: http://bit.ly/gcTX7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 15 19:48:28 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Donate to Organizing for America&apos;s health care campaign by 12am Thurs, and you could come to Chicago: http://bit.ly/oBaO7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 15 22:47:16 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Spoke with members of the American Nurses Association today on the urgent need for health care reform: http://bit.ly/tbJHj</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 16 01:08:57 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Congratulations to CA Rep. Judy Chu district on becoming the first Chinese American woman elected to Congress</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 17 19:22:42 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Speaking on health care reform. Watch live at http://bit.ly/GOZOt #healthcare09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 21 20:40:04 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Health care reform opponents scale up attacks, playing politics w/ our lives &amp; livelihood. Fight back: http://bit.ly/1bciXx</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 22 21:21:58 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Holding primetime news conference on health care @ 8pm tonight. Watch it live &amp; declare your support: http://bit.ly/17OkdA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jul 23 18:52:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Missed the primetime news conference last night? Watch it here and declare your support: http://bit.ly/88RCW</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 24 21:49:25 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Almost 1 million public supporters of health insurance reform. Help us get there: http://bit.ly/23QIba</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jul 27 23:43:16 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Are you calling &amp; writing members of congress re: health insurance reform? Now you can tweet them too: http://bit.ly/vIe0J</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 28 17:17:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tele-town hall with AARP on health insurance reform today. Listen live at 1:30pm ET: http://bit.ly/22W1EH (via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jul 28 23:56:45 +0000 2009</created_at><text>To small business owners: your input is crucial in the health insurance reform debate. Please weigh in: http://bit.ly/Wj3J1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jul 29 16:59:34 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Announcing eight fundamental health insurance consumer protections: http://bit.ly/1RBlHd #hc09 (via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jul 31 19:17:45 +0000 2009</created_at><text>For #FollowFriday #ff: @WhiteHouse and @DemocratsDotOrg</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 04 18:31:56 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Lots of disinformation on health insurance reform out there. Learn/share the facts: http://bit.ly/191Bzz #hc09 (Via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 06 17:28:21 +0000 2009</created_at><text>In August, the health insurance reform debate comes home. This is the moment our movement was built for: http://bit.ly/Vpiis</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Aug 07 16:59:12 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Members of Congress need to know how much support there is at home for reform. Please call your Rep&apos;s local office: http://bit.ly/4EeGB</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Aug 08 20:31:54 +0000 2009</created_at><text>History was made today when Sonia Sotomayor took the judicial oath and joined the Supreme Court. Congratulations, Justice.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 10 19:51:15 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Get the straight facts about health insurance reform: http://bit.ly/2NGoii #hcr #hc09 (Via the @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 11 22:46:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>In NH today to discuss ending insurance discrimination for preexisting conditions. Watch Kristen&apos;s story: http://bit.ly/3l4vc #hcr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 18 16:00:29 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Read the op-ed in the @nytimes on why we need health care reform: http://bit.ly/1vvi2a</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 18 22:39:34 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Join me for a live OFA strategy meeting on the state of health insurance reform this Thurs at 2:30pm ET: http://bit.ly/qZk8Z</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 19 18:44:05 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Submit questions &amp; thoughts for the health care strategy meeting by tweeting @BarackObama using the #hc09 hashtag: http://bit.ly/qZk8Z</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 17:08:54 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Organizing for America staff will be live-tweeting today&apos;s health care strategy meeting. Join in at 2:30pm ET: http://bit.ly/qZk8Z #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 18:20:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>OFA staff here, about to begin live-tweeting the strategy mtg w/ Pres. Obama. Join in: http://bit.ly/O1QRt. You can use #hc09 to discuss.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 18:52:16 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;We should be proud of what we&#x2019;ve accomplished, but we&apos;re not satisfied. We&#x2019;ve got more work to do.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 18:59:05 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;One of the options we want to provide&#x2026;is a public option.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 19:03:49 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;I want everybody to remember that this has never been easy.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 19:05:26 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;We&apos;re going to have a lot of work to do. I&apos;m grateful that you&apos;re willing to do it.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 19:14:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;Health care&#x2026; is subject to a lot of misinformation. That&apos;s why your work is so important&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 19:50:39 +0000 2009</created_at><text>&quot;We are not going to give up now. We are going to get this done, and show the American people that govt can work for them.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 20 19:51:01 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Thanks to everyone who joined the conversation on #hc09. Enjoy the rest of your afternoon!  -- OFA staff</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Aug 24 23:32:51 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Let&apos;s get it done. Host or attend a &quot;Health Insurance Reform Now&quot; event this week: http://bit.ly/MbbNg</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 25 01:32:22 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Spread the truth: How to respond to the lie that health reform means &quot;pulling the plug on grandma&quot; http://bit.ly/1WWuu4 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Aug 25 19:33:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Spread the truth: Don&apos;t let opponents of reform play partisan politics with health care. http://bit.ly/1aeWiG #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Aug 26 19:12:31 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Mourning the death of Sen. Ted Kennedy&#x2014;a dear friend, a wise colleague, and one of the greatest US senators of our time. http://bit.ly/fI7Ve</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 27 01:43:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Highlights from the tribute to Sen. Kennedy&apos;s life and accomplishments from last year&apos;s Democratic National Convention: http://bit.ly/TJcyr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Aug 27 19:38:11 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Spread the truth: Reform will prevent insurance companies from rationing your care. http://bit.ly/3ev3Aj #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 01 00:04:55 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Spread the truth: VP Biden busts the myth that our health insurance system doesn&apos;t need reform. http://bit.ly/I0zQS #hc09 (via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 03 16:56:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>This summer, we unleashed a powerful movement for change. See the latest dispatches from the ground: http://bit.ly/6SGna</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 08 15:42:04 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Welcoming the nation&apos;s students back to school&#x2014;watch today at noon ET: http://bit.ly/17eoNf</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 08 21:23:11 +0000 2009</created_at><text>It should never be controversial to ask our students to stay in school. Watch today&apos;s speech: http://bit.ly/cDO8F</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 08 23:36:30 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Addressing Congress on health reform tomorrow at 8pm ET. Sign up to host or attend a watch party with fellow supporters: http://bit.ly/oILrt</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 09 17:50:44 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Addressing a joint session of Congress on health reform tonight&#x2014;tune in at 8pm ET: http://bit.ly/m3OXQ Discuss via #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 09 23:24:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The health reform address to Congress will begin at 8pm ET. Watch it live on TV or online here: http://bit.ly/3ZJN93 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 09 23:52:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>OFA will be live-tweeting the special address to Congress, beginning at 8pm ET. Watch it live: http://bit.ly/3ZJN93</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 09 23:53:30 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Be sure to stay tuned after the address for a live Q&amp;A with Anita Dunn, White House Communications Director, who will take your questions.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:19:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;I am not the first president to take up this cause, but I am determined to be the last.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:26:19 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;Put simply, our health care problem IS our deficit problem.  Nothing else even comes close.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:27:25 +0000 2009</created_at><text>&quot;There is agreement in this chamber on about 80% of what needs to be done, putting us closer to the goal of reform than we&apos;ve ever been&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:28:21 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;The time for bickering is over. The time for games has passed. Now is the season for action.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:28:54 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The 3 basic goals of health reform: A) To provide security and stability to Americans with health insurance&#x2026; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:29:07 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The 3 basic goals of health reform: B) To provide affordable coverage to those currently without insurance&#x2026; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:29:15 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The 3 basic goals of health reform: C) To slow the growth of health care costs for our families, our businesses, and our government #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:29:37 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;It&#x2019;s a plan that incorporates ideas from Senators and Congressmen; from Democrats and Republicans.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:43:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pres. Obama: &quot;We can keep insurance companies honest by making a not-for-profit public option available in the insurance exchange.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:46:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;I will not sign a plan that adds one dime to our deficits &#x2013; either now or in the future. Period.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:53:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>&quot;The plan will cost&#x2026;less than the tax cuts for the wealthiest few Americans that Congress passed during the previous administration.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 00:55:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>&quot;Know this: I will not waste time with those who have made the calculation that it&#x2019;s better politics to kill this plan than improve it&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 01:03:27 +0000 2009</created_at><text>President Obama: &quot;I still believe we can do great things, and that here and now we will meet history&#x2019;s test.&quot; #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 02:02:34 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Congress knows where I stand. Now they need to hear from you: http://bit.ly/1a5uDl #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 18:31:55 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Members of Congress need to know you support the plan laid out in last night&apos;s address. Please call your reps today: http://bit.ly/12CO0C</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Sep 10 22:12:13 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Watch the stories of the two parents who joined the First Lady for last night&apos;s address: http://bit.ly/zmKQ3 (via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 14 00:55:56 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Please watch this special message, and if you haven&apos;t already, tell your members of Congress you support reform: http://bit.ly/9RHAe</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 14 16:10:06 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Delivering a speech to Wall Street on the need for financial reform. Listen live: http://bit.ly/17eoNf</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 15 22:02:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Your voice on twitter can help pass health reform &#x2014; tweet your reps today: http://bit.ly/LA253 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 16 20:41:19 +0000 2009</created_at><text>You and a few friends can help pass health reform on your lunch break: http://bit.ly/RZN59 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 18 15:27:39 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Exciting news&#x2014;House passes biggest overhaul of student aid program since the 1960&apos;s: http://bit.ly/1GN1Rx</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 21 22:33:37 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Every American needs to know what health insurance reform means for them. Take a moment to find out: http://bit.ly/4BnpJt #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Sep 21 23:38:57 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Feeling fired up and ready to go on health insurance reform&#x2014;let&apos;s get this done. Watch the video: http://bit.ly/4gtmy7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Sep 23 19:46:00 +0000 2009</created_at><text>In New York, meeting with world leaders at the United Nations. Watch the speech: http://bit.ly/2Z4d3J</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Sep 25 14:35:13 +0000 2009</created_at><text>VP Biden spent time Wednesday debunking myths on seniors &amp; health reform. Share this with a senior in your life: http://bit.ly/3SolSr #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Sep 29 16:39:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Have video skills? Want to help pass health reform? Enter OFA&apos;s Health Reform Video Challenge: http://bit.ly/SHdr3 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 05 19:01:38 +0000 2009</created_at><text>If you have an election coming, make sure to register to vote&#x2014;Virginians, your deadline&apos;s today. Learn more: http://bit.ly/3u1SAP</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 06 20:31:36 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Doctors and nurses across the country support health reform: http://bit.ly/2cE3h Help spread the word: http://bit.ly/1xvNeq</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 09 15:31:28 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Humbled.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Oct 10 17:39:01 +0000 2009</created_at><text>We&apos;re working on generating 100,000 calls to Congress for reform. You can help&#x2014;host a call party: http://bit.ly/rvmh6 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 14 03:23:44 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Health reform just took a huge step&#x2014;but the insurance lobby is working hard to stop it. Urge Congress to pass real reform: http://u.nu/6jhi3</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 15 23:07:03 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Health reform debate moving soon to the full Congress. It&apos;s time to be heard. Help OFA reach 100,000 calls on 10/20: http://bit.ly/10-20</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 16 21:22:25 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Have you signed up to host a &quot;Time to Deliver&quot; event in your area on 10/20 yet? http://bit.ly/10-20 #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 19 18:49:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Health insurers are trying to mislead you&#x2014;but their smoke and mirrors won&apos;t work this time. Watch: http://bit.ly/1qtBtn #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 19 23:32:36 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tomorrow, help #OFA generate 100,000 calls to Congress. Find a call party near you: http://bit.ly/44fyhM #hco9 #CallCongress</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 14:46:03 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Today is the day&#x2014;can you help #OFA generate 100,000 health reform calls to Congress in a single day? http://bit.ly/ls1PC #hc09 #CallCongress</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 16:02:58 +0000 2009</created_at><text>You&apos;ve made 35,000 calls to Congress already! Help us get to 100,000: http://bit.ly/ls1PC #hc09 #CallCongress #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 16:49:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Halfway there&#x2014;you&apos;ve already made 50,000 calls to Congress. Help us reach 100,000: http://bit.ly/ls1PC #hc09 #CallCongress #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 18:33:05 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Amazing&#x2014;you made 100K calls to Congress in a single day. Can we get to 150K? http://bit.ly/ls1PC #hc09 #CallCongress #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 20:36:22 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Unbelievable. 150K calls to Congress today. Let&apos;s go for 200K: http://bit.ly/tkU6l #hc09 #CallCongress #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Oct 20 23:45:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Will you join me for a live webcast for #OFA supporters at 8:00pm ET? http://bit.ly/2J9EK #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 21 00:39:26 +0000 2009</created_at><text>226,317 calls and counting. You made this day historic, and took us a giant step closer to passing reform. Thank you.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 21 21:42:40 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Yesterday&apos;s final tally: 315,023 calls placed or pledged. Watch the online address to #OFA: http://bit.ly/47xxc4 #hc09 #CallCongress</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 23 19:51:38 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Inspired as usual by Michelle. Watch her discuss what health reform means to her as a woman and a mom: http://bit.ly/4cKsIK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Oct 26 21:21:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Congratulations @SenChrisDodd, @SenatorReid and Sen. Baucus for your hard work towards health reform with a public option.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Oct 28 00:16:58 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Our Health Reform Video Challenge finalists showcase the creativity and passion you bring to this debate. Watch and vote: http://bit.ly/HR-</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 29 00:41:18 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Signed a bill today that protects citizens from violence based on what they look like, who they love or how they pray: http://bit.ly/HCB-</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Oct 29 21:57:18 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Congrats to the House for introducing strong, fully paid-for health reform legislation that includes a public option: http://bit.ly/n33d7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 30 20:09:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Recovery Act is creating jobs&#x2014;over 650k so far, according to data published today. Learn more: http://bit.ly/IEPkI</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Oct 30 21:53:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Which user-created health reform ad do you think will have the biggest impact? Rate the videos now: http://bit.ly/3tFjDx</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 03 21:09:40 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @DemocratsDotOrg In many places around the country, today is Election Day. Help get out the vote: http://bit.ly/26Zfz3</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 04 00:08:42 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tomorrow will mark a year since our historic victory. Do you have a favorite 2008 Election Day memory? Share your stories via #Nov4</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 05 00:02:06 +0000 2009</created_at><text>#Nov4 2008 stories have poured in over the last 24 hours. Sharing a few...</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 05 00:04:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Kathy recalls #Nov4 2008: &quot;People danced; people sang. I had a feeling that the country had somehow changed in one evening.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 05 00:05:19 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Kate recalls #Nov4: &quot;Standing in silence in a room full of campaign workers watching the acceptance speech, thinking anything is possible.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 05 00:07:16 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Erik recalls #Nov4 2008: &quot;Talking to my mother who grew up in pre-civil rights America and the history felt that day when she voted.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 05 20:15:55 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Pleased and grateful to learn that the AARP &amp; the @AmerMedicalAssn are supporting the House health reform bill. #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Nov 06 21:03:49 +0000 2009</created_at><text>This is it&#x2014;the House is voting on health reform legislation tomorrow. Tweet your rep and ask them to support reform: http://bit.ly/3AEkDz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 07 16:19:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Addressing members of Congress before the historic House vote on health reform. They need to hear from you today, too: http://bit.ly/3AEkDz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 07 18:52:50 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Finished meeting on the Hill. 4 hours before the big vote, reps are fired up and ready to go. Add your voice: http://bit.ly/3AEkDz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 07 23:23:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>House vote on health reform is imminent. This is a once-in-a-generation moment. Be part of it: http://bit.ly/3AEkDz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 03:42:50 +0000 2009</created_at><text>It&apos;s time&#x2014;the House vote is about to begin. Only minutes remain to weigh in, but every minute counts. Be heard: http://bit.ly/3AEkDz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 04:15:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>This is history.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 04:25:07 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @timryan House passes historic reform to provide health care for every American. Congratulating my colleagues on the floor.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 04:26:46 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @chelliepingree We won!!!!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 04:29:19 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @repblumenauer House did its job, now the ball is in the Senate&apos;s court. Don&apos;t let America down and let&apos;s get this done!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 04:32:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @kendrickbmeek Historic moment. Historic vote. We delivered on our promise to the American people.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 08 05:08:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @JimOberstar: Health Care Reform Passes!!! 220 to 215</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 11 00:46:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>With gratitude for the lives they led: http://bit.ly/1cZlfe #FortHood</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 11 15:49:21 +0000 2009</created_at><text>To the men and women who have served and are currently serving around the world: Thank You. http://bit.ly/R6a3u #VeteransDay</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 12 23:06:54 +0000 2009</created_at><text>En route to Asia. Follow the trip on the @WhiteHouse blog: http://bit.ly/2utjFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 15 03:42:26 +0000 2009</created_at><text>In Singapore, continuing the visit to Asia. Watch trip updates by staff on the @WhiteHouse blog: http://bit.ly/3s4PCD http://bit.ly/16W8YM</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 19 03:24:29 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Senate has released a health reform bill that secures and extends affordable coverage while reducing our deficit. Now that&apos;s progress.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Nov 20 19:05:21 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The senate has unveiled an excellent health reform bill. Call your senators and ask them to move forward: http://bit.ly/8Ar4yG #hc09</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Nov 21 20:14:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tweet your senators and ask them to support moving forward with the health reform bill in tonight&apos;s critical vote: http://bit.ly/5hSmDo</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 22 01:08:50 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Senate just voted to begin debate on a comprehensive health reform bill. America is now closer to real reform than ever in our history.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 24 17:20:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Welcoming Prime Minister Singh of India for the first state visit of this administration. Watch: http://bit.ly/6frh-</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Nov 24 21:56:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Reform must control health costs. One economist says &quot;you couldn&apos;t have done better&quot; than the Senate bill. Read why: http://bit.ly/5S76CE</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 25 00:12:28 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Help build support for the Senate&apos;s historic health reform bill. Write a letter to the editor of your local paper: http://bit.ly/5iRBHe</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 25 17:02:11 +0000 2009</created_at><text>It&apos;s official: Heading to Copenhagen on Dec. 9 to participate in the UN Climate Change Conference. Read more about it: http://bit.ly/4xn1X6</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Nov 25 22:52:02 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Video: The season&apos;s luckiest turkey http://bit.ly/8IRgrg</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Nov 26 15:52:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>From my family to yours &#x2014; Happy Thanksgiving.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Nov 27 20:08:27 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Check out the @WhiteHouse&apos;s November photos featuring yesterday&apos;s trip to Martha&apos;s Table, shots from China and more: http://bit.ly/5jSfYQ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Nov 29 00:13:35 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Michelle receives this year&apos;s White House Christmas tree yesterday. Watch the video: http://bit.ly/4o90RN</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Nov 30 19:50:10 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Video: Health care professionals join Vice President Biden to discuss why health reform matters so much: http://bit.ly/7VSdqI</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 01 17:03:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tune in tonight for an address that will lay out the path forward in Afghanistan. http://bit.ly/5UQoD1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 01 20:35:51 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Secretary of State Clinton announces 2012 Int&apos;l AIDS conference to be held in U.S.: http://bit.ly/8Bc- #WorldAIDSDay</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 02 00:50:28 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The address to the nation on Afghanistan is about to begin&#x2014;tune in at 8:00pm ET. http://bit.ly/5UQoD1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 02 17:29:36 +0000 2009</created_at><text>In case you missed it last night, watch the address that lays out the way forward in Afghanistan: http://bit.ly/4IS8n7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 03 16:38:28 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Jobs and Economic Growth Forum is taking place at the @WhiteHouse today. Watch the events streamed live: http://bit.ly/17eoNf</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 03 22:03:52 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The National Christmas Tree Lighting begins in a few minutes. Watch it at 5pm ET: http://wh.gov/live</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 04 20:01:09 +0000 2009</created_at><text>We still have a long way to go. One job lost is one job too many. Still, this is good news: http://bit.ly/7xGyUn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 07 17:53:48 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Today we pay tribute to those brave men and women who made the ultimate sacrifice for our country at Pearl Harbor.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 07 19:35:47 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Watch the town hall meeting last Friday in Allentown, Pa., about the job situation: http://bit.ly/7nQ0WZ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 07 22:15:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Over 38k federal workers offered ideas on making gov&apos;t more efficient. Help choose the one to include in the budget: http://SaveAward.gov</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 08 15:59:18 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Watch live at 11am ET: @WhiteHouse CIO Vivek Kundra and CTO Aneesh Chopra announce the new Open Government Plan: http://bit.ly/6frhMq</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 08 18:09:09 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Yesterday we took important steps toward solving the global problem of climate change. Read more: http://bit.ly/78HrDn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 09 00:43:33 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Tough times, brightening skies. Watch today&apos;s address on job creation: http://bit.ly/68zRzr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 09 18:43:32 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Video: Vice President Biden puts the health reform debate into common-sense terms http://bit.ly/4wZJtO</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 10 18:10:50 +0000 2009</created_at><text>With a creative new framework, the Senate has made critical progress toward the historic final passage of health reform. http://bit.ly/6t-P</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 11 20:53:54 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Send a holiday card to your senators telling them your wish this season is for them to pass health reform: http://bit.ly/7DB3wb</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 11 23:19:16 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Sending warmest wishes to all who are celebrating Hanukkah around the world.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Dec 12 21:07:59 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Phony arguments and bad habits can&apos;t be allowed to lead to another meltdown. We need real financial reform: http://bit.ly/4JW4np</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 15 21:01:00 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Ever wondered what the &quot;organizing&quot; in Organizing for America really means? Watch this video to find out: http://bit.ly/6FoAqd</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 01:06:20 +0000 2009</created_at><text>We are on the precipice of big changes&#x2014;the most significant reform of our health care since the passage of Medicare. http://bit.ly/5z9oXL</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 01:15:48 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The stakes are enormous&#x2014;if we don&apos;t get this done, your premiums are guaranteed to go up. http://bit.ly/5z9oXL</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 01:27:40 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Reform will save families money, will save businesses money and will save government money. It has to pass on our watch. http://bit.ly/5-z9</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 16:40:44 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Since August, OFA supporters have made over 800k calls to Congress to support health reform. Help break 1 million today: http://bit.ly/5-b</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 18:32:30 +0000 2009</created_at><text>We just passed 850k calls to Congress. Help break 1 million today -- call the Capitol switchboard at 202-559-1161 right away.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 16 21:45:43 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The stakes are too high to allow our differences to prevent us from passing reform. Call Congress: 202-559-1161</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 17 02:47:19 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Today, we reached a total of 1,008,426 calls (and counting) to Congress in support of health reform. Congratulations, and thank you.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 17 17:35:00 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The winter garden is in at the @WhiteHouse, ready to grow food year-round: http://bit.ly/4qSqyK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 17 18:53:41 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The reforms we&apos;re about to achieve will offer immediate benefits to families and small businesses: http://bit.ly/6VyvHL #hcr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 18 18:56:03 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Solving America&apos;s problems is going to require seriousness of purpose here in Washington&#x2014;not political games like this. http://bit.ly/8wSltO</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 18 23:05:40 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Organizing for America community came together to make a personalized holiday video for you. Enjoy. http://bit.ly/4stHmg</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Dec 19 03:14:24 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Today we&apos;ve made a meaningful breakthrough on climate change&#x2014;but we have much further still to go. http://bit.ly/5-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Dec 19 15:51:31 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Please read this&#x2014;Vicki Kennedy says it&apos;s time to pass #hcr and finish the work of her late husband&apos;s life: http://bit.ly/4ZRfRm</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Dec 20 21:46:08 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Biden today: #hcr &quot;includes the fundamental, essential change that opponents &#x2026; have resisted for generations.&quot; Read: http://bit.ly/7QcRX2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 21 20:32:48 +0000 2009</created_at><text>If you haven&apos;t already, be sure to send your loved ones a personalized holiday video this season: http://bit.ly/6s3Ah1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 21 22:26:05 +0000 2009</created_at><text>RT @SenatorReid: I&apos;m happy to hear the docs of the @AmerMedicalAssn support the Senate #hcr bill. Read the AMA letter: http://bit.ly/7hWA52</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 22 16:50:56 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The @NYTimes supports #hcr: &quot;the U.S. Senate has a chance this week ... to pass a historic piece of legislation.&quot; http://bit.ly/6Z0WXd</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 22 23:34:10 +0000 2009</created_at><text>This is what the Senate health reform bill will do for America: http://bit.ly/5-h. Please share this list with your friends and family #hcr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 23 00:07:10 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Forget to mail your holiday cards? Personalize this video for your friends and family: http://bit.ly/6s3Ah1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 23 15:16:55 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Wishing for health reform this holiday season? Sign this card to Congress: http://bit.ly/6lC2Ax</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 24 02:14:14 +0000 2009</created_at><text>On the brink of a major milestone -- the Senate set to vote on the historic health insurance reform bill tomorrow at 7am ET.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 24 12:54:57 +0000 2009</created_at><text>The Senate just passed health reform. Thanks to all who made this moment possible.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Dec 24 18:29:29 +0000 2009</created_at><text>OFA supporters are thanking the senators who made passing today&apos;s historic #hcr bill possible. Will you join them? http://bit.ly/8-M</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Dec 25 19:06:53 +0000 2009</created_at><text>To all those gathered in celebration today, Merry Christmas.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Dec 28 23:56:46 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Update on attempted Christmas Day terrorist attack and our next steps to ensure safety and security: http://bit.ly/6-0 (via @WhiteHouse)</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Dec 29 17:24:23 +0000 2009</created_at><text>Best wishes to all those celebrating Kwanzaa this holiday season.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Dec 30 20:23:43 +0000 2009</created_at><text>This has been a remarkable year. Read about what OFA supporters accomplished in 2009: http://bit.ly/5-q</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 01 05:00:20 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Happy New Year!</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 04 19:14:50 +0000 2010</created_at><text>As we kick off 2010, our Twitter community has grown to over 3 million. I continue to be grateful for your partnership as we work for change</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 04 22:39:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Watch this week&apos;s address on the Christmas Day attempted act of terrorism, and the broader strategy to fight Al Qaeda: http://bit.ly/6sGoaW</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 04 23:48:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Can you take a minute to fill out a quick survey on what&apos;s next for Organizing for America in 2010? http://bit.ly/74IZhF</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 05 23:35:24 +0000 2010</created_at><text>An important reminder about health reform on the @WhiteHouse blog today: http://bit.ly/8QFBbt #hcr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 06 18:15:47 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Watch yesterday&apos;s address for the latest on what we&apos;re doing to keep America safe: http://bit.ly/7oqhYX</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 06 20:26:45 +0000 2010</created_at><text>You do incredible work -- and right now is the perfect time to remember where we came from. http://bit.ly/6SUbAl #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 07 20:52:51 +0000 2010</created_at><text>To @SenChrisDodd: While your work in the Senate is not yet done, the loss of your leadership is already felt. Thank you for your service.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 08 00:20:43 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Read the urgent security review conducted by the administration in the wake of the failed Christmas terrorist attack: http://bit.ly/5yCKon</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 08 20:04:14 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Secretary Sebelius discusses how health reform will provide secure and stable insurance for American families -- Watch: http://bit.ly/8-u</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 11 21:19:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>This week&apos;s address: how reform will immediately start building a new foundation for American families. Watch: http://bit.ly/4BIS2o</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 12 17:36:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join a week of @WhiteHouse policy discussions&#x2014;today at 3pm ET, chat live w/ Ben Rhodes of the National Security Council: http://bit.ly/o-N</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 13 00:05:12 +0000 2010</created_at><text>For health reform and so much else, we need to elect @MarthaCoakley to the Senate next week. Call key MA voters tonight: http://bit.ly/F-K</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 13 17:58:22 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today, our thoughts and prayers are with the people of Haiti. Learn about relief efforts and how you can help: http://bit.ly/o-X</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 13 22:10:09 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The insurance industry: secretly spending millions to kill the reforms that have eluded us for generations. http://bit.ly/5CuXE8 #hcr</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 14 18:52:40 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The first waves of our rescue workers are on the ground and at work in #Haiti&#x2014;Watch today&apos;s update and learn how to help: http://bit.ly/6-x</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 15 16:05:25 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join Christina Romer, Chair of the Council of Economic Advisers, for a live chat on the economy today at 12pm ET: http://bit.ly/7-e</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 15 18:45:31 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Pres. Preval of #Haiti, by phone, to you: &quot;From the bottom of my heart &amp; on behalf of the Haitian people, thank you, thank you, thank you.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 15 23:43:20 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We want our money back and we&apos;re going to get it. Add your voice: http://bit.ly/7UBSRe</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jan 16 22:08:26 +0000 2010</created_at><text>To get the job done on health reform, we need to elect @MarthaCoakley to the Senate on Tuesday. Call key MA voters today: http://bit.ly/F-K</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jan 17 19:16:57 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Rallying for @MarthaCoakley in Boston today. Help make sure we get the job done on health reform--Call 5 MA voters: http://bit.ly/7-p</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jan 17 21:44:13 +0000 2010</created_at><text>If big financial firms can afford massive bonuses, they can afford to pay back the American people. Watch: http://bit.ly/V-8</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jan 17 22:43:05 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Presidents Clinton and Bush have issued a call to action&#x2014;Join the relief efforts of the Clinton Bush Haiti Fund: http://bit.ly/5-x</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 18 20:11:40 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today we honor the legacy and ideals of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Watch Sunday&apos;s remarks in DC: http://bit.ly/8-e #MLK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 18 22:02:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Polls open in MA tomorrow. For health reform, help get out the vote for @MarthaCoakley. Call 5 voters now: http://bit.ly/7-p #MASen</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 19 16:17:21 +0000 2010</created_at><text>This is it&#x2014;the polls are open in MA. Your calls can help send Martha Coakley to the Senate: http://bit.ly/7-5 #MASen Pls RT</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 19 18:58:28 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Let your friends in MA know where to go vote today&#x2014;Tell them to text PLACE to 62262, or send them this link: http://bit.ly/8-O #MASen</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 19 21:29:14 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The #MASen race is in a dead heat. Polls close in 4 hours &amp; every vote is crucial. Make 5 more calls for Martha Coakley: http://bit.ly/7-5</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 19 23:45:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Volunteers at OFA HQ are calling non-stop to get the #MASen vote out: http://bit.ly/7-q. There&apos;s 1 hr left&#x2014;can you call 5 more voters?</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 00:03:04 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Yesterday&#x2019;s election shows discontent with the pace of change&#x2014;a frustration I share.  We must move forward and keep working together.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 03:35:28 +0000 2010</created_at><text>To mark today&apos;s anniversary, @WhiteHouse Photographer Pete Souza shares some special moments from the past year: http://bit.ly/7-R</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 18:39:47 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Now taking nominations for the Citizen&apos;s Medal&#x2014;one of the highest civilian honors in our nation. Nominate an everyday hero: http://bit.ly/-u</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 21:06:38 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Never again will taxpayers be held hostage by a bank that is too big to fail. Learn about the reforms I&apos;ve proposed: http://bit.ly/7ta55g</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 23:03:09 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today&apos;s Supreme Court ruling gives special interests more power, and undermines the influence of average Americans. http://bit.ly/7-a</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 21 23:04:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The @WhiteHouse will work immediately w/ bipartisan Congressional leaders to develop a forceful response to this decision http://bit.ly/-I</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 22 00:41:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Next Wednesday, OFA members will gather across the country to watch the State of the Union address. Host a #WatchParty: http://bit.ly/5tGDud</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 22 18:06:23 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @WhiteHouse: Clinton: &quot;New technologies do not take sides in the struggle for freedom and progress, but the US does&quot; http://bit.ly/70GZMY</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Jan 22 23:19:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>So long as I have the privilege of serving as your President, I&apos;ll never stop fighting for you&#x2014;on #HCR and so much more. http://bit.ly/7-l</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Jan 24 18:11:26 +0000 2010</created_at><text>David Plouffe&apos;s @WashingtonPost op-ed today reminds us why November doesn&apos;t need to be a nightmare for Democrats: http://bit.ly/5-1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 25 19:29:31 +0000 2010</created_at><text>On this week&apos;s address: the recent Supreme Court ruling, and its potentially devastating effect on our democracy. Watch: http://bit.ly/A-q</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Jan 25 23:06:02 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Announced new steps, along with Vice President Biden today, to aid America&apos;s middle-class families. Read about them: http://bit.ly/7CVE0H</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Jan 26 21:54:41 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow OFA supporters will gather across the country to watch the State of the Union. Sign up for a #WatchParty near you http://bit.ly/a-H</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 27 17:43:14 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tonight at 9pm ET, tune in to the State of the Union address on TV, online: http://bit.ly/p-o or on your iPhone: http://bit.ly/V-P</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Jan 27 19:08:19 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join an OFA strategy call with David Plouffe at a State of the Union #WatchParty near you: http://bit.ly/a-H</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 01:17:50 +0000 2010</created_at><text>OFA staff will be tweeting highlights from tonight&apos;s #SOTU address. Watch live at 9pm ET: http://bit.ly/p-o</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:16:37 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;America prevailed because we chose to move forward as one nation. Again, we are tested. And again we must answer history&#x2019;s call.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:19:53 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;It is because of the spirit and resilience of Americans that I have never been more hopeful about America&#x2019;s future than I am tonight&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:22:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;The bank bailout was about as popular as a root canal. But I promised I wouldn&#x2019;t just do what was popular&#x2014;I would do what was necessary.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:25:07 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;Because of the Recovery Act, there are about two million Americans working right now who would otherwise be unemployed.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:29:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;People are out of work. They are hurting. They need our help. And I want a jobs bill on my desk without delay.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:37:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;We can&#x2019;t allow financial institutions, including those that take your deposits, to take risks that threaten the whole economy.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:38:37 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;The nation that leads the clean energy economy will be the nation that leads the global economy. And America must be that nation.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:41:20 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;In the 21st century, one of the best anti-poverty programs is a world-class education.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 02:47:45 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;I will not walk away from the millions of Americans who need health care, and neither should the people in this chamber.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 03:09:39 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;All of our men and women in uniform around the world must know that they have our respect, our gratitude, and our full support.&quot; #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 03:17:29 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;I never said change would be easy. When you try to do big things &amp; make big changes it stirs passions &amp; controversy&#x2014;that&#x2019;s just how it is.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 03:20:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>&quot;We don&#x2019;t quit. I don&#x2019;t quit. Let&#x2019;s seize this moment&#x2014;to start anew, to carry the dream forward, and to strengthen our union once more.&quot;</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 20:05:37 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Help me show that Americans are ready to join the fight for the middle class&#x2014;add your name to a letter to Congress: http://bit.ly/b-8 #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Jan 28 23:57:51 +0000 2010</created_at><text>If you missed it, watch the State of the Union here: http://bit.ly/b-F and submit a follow-up question via @YouTube: http://bit.ly/c3ixy6</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jan 30 16:41:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>If you haven&apos;t already seen video of yesterday&apos;s #questiontime, check it out: http://bit.ly/9-y</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Jan 30 20:17:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Departing the Duke-Georgetown game. Two great teams -- great game.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 01 16:53:48 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Answering your questions on the State of our Union today at 1:45pm ET. Watch live: http://bit.ly/7-e #SOTU</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 02 21:32:17 +0000 2010</created_at><text>On Thursday, February 4th at 5:45pm ET, I&apos;m taking questions from the OFA community. Submit one here: http://bit.ly/9-D</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 02 22:51:00 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @thejointstaff Stand by what I said: Allowing homosexuals to serve openly is the right thing to do. Comes down to integrity.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 03 21:48:14 +0000 2010</created_at><text>If you haven&apos;t already, be sure to RSVP for tomorrow&apos;s online conversation with the #OFA community at 5:45pm ET: http://bit.ly/9-D</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 04 19:10:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Don&apos;t forget -- having a conversation with #OFA today at 5:45pm ET. RSVP to watch online here: http://bit.ly/9-D</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 04 22:18:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to begin the conversation with #OFA -- tune in at 5:45pm ET. In the meantime, chat live with other supporters: http://bit.ly/U-i</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 05 15:25:26 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I&apos;m still fired up. I&apos;m still ready to go. And it&apos;s because of you. Watch yesterday&apos;s conversation with #OFA: http://bit.ly/a5WW0d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 05 19:04:16 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Addressing the Democratic Party Winter Meeting tomorrow morning. Watch live: http://bit.ly/9-L (Follow @DemocratsDotOrg for updates) #DNC10</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Feb 06 15:03:11 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to address the Democratic Party Winter Meeting. You can watch online here: http://bit.ly/9-L #DNC10</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 08 22:20:39 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Inviting Republicans and Democrats to an open, televised @WhiteHouse meeting on health reform&#x2014;Let&apos;s put our best ideas on the table.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 09 20:39:54 +0000 2010</created_at><text>As Congress weighs options&#x2014;and special interests tell them to give up on #HCR&#x2014;they need to hear from you. Take action: http://bit.ly/hc-ac</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 09 21:37:31 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Proud of the work the First Lady has done on Let&apos;s Move! &#x2014; a nationwide effort to tackle childhood obesity. Get involved: http://bit.ly/d-g</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 10 23:15:20 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Alarming study&#x2014;health care costs increased last year at the fastest rate in 50 years. Help show that Americans want action. http://j.mp/p-n</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 11 21:13:43 +0000 2010</created_at><text>#OFA supporters are pledging to support candidates who fight for real health reform. Join in: http://bit.ly/d-h</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 11 22:35:56 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Unbelievable. Already, you&apos;ve pledged to volunteer over 2M hours of your time to candidates who fight for health reform: http://j.mp/-hrs</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 12 18:06:30 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Over 3 million hours&#x2014;and counting&#x2014;pledged to support candidates who fight for health reform. Have you pledged? http://j.mp/-hrs</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Feb 13 20:53:13 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Invitations to the @WhiteHouse bipartisan meeting on health reform have been delivered: http://bit.ly/ag0uV1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Feb 13 21:20:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>To Team USA: Best of luck in Vancouver. I know you&apos;ll make America proud.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Feb 14 17:45:57 +0000 2010</created_at><text>This week&apos;s address: the new &quot;Pay As You Go&quot; law, and why it&apos;s so important to getting budget deficits in check. Watch: http://bit.ly/a-r</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 16 23:40:11 +0000 2010</created_at><text>You&apos;ve now pledged almost 7 million volunteer hours to candidates who fight for health reform. Thank you.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 17 00:16:23 +0000 2010</created_at><text>One year after Congress passed the #RecoveryAct there is still work to do, but we&apos;re on the road to recovery: http://www.bit.ly/9-l</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 17 16:41:45 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @PressSec: Read this and imagine &quot;something like 2 million&quot; more who&apos;d be unemployed right now. http://nyti.ms/9zQ2vA #RecoveryAct</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 17 22:51:34 +0000 2010</created_at><text>One year after passage, it is largely thanks to the #RecoveryAct that a second depression is no longer a possibility: http://bit.ly/bROnKn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 18 00:23:22 +0000 2010</created_at><text>OFA supporters are donating their Twitter pictures to mark the anniversary of the #RecoveryAct. Change yours here: http://bit.ly/b-E</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 18 23:45:57 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Wondering what the #RecoveryAct has done for our country since its passage one year ago? Watch the new #OFA video: http://j.mp/a9LudD</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 19 01:23:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Established a Commission today to build bipartisan consensus on balancing the budget &amp; improving our long-term fiscal health http://j.mp/r-7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 19 02:13:44 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Our work is far from over, but we have rescued our economy from the worst of this crisis. #RecoveryAct</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 19 17:42:53 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to begin a town hall event in Henderson, Nevada -- listen in here at 1pm EST: http:www.wh.gov/live</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 19 21:35:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>For #FF: Robert Gibbs, the @PressSec for the @WhiteHouse and Deputy Press Secretary @BillBurton44</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Feb 20 19:57:06 +0000 2010</created_at><text>See the latest videos and subscribe to @youtube channels: http://j.mp/BarackObamaChannel, http://j.mp/WhiteHouseChannel #subsaturday</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Feb 20 21:50:09 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Excited to announce the Race to the Top High School Commencement Challenge&#x2014;looking forward to visiting the winning school: http://j.mp/1--3</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 22 00:06:03 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Just one example of our commitment to doing our work openly and giving people the government they deserve: http://bit.ly/dpqfIK</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 22 16:09:20 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Released new health reform proposal to bridge the gap between the House &amp; Senate bills&#x2014;time to move forward on reform: http://j.mp/b784hk</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Feb 22 18:54:36 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today, the credit card reform we fought for takes effect. Learn more&#x2014;join the live chat at 2pm ET: http://j.mp/dxi3hR</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 23 20:24:17 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Grateful to the Democratic &amp; Republican Senators who put aside partisan differences and voted to move forward on a jobs bill last night.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Feb 23 21:50:29 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Met w/ our nation&apos;s governors yesterday and outlined new steps to better prepare our children for college and the workplace: http://j.mp/g-h</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 24 17:46:15 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Addressing the Business Roundtable at 1pm ET. See how business leaders and the WH are working together to create jobs. http://j.mp/l-c</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 24 18:39:24 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Have a question about the health reform proposal? Ask it at today&apos;s live White House video chat at 1:45 ET http://j.mp/ahbLsw</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 24 20:03:48 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Senate passes jobs bill with 13 Republicans voting &apos;yes&apos; &#x2013; when we work together, we can address our biggest challenges.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Feb 24 23:49:28 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Inviting you to watch the bipartisan health insurance reform meeting tomorrow at 10 AM ET: http://j.mp/7-h</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 25 14:43:06 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to begin the bipartisan meeting on health reform. Watch live at http://j.mp/aIfX8t. #HCRMeeting</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 25 17:09:03 +0000 2010</created_at><text>#OFA staff are tweeting live updates from today&apos;s #HCR meeting here:  http://bit.ly/cMF0dE Stay tuned for highlights throughout the day.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 25 18:28:23 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Watch the opening remarks from today&apos;s bipartisan meeting on #HCR: http://bit.ly/a2xczS</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 25 18:42:02 +0000 2010</created_at><text>#HCR meeting resumes after lunch at 1:45pm ET. Watch it live: http://bit.ly/-mtg #OFA</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Feb 25 22:13:10 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Watch highlights from today&apos;s #HCR meeting: http://bit.ly/b1nA7w; http://bit.ly/cFnJVS; http://bit.ly/bP01bn</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Feb 26 17:10:05 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Yesterday&apos;s #HCR meeting was the kind of open discussion between political parties rarely seen in Washington&#x2014;See highlights: http://j.mp/_N</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Feb 28 02:24:06 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The American people send their deepest condolences to the Chilean people. The U.S. is ready to help in any way.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 01 01:14:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Congratulations&#x2014;to all the athletes who competed in the 2010 Winter Olympics&#x2014;and to the American team for their inspiring performances.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 01 18:58:21 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Working with Gen. Colin Powell to help curb high school dropout rates&#x2014;a problem we can&#x2019;t afford to ignore. http://j.mp/v-a</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 02 01:16:05 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join Secretary of Education Arne Duncan for a live video chat on making college more affordable, tomorrow at 5:30pm ET: http://bit.ly/9oRvLL</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 02 16:53:11 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Visiting the Savannah Technical College to discuss job creation. Listen live at 12:30pm ET: http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 02 22:42:33 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Another remarkable demonstration of grassroots support for health reform: http://j.mp/g-w</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 03 17:42:16 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Presenting a final plan for health reform today&#x2014;it&apos;s time to move forward. Watch live at 1:45pm ET: http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 03 21:48:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>It&apos;s time for a final vote. Please join with me to help take health reform across the finish line: http://j.mp/9MlVE9</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 04 19:45:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join Health and Human Services Sec. Sebelius for a live video chat on health reform &amp; insurance companies, at 3:40pm ET: http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 05 00:08:43 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Urging all Americans who want health reform to make their voices heard now http://j.mp/bWRgVL [video]</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 05 16:19:42 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Speaking about the need for clean energy jobs this morning at a small business in Virginia &#x2013; listen live at 11:25am ET http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 08 15:57:11 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Speaking about the urgent need for health insurance reform this morning at Arcadia University &#x2013; watch live at 11:00am ET http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 10 21:35:30 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Speaking about health reform today&#x2013;listen live @ 4:50pm ET http://j.mp/4-f. The need is great. The opportunity is here. Let&#x2019;s seize reform.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 10 23:20:22 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Secretary Sebelius challenges big insurance companies to quit spending your money fighting against #HCR: http://j.mp/9QL9h1</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 11 00:16:33 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The final march for reform has begun. We need you to talk to your neighbors and help spread the facts on health reform: http://j.mp/cZg3To</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 11 17:58:54 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In these final days of decision on health reform, we need all of you to make your voices heard in Washington, D.C. http://j.mp/9RUGG6</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 11 19:26:33 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @RepHankJohnson: My office is receiving dozens of calls per hour in favor of Health Care Reform. I hear you. I&apos;m with you http://j.mp/c-b</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 11 23:25:47 +0000 2010</created_at><text>The time for talk is over. It&#x2019;s time to take health reform across the finish line. http://j.mp/dl3C4Q</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 15 16:26:25 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Strongsville, Ohio to speak about health insurance reform. Watch live at 1:05pm ET: http://j.mp/4-f.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 15 20:36:29 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In these final days before a vote on health reform, now is the most important time to make your voice heard: http://j.mp/crVJ80</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 17 21:14:45 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join HHS Secretary Kathleen Sebelius for a live video chat on health reform today at 5:15pm ET: http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 17 22:41:58 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I am here for Natoma Canfield &amp; countless others who need health reform. Who are you fighting for? #iamherefor http://j.mp/c-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 00:16:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I am here for the millions who are denied coverage because of preexisting conditions. #iamherefor http://j.mp/c-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 16:18:49 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Signed a jobs bill this morning that helps businesses hire new workers -- another step towards rebuilding our economy for all Americans.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 16:51:53 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I am here for the seniors unable to afford the prescriptions that they need. #iamherefor http://j.mp/c-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 19:00:56 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I&#x2019;m here for the small businesses who are forced to choose between health care and hiring. #iamherefor http://j.mp/c-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 20:43:32 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I am here for the millions of lives that will be touched and, in some cases, saved, by health insurance reform. #iamherefor http://j.mp/c-d</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Mar 18 23:02:50 +0000 2010</created_at><text>#iamherefor my mother, and all the Americans who are forced to spend time arguing w/ insurance companies instead of focusing on getting well</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 19 00:59:28 +0000 2010</created_at><text>These photos put a face on our fight for reform. This is why we will never stop fighting until the job is done. http://bit.ly/m-l</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 19 14:48:00 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Final House vote on health reform expected on Sunday&#x2014;with your help, we&#x2019;re going to make this happen. http://j.mp/cypzFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Mar 19 17:11:40 +0000 2010</created_at><text>I need you to help us finish the fight on health reform. Pick up the phone and make your voice heard in Washington. http://j.mp/cypzFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 20 00:11:51 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @tomperriello: for me, #hcr comes down to saving $ for families &amp; small biz &amp; keeping our hospitals open. This bill will. http://j.mp/l-h</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 20 00:45:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In just a few days, a century-long struggle will culminate in a historic vote. The time for health reform is now.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 20 14:02:34 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We have a chance to do something historic this weekend, and you have a chance to help. http://j.mp/cypzFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 20 22:06:19 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We are one day away from delivering historic progress for the American people.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 20 22:26:51 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow, we will have the opportunity to pass historic reform. To the House of Representatives -- it is in your hands now.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Mar 21 12:34:21 +0000 2010</created_at><text>This is why I&apos;m here, and why I&apos;m fighting so hard for health reform: http://bit.ly/cxVoFz</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Mar 21 14:43:49 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In the final hours before the House vote on health reform, your voice has extraordinary power. Call your representative: http://j.mp/cypzFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sun Mar 21 18:32:51 +0000 2010</created_at><text>If you agree that the health insurance system is not working for ordinary families, help us fix it&#x2014;help pass #HCR today. http://j.mp/cypzFv</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 22 00:33:41 +0000 2010</created_at><text>After a year of debate on health reform, it&apos;s time for a vote. It&apos;s time to make true on our promise to the American people.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 22 02:49:05 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Yes we can.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 22 03:35:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to address the nation on tonight&apos;s historic vote.  Watch live: http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 22 03:55:12 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tonight&#x2019;s vote is not a victory for any one party &#x2013; it is a victory for the American people. Tonight, we answered the call of history.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 22 04:17:45 +0000 2010</created_at><text>This is a major reform. This is what change looks like.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 23 15:02:23 +0000 2010</created_at><text>About to sign comprehensive health insurance reform into law. Watch live at 11:15 a.m. ET http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 23 16:01:54 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today, after almost a century of effort, health insurance reform has become law.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 24 21:44:39 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Thank you for your tireless work and for never giving up. You showed that change is possible&#x2014;this is your victory. http://bit.ly/bU0eNk</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Mar 27 15:59:41 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We said we&#x2019;d stand up to the special interests, and stand up for the interests of students &amp; families&#x2014;and we did. http://bit.ly/cyrJkP</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Mar 29 19:50:16 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Our thoughts and prayers go out to the people of Russia after the terrible loss of life and injuries from the bombings on the Moscow Metro.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 14:57:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Virginia this morning to sign a historic investment in higher education into law&#x2013;listen live at 11:05am ET http://j.mp/vuo-</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 14:57:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Virginia this morning to sign a historic investment in higher education into law&#x2013;listen live at 11:05am ET http://j.mp/vuo-</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 19:46:02 +0000 2010</created_at><text>A great battle pitting the interests of banks &amp; financial institutions against interests of students has come to an end. http://j.mp/bRTbeH</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 19:46:02 +0000 2010</created_at><text>A great battle pitting the interests of banks &amp; financial institutions against interests of students has come to an end. http://j.mp/bRTbeH</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 20:44:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We need to invest in our students, our community colleges, and in the future of this country. The bill signed today will do just that.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Mar 30 20:44:46 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We need to invest in our students, our community colleges, and in the future of this country. The bill signed today will do just that.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 31 22:27:27 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join Health and Human Services Sec. Sebelius for a live video chat on the new health reform law, at 7pm ET: http://www.healthreform.gov/</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Mar 31 22:27:27 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Join Health and Human Services Sec. Sebelius for a live video chat on the new health reform law, at 7pm ET: http://www.healthreform.gov/</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 01 19:15:10 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Portland, ME today to talk about how health reform will help small businesses. Listen live at 3:25pm ET  http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 01 19:15:10 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Portland, ME today to talk about how health reform will help small businesses. Listen live at 3:25pm ET  http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 02 15:12:06 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Charlotte, NC today to visit a local business and discuss jobs and the economy. Listen live at 11:55am ET  http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 02 15:12:06 +0000 2010</created_at><text>In Charlotte, NC today to visit a local business and discuss jobs and the economy. Listen live at 11:55am ET  http://j.mp/dvUmn2</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 12:34:21 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Attending the annual White House Easter Egg roll on the South Lawn. Watch live all morning at WhiteHouse.gov/live.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 12:34:21 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Attending the annual White House Easter Egg roll on the South Lawn. Watch live all morning at WhiteHouse.gov/live.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 16:33:07 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Opening the 2010 baseball season with the first pitch at Nationals Park today.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 16:33:07 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Opening the 2010 baseball season with the first pitch at Nationals Park today.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 21:42:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow, Arne Duncan will be answering your questions on education reform. Ask a question here: http://j.mp/cTzX6i</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Mon Apr 05 21:42:08 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow, Arne Duncan will be answering your questions on education reform. Ask a question here: http://j.mp/cTzX6i</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 14:32:12 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Arne Duncan is answering your questions on education reform. Watch live at 11:00 a.m. ET: http://bit.ly/cnB6sZ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 14:32:12 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Arne Duncan is answering your questions on education reform. Watch live at 11:00 a.m. ET: http://bit.ly/cnB6sZ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 17:46:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Our thoughts &amp; prayers are with the families &amp; friends of the workers who lost their lives in a West Virginia mining accident yesterday.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 17:46:55 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Our thoughts &amp; prayers are with the families &amp; friends of the workers who lost their lives in a West Virginia mining accident yesterday.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 19:11:52 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today, we take a significant step forward in pursuing a world without nuclear weapons. http://j.mp/cg8cj7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 19:11:52 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Today, we take a significant step forward in pursuing a world without nuclear weapons. http://j.mp/cg8cj7</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 23:45:42 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Met with two volunteers who brought the names of 1.1 million co-signers of health reform to the White House. Watch:&#xa0;http://j.mp/bibhlY</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Tue Apr 06 23:45:42 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Met with two volunteers who brought the names of 1.1 million co-signers of health reform to the White House. Watch:&#xa0;http://j.mp/bibhlY</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 18:32:09 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Arne Duncan stopped by Organizing for America&apos;s headquarters to answer your questions on education. Watch: http://j.mp/c7K0Rx</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 18:32:09 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Arne Duncan stopped by Organizing for America&apos;s headquarters to answer your questions on education. Watch: http://j.mp/c7K0Rx</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 19:29:42 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @OpenGov: Every cabinet department has put out a plan for feedback. Here&apos;s where to find them:http://www.whitehouse.gov/open/around</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 19:29:42 +0000 2010</created_at><text>RT @OpenGov: Every cabinet department has put out a plan for feedback. Here&apos;s where to find them:http://www.whitehouse.gov/open/around</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 21:00:04 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Thanks to the Recovery Act, middle class families are seeing larger tax refunds&#x2014;see which benefits you&apos;re eligible for: http://j.mp/biq0rQ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 21:00:04 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Thanks to the Recovery Act, middle class families are seeing larger tax refunds&#x2014;see which benefits you&apos;re eligible for: http://j.mp/biq0rQ</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 23:01:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Leaving for Prague tonight, meeting with Russian President Medvedev to sign a new strategic arms reduction treaty tomorrow.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Wed Apr 07 23:01:18 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Leaving for Prague tonight, meeting with Russian President Medvedev to sign a new strategic arms reduction treaty tomorrow.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 08 23:51:17 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow at 9:15 am ET, Secretary of Education, Arne Duncan is answering questions on student aid and education reform. http://j.mp/UT2FE</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Thu Apr 08 23:51:17 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Tomorrow at 9:15 am ET, Secretary of Education, Arne Duncan is answering questions on student aid and education reform. http://j.mp/UT2FE</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 09 20:03:54 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Justice Stevens&apos; leadership will be sorely missed, and I thank him for his service. I will move quickly to name a new nominee.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Fri Apr 09 20:03:54 +0000 2010</created_at><text>Justice Stevens&apos; leadership will be sorely missed, and I thank him for his service. I will move quickly to name a new nominee.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Apr 10 17:02:22 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We join the people of Poland in mourning the passing of Polish President Kaczynski, and all those killed in today&apos;s tragic plane crash.</text></tweet><tweet><created_at>Sat Apr 10 17:02:22 +0000 2010</created_at><text>We join the people of Poland in mourning the passing of Polish President Kaczynski, and all those killed in today&apos;s tragic plane crash.</text></tweet></twitter>