<?xml version="1.0"?>
<twitter>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 13 13:51:48 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>working</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 13 14:01:46 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>continuing to search ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 14 09:05:37 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is in DC visiting Laura Bush with the Cooper-Hewitt.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 15 02:20:14 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is preparing for risdjogs.ning.com</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 15 15:27:36 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is writing about Scott Stowell on our.risd.edu</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 17 11:53:09 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is pondering the difference between orange juice and fizzy water.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 18 14:20:21 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is understanding the word 'research' in multiple contexts as being the same in principle.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 19 22:08:51 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is at Harvard learning how to be a president.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 20 12:28:00 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is contemplating the brilliance of a book title he sees "UNKN()WN QUANTITY"</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 21 21:55:21 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is captivated by the phrase "Less presentation, more discussion."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 22 17:30:05 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering what bees think about as they go about business.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 23 02:55:53 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is happy to be sentient.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 23 15:32:36 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering when books will be simply uploaded to our minds, how will we erase them?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 24 00:07:34 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is deeply struck by the correlation between Community and Communication. Connect and Context.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 24 12:57:03 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is realizing that "better" is not a subjective target.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 25 02:57:25 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is certain that complementary colors get along well.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 25 13:07:32 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is trying to multitask microtasks but is preparing macrotasks concurrently to increase the value of his time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 26 15:30:30 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is happy to have attended the recent MIT Scratch event with RISD folks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 27 04:35:21 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting the "dialog box of life" with options: OK, Cancel, and Be Happy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 28 09:01:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is curious about the implications of the sixth and seventh dimensions to art and design.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 29 18:14:05 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is fond of channeling JFK, "Ask not what RISD can do for you, ask what you can do for RISD."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 29 22:59:47 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is happy when his plane lands, and is unsure of how he would feel if it didn't.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 31 13:11:26 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is seeking to secure the future of art and design by empowering its past forms.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 01 00:06:10 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is standing two feet from Thom Browne and wondering if he can wear Thom-style pants.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 03 12:28:09 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is recalling the moment in his life 8 years ago when he learned the distinction between tactics and strategy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 05 01:05:18 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on what Richard Saul Wurman told him today, "Skills shouldn't be taught in schools."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 06 09:49:25 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is moved by Gong Szeto's assertion of strategy=idealize vs tactics=realize ... "thoughtful execution" comes to mind as a compromise.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 07 13:37:13 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is following the simple Web-like wisdom of "it is better to give than receive."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 08 20:39:13 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is confident that there's nothing more stupid than overlooking one's own stupidity.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 09 18:50:38 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is regretting he ate amusement park pizza.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 09 20:43:48 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about Randy Pausch today and is being grateful for Randy's memory and to be alive.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 11 03:41:44 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on Siddartha's acknowledgement of "self" as being a critical turning point.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 12 03:53:22 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is struck by the distance that can be achieved between perception and reality. Oddly they can be different, but equally important.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 13 04:59:07 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is uploading sixteen ~60Mb files to an online printing service so he doesn't have to buy a lg-format printer.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 13 17:26:53 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering if Batman is Buddhist.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 13 22:56:17 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is grateful that email traffic slows down after 6pm.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 15 11:22:28 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking that disabling all the visual acrobatics on the iPhone 3G would be a great way to save power.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 16 23:23:35 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is pondering the future of academia today with more intensity than usual.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 17 20:23:53 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is realizing that someone that "manages up" well is not a good manager if they can't do it down and sideways too.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 18 09:55:05 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is struck by the important balance between being educated for the long term (life) and for the immediate future (making a living).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 19 02:40:38 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is enamored by the true intent of freedom of speech.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 24 03:59:50 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is teaching himself how to make iPhone applications.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 26 03:39:07 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is curious about how design that satisfies 70% of the need utterly fails to serve the other 30%.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 27 03:19:15 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is recalling scene from Batman: "Why do we fall down? To pick ourselves up."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 28 11:05:49 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is struck by the level of sincere dedication in the people that he meets every day.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 31 01:14:24 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is trying to understand how "cautious optimism" can convert to "unbridled optimism."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Sep 02 04:26:54 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is amused by a novel term used for the mood on RISD campus as characterized by "cynical optimism."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Sep 04 17:52:44 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is at P&amp;G hq in Cincinatti engaging some of the world's greatest marketers. I feel like buying something.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Sep 05 02:10:40 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is easily impressed by the bright lights at night in Times Square.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 10 05:24:04 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is powered by hope.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Sep 11 09:00:18 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is at a party in NY for the Esquire 75. He met LeBron James, ate mini hamburgers, and is ready to return to RISD.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 13 03:07:43 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is all done with his RISD inauguration as the 16th President. Phew.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 17 10:11:38 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is happy to make his inauguration speech available online http://our.risd.edu/start-here ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 28 16:28:34 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is through his first Trustee Meeting at RISD. He renewed his determination to imagine what may be.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Sep 30 17:38:45 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is a believer in the power of mutual respect.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Oct 05 19:37:15 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is learning how to see farther into the future.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 08 03:48:16 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is curious about rumors and how they form.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 11 01:12:07 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is seeing a gazillion alums and parents here for RISD By Design weekend rbd.risd.edu</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 14 17:09:00 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is grateful to his father for his lifelong example of personal integrity.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 15 12:03:20 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is experiencing loss of right-brain strength. Drew images this morning to revive functionality.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 16 02:41:47 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is now able to see the mountain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 18 12:39:24 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is interested in making open communication scalable and respectful somehow. Thinking ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Oct 19 20:51:53 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is making art.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 21 18:31:55 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about Jessie Shefrin's point about when things are turned upside down you get the chance to truly see something for what it is.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 22 15:48:33 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about Jessie Shefrin's point about "artists that make art for the art world" vs "artists that make art for the world."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 23 01:55:22 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is spying a T-shirt in NYC that says "NO to Hate!" It seems contradictory to hate hate.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 24 20:10:41 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>Karten (ID '78)!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 24 20:10:43 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is proud of the two RISD alums that took home two separate National Design Awards last night in NYC. Congratulations to Scott Stowell (G ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 25 03:03:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is chatting with filmmaker Deborah Scranton about how artists traditionally *conjure* something from nothing. Conjure is the right word.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 25 15:35:11 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is likening good education to the art of instilling curiosity in people.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 27 12:26:51 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is answering a reporter's question of "What is an artist" with "Someone who does the wrong thing at the right time."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 01 01:27:40 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is marveling at the proliferation of LEDs in Halloween garb this year.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 02 13:13:00 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thankful for the outpouring of b-day wishes and realizes he should someday set his FB b-day to the correct date.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 03 11:57:28 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about RISD  Provost Jessie Shefrin's point on how we can use the phrase  "the big picture" as a metaphor for art and life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 05 18:03:25 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is talking with Providence Mayor David Cicilline about creativity and economic development.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 07 00:18:19 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is having fun with RISD alum Ann Harakawa at the ADC gala in NY.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 07 12:01:06 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is returning to RISD after being inducted into the Art Director's Club Hall of Fame. NDA winner and RISD alum Scott Stowell made him laugh.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 08 23:08:04 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about the nature of art (school).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 08 23:12:08 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is also testing out the new Google G1 phone. Impressive first step.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 09 13:34:08 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is startled by how hard iMovie is to operate now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 12 00:57:22 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is en route to giving his Art Director's Club Hall of Fame talk in 30 minutes and realizes he forgot his computer. Slideless! Challenges ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 12 03:34:34 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about what Maira Kalman said this evening, "Abraham Lincoln never had to go to school and be bored."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 12 23:44:22 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is considering the difference between being grounded in theory versus being grounded in the world. Is there one?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 14 17:25:00 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is at an off-campus event where 70% of the people here have beards. Awkward.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 15 15:17:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is saddened by his disbelief when he hears a bird chirping sound that it could come from a real bird instead of a mobile's ringtone.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 20 04:12:49 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is inspired by student Aaron Perry-Zucker's generation's belief in the power of open emgagement. Everyone matters.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 22 21:36:04 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is reading Lessig's "REMIX" book and is thankfully RENEWED.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 23 15:18:42 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is at an American Girl Doll Store -- witnessing the power of fantasy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 23 18:09:41 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking that the younger visionary is good at finding new keys, and the older visionary is good at knowing which doors to open.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 25 02:04:12 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is proud of the new viewbook site: http://www.risd.edu/undergraduate -- a sign of things to come.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 25 21:23:35 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is acknowledging the difference and relationship between listening and leading.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 26 18:41:52 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is smarter for learning from student Kristine Lee that a "good assignment" is one that has a clear purpose.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 27 12:43:46 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thankful on Thanksgiving Day  to have the chance to lead RISD.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 27 19:31:30 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how design is about the "well made," and art is about the "well thought." At the intersection lies RISD's authentic voice.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 01 01:27:46 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is a believer in "academic freedom" -- especially in an era when the academy's monopoly of knowledge is set free.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 03 02:44:59 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is open to thinking openly.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 04 02:27:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is happy to have learned from Provost Shefrin the important distinction between being transparent ... and being clear.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 06 12:16:58 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how a good student is someone who accepts the possibility of  being wrong for the opportunity to learn if s/he may be right.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 08 12:55:07 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how the goal in life is to know that you have lived.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 09 03:07:27 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering how many flavors of knowledge there are in the world. Sweet, bitter, tasteless, angry, lemon-lime.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 10 04:46:26 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on the importance of being awake -- intellectually, spiritually, emotionally, physically.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 10 13:03:15 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about youth as a way of life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 10 21:01:52 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how in a world where everyone is an author,  author(ity) means less.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 11 12:40:11 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering whether people still use fax machines.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 12 04:29:32 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is remembering how to program in Java.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 12 21:17:45 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is considering the subtle difference between contributing versus interfering.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 12 23:08:03 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how positive acts often go unrewarded; negative acts always remain unforgotten. The choice is yours.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 14 00:24:29 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is resisting the seduction of conformity.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 14 19:40:03 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering whether the Web will ultimately look like one big, gigantic graphic novel.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 15 12:59:56 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how all thoughts we have, no matter how global and grand, start ultra-locally -- deep inside our heads.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 16 03:34:52 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is wondering if Rome wasn't built in a day, then what *can* be built in a day?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 18 01:54:39 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how our best work is done when resources (time, materials, etc) are limited because there is no other choice.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 18 22:58:16 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting how a mirror to one's soul reveals the unseen work that remains -- vanity has an unexpected up side.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 19 13:31:21 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is relecting on how a good teacher can make even the most boring of topic matter to be somehow exciting.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 19 17:55:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how education is about unlocking the freeing power of confidence in oneself.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 20 16:16:58 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is open to modern REMIX culture, and notes how every artistic act -- analog or digital -- samples and reorders reality anew.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 24 14:34:09 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting that great art bridges the artist's private integrity and her public contexts with a timely degree of concern or lack thereof.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 25 15:05:14 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting how on iTunes, music videos have become a natural stand-in for the elaborate CD packaging we once knew.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 26 21:43:03 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is recalling a favorite inspirational phrase, "I'd rather be green and growing, instead of ripe and ready to rot."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 27 13:58:35 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how the quest for perfection can empower (give an impossible  goal) or paralyze (give up on the impossible).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 28 14:11:25 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting how timesaving aids ironically become timewasting aids when you are desperate to recall where you last left them.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 29 21:04:35 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is considering the difference between restoration and transformation. The latter is a to; the former is a to-from.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 30 15:32:53 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is tickled by barber's response to my Q, "Do you believe in leadership by example?" "Sure. But not if it's a bad example."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 30 19:06:57 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how artist Kelly Dobson's work on "machine therapy" is going to make our world a more hummin' place.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 31 13:34:22 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is noting how an aimless walk through the snow can amply satisfy one's goals.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 31 15:28:11 +0000 2008</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how a caste system imprisons *everyone* from achieving change -- status quo is defined by status itself.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 01 20:06:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is wondering if a new year smells different than a used one.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 02 05:56:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking that if we learn by knowing, then what makes us know how to learn? Practice.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 02 14:04:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is squinting to see the vanishing fences that once protected intellectual property from making a meaningful difference.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 02 14:28:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is wondering whether "meaningful" impact is to be measured by depth or breadth. It depends.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 02 15:27:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how "free thinking" implies unlimited "undo"s for what may be thought or said. To Undo = To Forgive.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 02 16:32:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is going offline, to go online in the real world.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 03 01:56:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is wondering how creativity would be impacted if we all stopped using $$-ive software and went open source instead.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 03 16:49:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is respectful of how teaching even the lightest of seminars requires arduous and advanced preparation.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 04 01:38:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is resolved in 2009 to recruit the many creatives who dream to lift the spirits and hopes of our challenged world.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 06 01:43:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking about Jessie Shefrin's point that "problem solving" with a changing problem needs a changing solution.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 07 01:19:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how fresh ideas often come from professionals that allow ego to give way to the naivete of their youth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 08 03:49:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>recalls his former producer  Enami-san who would say with resolve amidst any chaos, "If I am here, all will be okay."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 09 04:00:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how doing something can be the next step after figuring out how to do something. It's up to you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 10 13:36:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how although his eyes are naturally weakening with age, with every year of life he can actually see *better*.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 11 13:24:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>recalls being told long ago that "a picture is worth a thousand words ... and yet it takes words to say that."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 11 21:05:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>teaches chess to a child, "A king barely moves and has no power." Her reply, "The king is *most* powerful. If he dies, it's over."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 12 16:25:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>reflects on how talking inspires doing; doing inspires talking. Talking about what you are doing is the real thing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 13 01:34:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is enamored by the simplicity of how toddlers can make intellectual arguments: "Because yes." Or, "Because no."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 14 04:38:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>feels the gravity of the challenges we face together globally and locally; lightness not only illuminates, but lifts us up.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 15 04:30:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how you can always find the truth around you when you stop looking for it and just listen to what is.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 15 17:56:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes the choice between doing some thing vs doing any thing. But doing the right thing is known only after it is done.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 16 11:34:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how a sense of community is formed by active, impromptu conversations that speak the truth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 17 13:11:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how creativity is not always communicative, but all communication Is  creative.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 17 14:47:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art allows us to consider the world with the open mind of a child, as an antidote to the isolating effect of an adult life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 18 15:52:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how trust in others is founded upon the doubts we have that get erased with evidence of action.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 19 01:32:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is wondering when the snowfall completely stops, what else will completely start.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 20 05:48:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is behind on a few things and is looking to decrease the quantity by multiplying with a number &amp;lt; 1 ad infinitum.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 20 05:52:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how "I can" easily turns into "I can-not"; however starting with "I cannot" misses the one chance to "I can."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 20 13:16:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is locked out of updating http://our.risd.edu but because of "yes we can" he found a way to say to all, and from today forward, yes we can.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 21 04:39:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is seeing, and thinking. In that exact order.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 21 13:46:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on W+K's John Jay saying, "The most powerful thing in the world you can be is to just be *you*." No one else can.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 23 04:55:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on W+K's John Jay saying, "There are times when symbolism is substance."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 24 17:12:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how creative teams retain members' individualism to keep group-think at bay. We and I in careful balance.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 25 20:51:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is testing the premise of "fast" food at McD. 56.9 sec in/out for a single cheeseburger order. He wonders if it is the norm.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 26 11:20:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how actions intended to clarify often result in more confusion. However, inaction tends to reveal nothing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 26 11:45:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is finding how as a "reality artist" he expresses himself with the actual experiences he finds around him ... as his medium.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 26 13:08:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on a comment by Provost Jessie Shefrin that, "Feeling ... is thinking with your body. That's why it is so real."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 27 06:08:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is recharged when he speaks with RISD undergrads at dinner in the cafeteria. Teaching happens anywhere.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 27 21:59:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is humbled by the nature of knowledge and the nurture of action.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 28 15:15:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how industry's activities are punctuated with ! and . -- academia's by " " and ? and ,</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 29 16:53:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is considering how "collective intelligence" can degrade to simply "group-think" when the group forgets to think.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 30 00:18:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@teamretro keep up the good work.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 30 01:34:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is en route to Davos World Economic Forum to speak on the topic of "creative leadership."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 30 02:27:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how the self-centeredness inherent to the referent "I" shifts dramatically when attached to "am sorry."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 30 12:20:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how easy it is to lose one's creative spirit to the demands of leadership if you forget to be a creative leader. I won't.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 30 21:42:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on Robert Scoble's point at dinner wrt "entertainment vs art" as "popularity vs morality."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 31 10:03:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is amused by Accel Partner's Joe Schoendorf comment from his old days at HP that, "Marketing people are engineers with personality."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 31 19:32:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how courage is a noble form of stupidity that aids getting impossible things done.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 31 23:26:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how Facebook is like Second Life but without the "reality" in "virtual reality."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 01 10:27:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is resolved at Davos that the world's sense of helplessness shall be countered by the 
Invigorating forces of art and design.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 01 12:56:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is intrigued by Mozilla's Mitchell Baker comment -- as crowdsourcing gets more popular, "the crowd" is bound to fatigue.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 03 03:10:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is inversely correlating the speed of the world in the last ten years with how much it has slowed in the last ten months.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 03 19:21:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@fancyjeffrey Nice. http://tinyurl.com/dxrsma FYI Mitchell's point was made at the Davos panel we were on.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 03 22:17:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is closer to how the cat thought and felt when the dog stopped noticing him -- able to see through, instead of around.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 04 05:29:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reminiscing to when a RISD alumni told him declaratively  and emphatically that, "Decoration is purely functional."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 04 14:58:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how seeing the world through students' eyes is the best way to always remain fresh and sane, http://tinyurl.com/brnxsb</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 06:47:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is quoting artist Yann Arthus-Bertrand, "We don't want to believe what we know."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 06:57:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@mihae I can see it both ways.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 07:05:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is fairly certain that when you work your hardest, the only downside is that you get tired. The upsides, however, can be limitless.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 16:42:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how when your  arms are crossed, ideas are deflected from entering your heart. So, open your arms.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 17:29:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting artist Olafur Eliasson's elegant point, "Between thinking and doing ... is experience."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 05 20:28:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is enjoying designer Jacek Utko simple statement, "To be good is not enough." http://tinyurl.com/bcx2rw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 06 07:15:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is marinating on what actress Glenn Close told him, "Art has the power to rearrange you."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 06 19:39:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting world stat that 1 in 2 people are of Asia, and 30% population in India are under 15 = the total US population.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 07 15:51:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>overheard, "Artists should be thought as more than content providers -- as catalysts that can transform communities."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 07 16:42:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is struck by Chris Anderson's comment, "Pessimists simply worry; optimists get things done."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 07 19:57:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes comment by Alex Tabarrok, "New ideas drive new growth. One apple feeds one man; one idea feeds the world."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 08 14:23:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on last nite's design thinktank dinner at the Eames House. Concluded that new era will bring advances in creative leadership.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 10 03:08:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting the tendency to ignore the ideas right in front of you because they don't play hard-to-get.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 11 03:42:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is optimistic to empower his creativity, pessimistic to carefully test assumptions, and realistic to see straight and clear.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 13 11:18:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how VISION = Prediction (see the future) + Intuition (*feel* the future) + Realization (make the future).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 13 15:04:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how entitlement and enlightenment are two very different things.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 14 16:29:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>weighs the distinction between a printed book and an electronic download. The gap closes for reasons of time, not matter.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 15 02:08:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how all crystal balls to see into our future have become like souvenir snow globes shaken, not stirred.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 15 21:08:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>when a student says they love a subject of study, they are saying that they love the teacher even more. Learning is personal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 16 00:45:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@elinesca Good point. And the memory of a teacher can be forever as well. To @amandarust -- the answer is that we all have each other now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 16 14:56:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is in wonderment from 1st grader's declaration that, "Today is Microsoft Word Day!" Wishing you all a good one.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 16 22:43:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>recalls his father's life mantra of the Japanese aesthetic of "mada dame" (maw-dah dah-may) -- "It's not good enough yet."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 17 09:47:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is noting how changes happening on the edges always find their way in -- why outside the box is the entrance to the box.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 18 01:38:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is wondering if domino pieces are more often used to be lined up in long rows instead of played as a proper game.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 18 02:30:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on the difference between doing something just to do it, vs doing something that leads to bigger other somethings.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 19 04:02:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>spoke with former banker that espoused simple finance logic: 1) save more, 2) borrow less, 3) don't invest in anything you don't understand.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 20 01:39:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>was asked by a student debating a choice in major as what she is good at doing versus what she wants to do,</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 21 18:00:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is reflecting on what Prof Charlie Cannon says about the importance of having space to *rehearse* an idea.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 23 00:23:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>believes that artists turn what is only imaginable to some, into that which could otherwise be unrealized.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 25 03:46:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is listening, steady, and focused.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 28 17:38:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is still listening, steady, and focused. He will be like that for a *very* long time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 01 00:19:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is considering @veek's comment on "role models" and is wishing he had met John Gardner http://tinyurl.com/cx9kfa</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 01 18:16:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>am analyzing data on Many Eyes by @wattenberg and @viegasf http://tinyurl.com/cv3wvl to see shifts in high school grad patterns by 2018.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 02 05:53:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>knows that everyone can make an image. But making the image say something extraordinary is not for everyone.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 03 14:47:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is admiring RISD grad student leader Jessica Roundy's charge to "think critically, and react creatively."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 05 11:05:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how the word "hope" can be used as a noun (goal) or as a verb (imperative). Together they form a state of being.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 06 13:05:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is chairing the National Design Awards jury. The inventiveness in the USA tells me "Yes we can" design us a future.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 09 00:04:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how the beauty of the snow segues to the sloppy mud. The ground eventually dries, and we can firmly stand once again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 09 02:24:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how the beauty of the snow segues to the sloppy mud. The ground eventually dries, and we can firmly stand again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 10 13:01:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@tinabeans thanks for your "expanding" thought.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 10 13:04:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how when we know where we've been, and know where we are ... we then know where to go next.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 14 22:26:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is looking forward to the upcoming RISD student-run event, "What We Do" -- http://tinyurl.com/cdab2q</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 16 01:25:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is open to a RISD campus run (technically a "jog") tomorrow night: http://is.gd/nu62</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 16 14:36:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@misterjonah thanks. Hope to see you there. JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 16 14:41:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how a team will win when everyone learns how to depend upon (and trust) one another. Earth, USA, RISD, family - all the same.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 19 01:22:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is challenged by living in a time when anything is creatively possible but eveything is fiscally improbable.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 20 02:56:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@damianewens thanks for that insight.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 20 03:04:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how subjectivity and passion are traditional hallmarks of the arts, but these times require objectivity and compassion instead.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 21 18:23:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes how depth in one's character may be evident at first glance, but only through tireless reinforcement can the disbeliever be turned.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 21 18:40:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A great image, whether representational or abstract, constantly generates brand new meanings regardless of how well you might know it.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 21 19:59:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is comfortable with his ponderings realized as a team sport. A team can do great things together when to play as a team becomes the goal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 21 20:14:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@efescenmeyer I feel that apathy is an extreme form of objectivity. To "feel"apathy is an oxymoron for certain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 22 01:15:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I was sorry to hear that @stop is leaving Google, but glad to know that @ireneau is still pushing forward -- http://is.gd/nVUI</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 22 16:53:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I was taught to embrace adversity by leaning *in* (vs out and away) to changing circumstances. My back aches with all of you leaning in now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 22 21:05:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@bigwags Great point. It is like we are all on the same sailboat and have to lean-in a unified direction else the boat tips over.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 24 10:10:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how *anything* you do will be done more wrong until you learn how to do it more right.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 24 18:26:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is elaborating on a Twitter post from long ago about punctuations marks http://is.gd/oKIO</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Mar 25 18:17:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is having an epiphany that if RISD stands for "Reason I'm Sleep Deprived," then he's happily living the RISD way.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 26 09:17:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how he's always treated students as adults because that's how they become professionals and 1st class citizens.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 26 21:10:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>overheard a nice phrase, "It's nice to be important, but it's important to be nice."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 27 19:38:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>notes that having an ego is usually healthy and fine. It's how you build the  ego that determines whether it is truly deserved.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 28 15:42:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@bwycz I like your point on the question of one's sense of peace. Peace to all of you today.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 28 16:21:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I've been forever told, "When you are new to something you think you can take it all on. Give it up." Artists don't give up. Ever.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 28 17:25:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>to dismissively say, "No they can't." neglects the fact that *they* are a part of *we* in "Yes we can."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 29 15:00:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@johnmaeda I disagree - a little bit. I'm an artist - I give up at least twice a day. The difference is I start again. (via @heidirettig)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 30 01:36:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is stuck on the ground at JFK and having an existential moment as to how many people on this flight are blogging or tweeting right now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 30 08:44:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>all the input on FB and Twitter made me wonder who just got in late to LAX? Perhaps just me. No electronic ghosts.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 31 12:45:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is curious how individualism can become a team sport.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 31 15:16:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks -- @johnmaeda you have to learn (and teach) that one can win without making others lose (via @jimhill)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 31 16:36:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is in SF to connect with close to 200 RISD alums, parents, and supporters. In LA heard gleeful stories about the empowering force of RISD.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 31 22:46:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>likes the sign for a business spotted in LA that realizes the fusion of two worlds -- SIGN-TIST --  design and science. Well ... sort of.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 01 21:18:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is thinking how #RISD is the authentic symbol of American right-brainedness that our world needs right now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 02 06:13:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Business adapts to societal norms, whereas artists often do the opposite to avoid being populist. There is good reason to either approach.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 03 00:06:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>from my scribbled notes from hearing someone in the world: "Revel in the unresolved." + "What you define as waste, I define as joy." Pretty.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 03 12:06:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>likes what #RISD Provost Jessie Sheffin says about decision-making, "It's not about top-down or bottom-up -- it's about working together."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 04 17:38:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>wisdom from Tony in #RISD Public Safety for emergency response situations, "Your pulse rate should always be lower than your patient's."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 05 15:44:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>insecurity &amp; vulnerability are weaknesses that when managed with courage (vs fear) embody humility -- a leader's greatest strength.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 06 14:08:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>speaking to fellow on the phone from S. Africa pitching that we work together ... using a lovely phrase that we need to "hunt in pairs."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 08 14:21:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks @zoheba -- I missed out on that part in biology class but can imagine it.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 08 14:21:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>the common occurrence of "human error," although often handled by poor leaders in a dehumanizing way, is essential to the human experience.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 09 02:27:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Winning an argument is less important than coming to a solution.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 09 11:27:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@tmtek I often wonder about the subjectivity of "right" -- when viewed from opposing sides. Being objectively opposed doesn't happen.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 09 11:28:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>saying you are sorry is only meaningful if your ego has left the room.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 10 01:45:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>only two more days until the first #RISD What We Do event ... http://tinyurl.com/cml2hf</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 10 13:27:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>recalls a former MIT colleague on the science of learning -- it happens particularly quickest when u r disoriented. Get lost, then found.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 11 22:43:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A fact is an idea that has evolved into an ideal. Evolution doesn't get it right always.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 12 12:35:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@g33kski11z Mathematical facts are certainly different, and I like @narinda's point on justice. Thanks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 12 12:41:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>On brevity, #RISD Provost Shefrin tells me that a 1-sentence thought makes u wonder, "What comes after?" The after-Tweet is key.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 12 21:46:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>is contemplating a commonsense derivation for the volume of a sphere. Cylinders are so much easier.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 14 02:19:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>sometimes u need to let go of who u r or what u r so that u can learn why u r u, especially when it counts.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 14 11:59:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Integrity comes natural to the artist because it is the raw material that invisibly dominates her work -- *honesty* is the medium of choice.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 15 04:00:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>told to me by a new friend from India, "if you come upon an elephant, walk around it."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 16 05:09:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Meetings exist to promote communication; rules exist to demote communication.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 17 01:26:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Misinformation is B-list info that underwent plastic surgery to get on the A-list.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 18 12:22:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The difference between closing or opening your eyes is the choice between the imagined vs real. Blinking is only human.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 18 13:08:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@hotlou Fair enough. Thanks. JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 18 13:15:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>No coincidence that #RISD graduates founded 2 of the 5 startups in this week's TIME article on neue entrepreneurs. http://is.gd/t8zc</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 18 16:21:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The artist's inhuman passion for perfection can only be managed by attention to her own mental, physical, and relational health.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 19 14:54:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Provocative: "Enough of the Great Depression analogies" http://www.newsweek.com/id/194609 (via @TEDchris)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 19 15:23:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Self-confidence comes from w/in and w/out oneself. Same w/self-doubt. To live both selves is to w/stand the truth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 19 18:46:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I was cautioned to distinguish between learning and knowledge. Maybe I learned something.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 19 20:18:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>After watching Dora the Explorer I'd have to say I'd trade my iPhone for a "Map and Backpack" bundle any day.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 11:36:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In the diner of working-life when the toast gets burnt or you're out of OJ, a side order of apologies makes the meal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 12:37:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>recalls his smartest professor at MIT who was never shy to respond, "Sorry, I don't know."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 14:00:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thought I was running a 5K race today, but it is a 5-miler it seems. Whoops. I like the metric system better.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 21:52:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@OnurOrhon my European friends certainly tell me so. Personally I an partial to millimeters. Live them more than 16ths of inches.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 21:53:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@heidirettig Reminds me to think about post-meeting time and what it means. Thank you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 21:54:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@jorgensen_ian I made it by thinking without units and just counting 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 20 23:06:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Japanese people are the only folks I know that get hungry when they visit an  aquarium. #Toshiba friend reminded me of that.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 21 10:50:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The upside of overworking is in those rare cases where you feel you actually got something done.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 04:13:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD frosh said 1st term was hard and now 2nd term is easy as it's routine. She misses 1st term -- artists yearn to struggle.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 14:42:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@ematamoros Simplicity is about subtracting the obvious and adding the meaningful. (10th law of simplicity)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 14:52:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>"Corporate" is thought in academia to mean "unfeeling." This stereotype is unproductive. Let's celebrate companies that *feel*.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 16:32:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Reflecting #RISD Grad student Lauren Mackler said over dinner last nite about narratives, "Failure makes a better story."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 16:46:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@Egnaro Thanks. Making art is as *real* as it gets thus failure is so natural to the artist.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 16:54:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Useful-&amp;gt; "slides and documents aren't the point: discussion and decisions are" - Kim Goodwin #ux #design (via @amyhillman)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 17:20:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The discipline of not-for-profit work is if u feel the organization owes you something, then u'r not focused on the mission.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 22 19:58:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Work is easier when it's just work; it's much harder when you really care.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 24 15:39:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@roonoid I like your "flipped" Tweet. Thanks, JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 24 15:43:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@not_yet I agree that "bureaucracy" has both negative and positive connotations. Where we stand changes what we see. That's why we move.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 24 15:52:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Met CEO of RI mfg firm Tacohvac when asked "How do you lead your people?" Responds, "I don't *lead*. I *love* my people."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Apr 24 17:22:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Stereo-types make it perilously easy to think in "mono."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 00:05:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>From friend: When ur young, ur told u have potential; when ur old, ur praised for what you did. Always b told u have potential.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 01:10:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The rocking chair Is a cross between a stool and a treadmill. What other #designhybrids exist?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 13:13:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>My favorite scene in Wall-E is when he isn't sure where to place the "spork." #designhybrids being collected: http://is.gd/uudi</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 14:17:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Institutional memory smartly skews decisions in the present towards successful past outcomes. Forward leverages backwards.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 14:32:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The pride expressed in a child's loss of a baby tooth is the rare case in life when losing is winning. "Just 1? I lost 5!"</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 15:44:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Effective listening is at least 66% of effective communicating. That's why we have 2 ears to 1 mouth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 25 18:14:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Even when everyone's on the same team, each person deserves to be treated as a unique individual.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 26 00:11:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Artists make art. Art makes artists.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 26 14:49:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@drwave intro'd Angus as a #RISD grad to me at Pixar -- "Angus MacLane came up with that (spork) gag in WALL-E." RT@drwave</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 26 14:51:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Spring is in fashion on earth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Apr 26 18:27:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thirst versus hunger for knowledge is subtly different. I'm unsure which is better. How you get full is important tho.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 28 02:41:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In the best meetings there are usually more wannacomes than havetacomes.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 28 12:24:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Humor keeps me human.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Apr 28 14:24:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The idea of "here" is becoming more of an "idea" than the specific places it one signified.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 00:31:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD alum Gus Van Sant speaking in the RISD auditorium now. Referring to Goodwill Hunting and how story built on 1 scene.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 02:59:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An "open invitation" is an open invitation not to come.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 04:15:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@necannon The #RISD auditorium was packed. Gus made everyone smile and aspire to great (and teeny little) works.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 04:17:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@a_maniac No, the scene where Damon and Robin Williams (the shrink) first meet, and Damon's character speaks ill of the shrink's wife.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 04:21:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A #RISD student suggested to improve my time mgmt skills by counting in secs instead of mins. I get 60 times more time now!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 12:31:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm a Moo fan so was glad to connect with @richardmoross -- small is not only beautiful, but memorable.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 14:01:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>From a RWJF friend, "Healthcare is not about life or death, but it is about quality of life."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 29 19:58:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Keeping your mouth shut and your mind open is a good thing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 30 04:21:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Writing and thinking are quite similar.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 30 10:08:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When someone says you have a gift, your job then becomes to give it away.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 30 10:18:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Made me think. @johnmaeda Writing is harder - someone may read what you wrote. (via @dsimov)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 30 10:28:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When I can convert a "meeting" into a "critique," although it opens me to all criticisms, I oddly feel more at ease.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 30 14:19:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Students speak the truth because they haven't learned it any other way.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 01 01:41:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Nice. @johnmaeda Older folk speak the truth because they learned the pointlessness of the other way (via @jholtaway)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 01 01:43:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Fav #RISD Provost Jessie Shefrin quote: "Thinking is a kind of making, and making is a kind of thinking."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 02 10:49:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The shortest communication path between two people is a straight talk.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 02 18:41:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Buy-in is often acquired on credit.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 04 02:11:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I like to say I'm neither low-tech nor high-tech. Both sides have validity so I've always stuck to being "less-tech."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 04 13:02:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>We all have faults. What matters is how we address our own before others'.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 04 15:07:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm lucky to be in one big, long, open crit as president of #RISD. The opportunities to learn are staggering.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 05 01:18:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An 85-year old new friend heckled me today, "You don't speak bureaucratese!" I do from time 2 time; catch me when I do so.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 06 04:25:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Black and white photographs evoke nostalgia. Low-rez photos seem to do a similar thing for me.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 06 13:41:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Having ideals is having a compass that always points to your heart instead of your brain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 07 09:09:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Exploiting spammers to make computers smarter http://bit.ly/2nZ1X (via @newsycombinator)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 07 10:18:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Pictures help to reveal qualitative insights better than quantitative ones. For the latter, that's what we have numbers for.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 07 10:19:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @slicesofsoup @WoollyMittens: A customer asked me to translate some content. It read: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur ..."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 07 10:25:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Those who speak ill of others tend to become infected by the same illnesses they share. Use hand-sanitizer often.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 07 10:50:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @jholtaway Reminds me of someone who opened a book inscribed with "Printed in Helvetica". She then asked, "Where in Greece is that?"</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 08 02:38:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Complacency occurs when u forget that ur not as good as u became.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 09 00:48:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>"Materiality is functionality." Overheard at Museum of Art and Design in NY today.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 09 15:09:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When u close ur eyes u can hear better; when u close ur computer u can parent better.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 10 15:26:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When the wind blows, Mother Nature wins the best prize for animated feature film.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 10 15:55:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Geography does matter. @johnmaeda ... and when the leaves turn colors, MN wins for best installation (via @ten_ten)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 10 17:09:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I wonder if birds sing in Dolby.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 10 22:26:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @KathySierra @Armano There's got to be a t-shirt in there... "I went outside once. The audio sucks." (after http://bit.ly/j4Hdf )</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 11 10:29:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Design illuminates the incomprehensible. Art ameliorates the intolerable. Art and design give sense and meaning to life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 12 10:55:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @mimojito @LukesBeard 40 Useful and Creative Infographics http://digg.com/d1qqKg</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 12 11:05:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When people ask if I've stopped designing I say, "No. I'm designing how to talk about/with/for our #RISD community."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 12 11:59:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A community needs to hear itself tweet in many voices for it to find the right songs that can be shared.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 12 15:15:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>How u carry a burden determines how light it will feel. An open, honest critique is a fast means to find a lightening how.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 13 13:40:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Answering all questions with respect provides the real answer we all look for.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 15 23:42:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Anger is form, not content.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 16 14:31:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Kids remind us that looking in the mirror or blowing bubbles are the ultimate in 2D/3D user experiences.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 16 21:23:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@business_design I tweet as a form of therapy meets semantic-sudoku. Glad to be useful to others.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 17 13:30:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Was asked at NY #RISD alum event on how to balance tradition versus innovation. Sounds like a plan.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 17 14:53:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When the weeds outpace the grass in your lawn keep remembering that when looked at from afar, it's still all green.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 17 16:22:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @mimijito @ravindra1982 80+ Web Tools and Typography resources for web designers http://bit.ly/y6ybE</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 17 17:40:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The microwave oven is to cold pizza as microsoftexcel is to stale data.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 17 18:02:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When something is advertised as specifically *live*, it is hard to get excited about the alternative.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 18 00:04:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Misunderstanding is a design problem. It can be solved at a cost of time/$/energy. The one cost to avoid is its recurrence.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 18 10:19:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Programmers eliminate bugs; artists, instead, appreciate bugs. We should all be so accommodating.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 18 20:13:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Misunderstanding is a missed opportunity to understand. When such opportunities are abundant, we all win.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 19 04:11:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Regret is one part worry with two parts wimpy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 19 15:16:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Kermit was my favorite muppet because he seemed to always be searching for a key life aesthetic. He still is.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 19 17:05:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Am at the #RISD / #Toshiba final projects review with Profs Walker and Somerson. Lots of excitement in the air!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 19 17:38:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Diversity of opinions and circumstances increases the likelihood of "happy accidents." Serendipity comes from differences.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 20 01:41:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter is like MTV for the mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 20 15:03:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art establishes purpose in society simply by talking about it. So whereever you are, strike up a conversation on art.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 21 01:33:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Teaching is the rare profession where the customer isn't always right and needs to be told so appropriately.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 21 18:22:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard at #RISD Landscape crit, "You haven't shown the ability to work across multiple scales. You've only shown work at a single scale."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 22 03:11:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>People who raise their voice in unreasonable ways often lose their voice to more reasoned ones.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 22 14:16:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The selection of eating versus sleeping is a difficult one.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 22 22:49:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>During #RISD finals marathon when the computer plotters fail, graphite and gouache mobilize to close the last mile.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 23 00:19:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Pixels repackaged. RT @jggube An interesting open source Flex/AS 3 data visualization framework called Axiis http://www.axiis.org/</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 23 13:48:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Cognitive dissonance usually occurs before a learning moment. Or, being "brain-dissed" can sometimes be good for you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 23 17:02:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>R = H x C : Respect is the vector cross product of Humility and Confidence.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 24 13:32:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A child's relentless plea to "read it again" reminds me that resilience and determination prevail. Time to read it again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 24 15:59:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Politics is a legitimatized form of group-think.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 24 16:30:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@tmtek Good point. We know that all group-think isn't bad. Thanks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 24 16:38:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Curiosity runs counter to established process, unless the norm is to innovate.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 24 22:12:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter grants every mind its own manual RSS feed. No PHP required.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 25 17:15:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The time we gain in life at peace honors the lifetimes we've all lost to war.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 25 21:50:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Attention to New Yorker cover done on iPhone app makes me think MacPaint and Kai's Power Tools may save the world again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon May 25 22:42:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Lovely RT @mwa4 @johnmaeda's tweet made me go back and read this article at folklore.org. reminds me of childhood. http://bit.ly/Y7hea</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue May 26 01:09:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A case for dirty hands in the recent NYT http://bit.ly/MAOaL as intro'd in #RISD HBR  http://bit.ly/11JjZv</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed May 27 16:30:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Printing 100% black wastes toner; displaying 100% white wastes lumens.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 00:43:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @wattenberg This optical illusion is strong, and new to me: http://bit.ly/13C92D</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 00:45:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @kirstiscott @johnmaeda  Check out ecofont http://twurl.nl/l4h64z - prints with 20% less ink!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 01:30:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being grateful is knowing that "thank you" is not enough.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 10:22:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Pity. RT @iagor @johnmaeda Don't use EcoFont, it's a marketing scam   http://bit.ly/g3iZa</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 10:26:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @daylinbreen @presentationzen: Can a bento be too sexy for Japan? http://snipurl.com/iwr7e Pics of bentos almost too beautiful to eat.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 10:49:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Spontaneity isn't something you can consciously strive towards as it is by definition unplanned. #hiriskhireward</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu May 28 12:04:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A radical idea succeeds because by the time it is implemented the world has just caught up. When is as important as what.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 29 01:01:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Yes. RT @johnmaeda However, I do think it is possible to nurture a "space" for spontaneity to be a potential outcome. (via @lexpression)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 29 01:39:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@lessig is such an incredible visual presenter -- http://bit.ly/6YwX -- his images and voice sync so fluidly.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri May 29 11:14:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>What ur told u can't do &amp;gt;&amp;gt; What ur told u *can* do.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 30 03:11:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>At #RISD dinner with Apple's Jonathan Ive, Jony made a case for designers that think with their hands vs 3D renderings.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 30 09:51:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@drwave In 80s design was hand v. mouse; in 90s hand dates mouse; in 00s hand marries mouse. Next hand/mouse play the field.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 30 09:54:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Today at #RISD commencement we are honored to have @sirkenrobinson speak more than 140 chars!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 30 19:52:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @joshspear Seen on t-shirt "Love can defeat the worlds strongest ninja..."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat May 30 20:10:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Even something old hat seems new when it is surprisingly relevant. Timeliness matters in the mathematics of originality.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 15:25:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Congrats Dr. Fake! RT @caterina Love #RISD. @SirKenRobinson gave a great commencement address, love Jony Ive, Betty Woodman, @johnmaeda.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 16:07:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Timeliness or timelessness. Seems you would want a mixture of both.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 16:10:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It seems wonderfully relevant to tweet live from an Audubon wildlife sanctuary.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 16:55:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Hierarchy is reinforced by exclusion; teamwork is reinforced by inclusion.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 20:04:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Great nav is about not getting lost. RT @gracesmith 30 Examples of Attractive Nav: http://bit.ly/JvTvq</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun May 31 20:24:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Tweets r social lint that when RT-ed become bigger balls of lint that stay small thx 2 the 140 char filter in the dryer.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 01 02:49:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>NYT Alice Rawsthorn on "The Demise of Form Follows Function" http://bit.ly/RBsmT</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 01 02:54:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The best defense, is to simply not be offensive.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 01 19:50:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Children's drawings reveal visual truths we've let reality fool ourselves into denial.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 01 20:49:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @mediajunkie: @johnmaeda very true: such as how heads with arms and feet map pretty well to the neurological body image</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 01 23:59:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>As jjr MIT prof my mentor urged me 2 avoid internal politics and 2 focus on the gr8er world instead. I love life's Yodas.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 02 00:06:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I follow tweets in non-English languages as it makes me feel like I'm in London or Hong Kong. Frugal #mindtraveling.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 02 01:47:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Regexps are the trigonometry of chars.  RT @smashingmag: Essential Guide To Regular Expressions http://tinyurl.com/m6lskb</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 02 10:06:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Dreams are the stories we tell ourselves when the non-fiction aisle of our mind gets stale.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 02 15:34:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In case you missed @sirkenrobinson at #RISD commencement, here he is on video http://bit.ly/EokoL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 03 02:58:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I saw this talk and it waa great. RT @presentationzen "How to Give a Great Talk" by Barry Eisler http://snipurl.com/jbk4z</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 03 23:48:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The past is always preserved in the name of the future.  I wonder how the reverse could happen.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 03:04:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @sgentiluomo: @designboom random international: 'audience' installation at design miami/basel 09 http://tinyurl.com/nvwj2y</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 03:06:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Historians are professional rememberers.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 03:24:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @azinman: hi-larious: how to write unmaintainable code http://freeworld.thc.org/root/phun/unmaintain.html</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 03:26:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @SteveCase: Obama on Middle East:  "Leaders have to lead -- hopefully they'll get supported by their people" http://bit.ly/16SOgU</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 03:46:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Discontent is best eaten with a fork and knife, instead of chopsticks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 10:20:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @bbaxley: @johnmaeda Similarly, photographers are professional spectators.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 04 11:01:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Kids make priceless artworks as gifts for loved ones because they can't buy less meaningful things yet.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 02:45:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>We preserve the past so that we can remember what we once did right.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 04:28:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A circle is nothing more than a square without any corners.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 10:58:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A triangle is a square with a mohawk hairdo.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 11:10:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When you fail to say something, you've said something. Find the right balance between your saids and unsaids.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 12:24:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Well not-unsaid, Mike. RT @mikenourse: @johnmaeda you can never not say something.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 12:27:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I've started to have Twitter with my breakfast. I hope I don't gain weight from it.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 22:42:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@n_g_r it gets easier with age because each second becomes more valuable, so you use time differently.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 22:46:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Websites r messy RT curiouslee Diagram of t inner structure of a corporate web site I did over five years ago... http://tinyurl.com/o8ke2o</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 22:52:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>main() { printf("Hello world!\n"); } no longer needs to be compiled to serve its true intention.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 22:58:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks Dr @tomguarriello for the medical advice. Nothing like the doctor's orders.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 05 23:48:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I recall my friend's dad in answer to her desire for car AC, "We've got 4-60 air conditioning. 4 windows down at 60mph."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 00:02:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A #RISD prof said to me today, "I don't want my students to trust me. You know, a little suspicion can go a long way."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 00:13:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @armano top 100 brands on twitter http://twurl.nl/kndbcd</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 00:33:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Am curious what sits outside the circles. RT @katherineabell: http://bit.ly/1Y0yzk</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 01:28:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Trends are ideas on enhancement drugs.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 14:16:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@bigwags "O2"; @peterpavlov Elegant; @enlargedheart I let Prof Fink know. (Apologies for MRV-ed Tweet.)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 14:19:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Finally. RT @warrenki Interesting perspective: "Dear Pixar, From All The Girls With Band-Aids On Their Knees". http://tr.im/nDj6</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 14:26:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Audiocast with radio legend Christopher Lydon and @sirkenrobinson the morning of #RISD commencement  http://bit.ly/4FOet</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 16:36:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter is everyone's two cents said at once.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 18:18:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Provocation nourishes the brain with Vitamin C(onflict).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 18:26:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm v impressed with Walmart's new in-store navigation design and can see why competitors are concerned.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 19:01:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@jeffrey Noted. Thx.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 19:06:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Originality is the second-cousin of invention.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 19:12:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Faulkner would have liked Twitter perhaps.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 06 19:24:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Design is a solution to a problem. Art is a question to a problem.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 13:34:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Humane. RT @wattenberg Charmed by GIMP feature: if u go 2 close a file w/o saving, it tells u how many mins or hrs of work u would lose.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 14:36:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@needle_e I can see it  depends whether you are an advocate for humane uses of electric charge or magnetic fields. Perspective is all.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 14:38:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@RobertaRimes has my current favorite Twitter icon as it captures a feeling instead of a specific likeness.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 14:42:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A case for education as an opportunity founded in hard work. RT @newsycombinator: Rising Above I.Q. http://bit.ly/XIi1Y</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 15:04:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Fake flowers evoke real feelings.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 16:02:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @bwycz and sometimes real flowers evoke fake feelings.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 17:30:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Subtle and useful. RT @jggube 8 Excellent Tools for Optimizing Your Images : http://digg.com/d1tBMa?t</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 17:42:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The business model for futurists is coming shortly.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 17:45:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Logical. RT @doriantaylor wondering y those (image optimizers) aren't just woven (as caching filters) into web servers as matter of course.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 17:51:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@arthabaska There's also the need for humans to tweak the image quality manually; automatic isn't automagic.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 07 18:58:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Love Brits. RT @designobserver @designrelated "Changing face of everyday design" from Corn Flakes to Orwell's 1984: http://ow.ly/cL7U</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 08 00:14:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Haven't seen Ellen in a while cuz she's working. RT @slicesofsoup @ellenLupton 7 signs of a high-functioning workaholic. http://bit.ly/1ZdN7</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 08 12:19:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Good music is like tenderizer for the stiffened brain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 08 13:58:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Turkey designing. RT @lubar @endlesscities @barbarahui: History of Visual Communication (incl coll of gorgeous imgs): http://bit.ly/J0XRC</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 08 14:13:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @junecohen New today: A contextualized, crowd-sourced dictionary of the future http://wordnik.com</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 08 14:40:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Management is the art of managing to remember that leadership always matters.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 01:43:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @dcdomain: Read another quote on leadership recently that struck a chord: Leadership is influence not control.  http://twurl.nl/bkhkbw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 01:45:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Keep designing #RISD grad Miller! RT @kmartdesign: http://bit.ly/QJ4g0</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 01:51:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD students seem to love Zombies. I'm learning lots about them: http://bit.ly/10rV7W</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 02:59:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If you are in Providence, RI on June 10 and want to go on a 6AM "runversation" here's the event for you: http://bit.ly/pYsJX</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 03:25:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It would seem that in a 140-char  economy that a brand new URL shortening service can sell shorter ones at a premium.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 10:14:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The better to see you wiith. RT @newscombinator Datablindness http://bit.ly/122VFo</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 09 11:40:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A good ruler should use his straightedge if he starts going crooked.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 00:31:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Opens doors. RT @dching_jgcc MIT Ed Arcade's "10 Keys 4 Designing Video Games 4 Foreign Language Learning" http://bit.ly/LIRwi</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 00:36:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD is aboveground. RT @rachealanilyse Underground Art School Mag on Doodlage! @RaShell's homage 2 Post-it art http://tinyurl.com/ls4355</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 01:43:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>See you in Japan. RT @mutsumiota: applied to @johnmaeda + yugop talk in AXIS gallery! http://tinyurl.com/mtssvo</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 01:47:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Enjoyed this. RT @gtmacki: consegui o novo ep das cocorosie. milkman &#xE9; linda: http://is.gd/WiMN</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 03:24:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I like to pace or jog because even when I'm mentally stuck, at least my brain keeps moving forward.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 11:22:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Advancement occurs when  "constructive skepticism" turns into "constructive criticism" turns into simply "construction."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 10 16:16:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @heidirettig Pew Internet &amp; American Life report shows social networkers suffering from "internet fatigue" http://tinyurl.com/nrplmc</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 11 00:02:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Procrastination is work without formal intent that always manages to get done on time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 11 01:56:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Persuaded me. RT @jkottke 50 Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Persuasive http://bit.ly/niFYC</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 11 12:01:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @bgaffnbk: Non-profits need a new name that focuses on what they r instead of what they're not. What about "Added-values?"</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 11 12:27:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks. RT @bwycz "non-profits" used to be called "public charities."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 12 03:31:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I could pretend I'm someone else, but that would be a lot more work. http://bit.ly/n6NT4</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 12 03:35:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Inspired RX (Retail Xperience). RT @dhanisutanto: UNIQLO calendar http://bit.ly/CpuOs</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 13:00:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Feeling the rhythm is more important than knowing the tune.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 13:30:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Clarify for @sirhendrix and me: Feeling the rhythm (spirit) of your team is the first step before knowing the tune (plan).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 14:04:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter is a Makers Faire. RT @helf "Writing is making" http://www.murketing.com/journal/?p=3447</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 14:14:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@SirHendrix  I don't know. But we'll figure it out eventually I'm sure. I'm still learning the rhythm. (smile).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 14:16:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Heard about this in Jan 09 and wasn't sure if it was for real. But it actually works. Magic. http://bit.ly/2SZP2u</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 15:21:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Writing comment was from my buddy @heif and not from helf. I don't wear my glasses when I type on my iPhone. Sorry @heif.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 15:23:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Adobe Acrobat 8 Pro is 832Mb. MS Office is 694Mb and iWork is 659Mb.  How did Acrobat get sooo big?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 15:35:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Open AP(I) news. RT @mathewi @Poynter: AP to distribute work by nonprofit investigative journalism orgs http://bit.ly/6NTgA</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 15:37:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>"Watch Trailer" for an art exhibition. Nice idea. RT @andrew_zolli: Banksy's exhibition http://banksy.co.uk/</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 19:16:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I have a 60Gb hard disk on my Mac and I try to stay in the 140 char-like limitation -- this helped. http://bit.ly/V2tap</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 19:20:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Explains it. Thanks, Wave. RT @drwave:  Adobe got so big by eating MacroMedia, but then not fully digesting them...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 20:58:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Many. RT @missrogue Meritocracy is good for self-organizing, but there are some issues in regards to biases (gender, racial, etc.).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 21:00:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I've used this before. Softer edges due to optics. @luismendo Meer over Photolettering kan je hier lezen http://bit.ly/tz3IL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 13 21:26:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Even with printed Google maps, car navi, written directions I get lost 9 times out of 10.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 14 12:38:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>From the company u keep come good habits and bad ones. If your brain's spam filter is enabled and learns, all will be ok.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 14 19:29:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I saw a makerbot being made today. RT @makerbot: MakerBot is on BoingBoing! Go check it out! http://tr.im/bbmakerbot</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 01:46:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In praise of clouds. RT @congbo: Products are Worthless http://tinyurl.com/nhvefu</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 02:34:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Entropy accelerates disorder. RT @SoftwareService: The "broken window thesis" http://bit.ly/pISJw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 13:15:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Questioning authority, or "enforced norms," is what creative people do by design because they eschew conformity.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 18:13:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@matthewcornell When established norms are already "good design," they still need to be regularly critted to justify surviving.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 18:16:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I always envy how "Scoble" rhymes w/ "mobile." RT @scobleizer The 140 Char Conf #140conf will be Broadcast LIVE: http://140conf.com/watch</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 18:24:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Even the strongest leaders today need to be vulnerable; when shields are down, the *photon* torpedoes can bring *light*.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 18:40:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I've felt "forever in beta" so this is helpful. Thanks. RT @mediajunkie Maeda rhymes with beta</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 18:52:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Alpha must be our 1st 9 months. RT @jayeffvee I think one comes out of beta on one's deathbed, and not before.  :-)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 15 23:08:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Are you a .EXE (do-er), .PPT (talk-er), or .TXT (leafy potted plant)?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 16 18:55:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Design is the studied synthesis of more than one element. Elements are found, or synthesized, in turn.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 17 02:32:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art is the inexplicable urge to manifest feeling, intent, or question as a specific experience outside the artist's mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 17 12:25:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Feedback makes the mind grow stronger.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 17 12:32:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Chess is work. Checkers is play. The fact they share the same checkered board means that work and play *can* coexist.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 18 12:04:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@askedgirl I hope it isn't falling down (like the children's song). Thanks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 18 22:41:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@shawnparkinson Sorry. It seems to crash for me too.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 18 22:46:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An open door. RT @T_C_P http://www.artocracy.com (via @nellferragamo)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jun 18 22:56:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Participation is never played by professionals. Only volunteers.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 19 11:20:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Having a sufficiently big ego means you're comfortable enough to not have one at all.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 19 11:58:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The time spent determimg whether to purchase something often exceeds the time spent actually using the purchased item.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 19 12:20:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Front loading. RT @mbadger Very true, but the time spent choosing is often an investment in avoiding remorse and not in the item itself.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jun 19 23:05:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Dis(agreement) is 75% agreement, and 25% not feeling (dis)sed.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 09:56:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Always knew this worked. RT @jggube Lessen stress and anxiety, "Feeling Overwhelmed? Clean Your Desk":  http://is.gd/17cPi</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 10:03:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Good education is when value reallly exceeds cost. RT @levity "If the value exceeds the cost, do it." http://bit.ly/eoL6e</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 10:09:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter and FB create a glance-ocracy. RT @rmack @feng37: Is Twitter Really a Tool for Democracy?  http://bit.ly/unWiL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 13:35:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@brucenussbaum Glanced.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 13:50:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@designprov URL is rather long. Did you think of provdesign.org or designprov.org?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 13:52:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I get hives thinking of GridBagLayout from early Java days.@chiudesign Flexible CSS grids: http://tinyurl.com/knrkwx</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 13:58:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Feels odd propagating headline news on microchannel; makes .alt become .com. But I am unabashed Ann Curry fan. RT @AnnCurry #iranelections</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 14:01:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Government is the original mainframe computer. RT @cheeky_geeky Gov 2.0 Expo Showcase http://gov2expo.com</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 14:05:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Made me wonder about the concept, scale, and limitations of a minority. RT @sirhendrix Twitter is a communication tool, used by a minority.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 14:55:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @netdivermag TW used by minority and now minority of corps want to take it over as if it was something they 'could' learn to imitate.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 14:56:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@kathy_h I hope they have provdesign.com too. Thanks Kathy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 15:00:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>But within 0 km from your phone. RT @artmonastery @bruces: "There are always amazing people within 10km of any place on this planet."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 16:04:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@jankabili Funny. Thanks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 16:06:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I wonder how much water lies imprisoned in half-drunk PET bottles at TSA security.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 20 17:43:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Bullies bully because they didn't grow up in china shops.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 23 15:18:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being tired is not as rewarding as getting to that point.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jun 24 22:11:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Both visionaries and politicians make promises that may never be fulfilled.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jun 27 05:58:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art is the new technology that will fuel future economic growth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 18:40:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>To all #RISD grads:  3 days left in our 08-09 Annual Fund drive.  I've personally committed 100K to scholarships.   http://bit.ly/9G9W7</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 18:59:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Fashion gives the means to express oneself, even when botoxed.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 19:55:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I wish Amazon put the $$ into fancy packaging for the Kindle DX into the actual design of the device instead. 1st gen rocked.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 22:00:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@jonathanevega I like your traytop pic. Innovative. Thanks, JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 22:04:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@chiudesign Can't stand the next/prev buttons. Gen 1 buttons had a "page-like" feel with sharp-angled bevel detail.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jun 28 22:16:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@gapingvoid I enjoyed your new book. Bought 3 copies for friends. Congratulations on a work that cannot be ignored.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 29 00:17:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Those who actively seek conflict as entertainment do so till they learn that front row is often directly on the stage.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 29 18:00:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Tic-tac-toe is a game that can only be won if your opponent is completely distracted. Or, if you're playing your parents.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 29 18:39:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@dr_shelley Honored to know so. Thank you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jun 29 18:42:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Pondering Adam Smith's Wealth of Nations' factors behind division of labor: 1/ cheap xportation, and 2/ cheap communication.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jun 30 03:16:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Most daily existential crises are simply addressed by glancing in the mirror. "I see me, therefore, I probably exist."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 01 01:35:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@paulkim511 Thanks Paul. NH Kim is an inspired leader.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 01 01:46:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A true sign of CEO-loneliness is when you think your lawyer is someone to talk with like a close friend.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 02 04:23:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A martyr falls on his sword; a hero simply puts it away.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 02 23:16:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Multiplication (X) and addition (+) differ only by 45 degrees.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 00:39:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Novels are the original virtual reality.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 01:43:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@truthiscolor Thanks. It appears that Dr @Caterina has the answer. Our brains are such interesting, cavernous places.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 01:44:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@tkesh Indeed.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 01:47:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Cartography 2.0 RT @golan "Experimental Geography" exhibition, hosted at CMU Miller Gallery (http://bit.ly/sYrN).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 15:32:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@gregoryjwells Thanks. I was introduced to Latour's work in grad school. Quite captivating.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 15:36:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Integrity is the amcient steel fabric that withstands a high-tech world of hardened aluminum shears.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 15:58:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Mobile phone users resemble smokers managing habits of stepping to aside, searching for a light, trying to be unnoticed.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 16:40:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Generation gap felt realizing that kids today don't know Bugs Bunny. Macgyver gap was bad enough.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 16:43:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@ireneau Rocks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 18:02:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Soccer is a sport where a  low-res polygonal object gets batted around with no sign of an impending graphics upgrade.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 18:16:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A mirror Is the one window in the house that doesn't look outside.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 19:05:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Processes remove the need to think, but should retain the ability to judge.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 20:57:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>! RT @Nick_Oakley The lo-res B&amp;W polygonal was upgrade from brown leather balls -- invisible against green grass on B&amp;W UK TVs in the '50's.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 20:57:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@mikenourse Crossed my mind as well. Thanks Mike.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 21:00:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Hmm. @RT johndmitchell I've always liked: "A technique is something you use instead of your brain." --Henry Mintzberg</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 21:03:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Team morale is more valuable and precious than Chanel No. 5.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 22:52:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@drwave Yup Wave. Big sighs.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 03 23:36:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Favoritisms run counter to keeping an open mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 04 14:29:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Class hierarchies define a ceiling in the sky that isn't that high because we're all roughly the same height as humans go.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 04 15:50:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In an economy of real colors, flowers in full bloom remain the gold standard.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 04 18:32:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Patience is often an uncredited virtue because it appears like you're dong nothng. You are, and yet you aren't.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 04 22:51:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @paulkim511:  impatience can be a virtue too http://bit.ly/Qw5Cv ; Thx Paul. Reminded me of http://bit.ly/gQKOb Wish I were a Brit.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 00:34:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I've gone for less data. RT @joi Thx to Disk Warrior, able to salvage most of my data, but took all day. Need faster disks or less data...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 00:50:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Interesting. RT @newsycombinator India creating new identity card system for 1.2Bn people http://bit.ly/MDfvP</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 16:08:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>"Diploma half-full" is an adult ailment where u dream of an untaken biology test that will let u graduate from high school.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 17:21:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@grandin @unklewood Most of us seen to have it.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 17:21:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Aging is not a spectator sport.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 23:37:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@paulkim511 at least 3 times per year :-)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 23:39:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The deep darkness of evening makes closing one's eyes somewhat irrelevant.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 05 23:40:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Great article on Visual Decision Making by the people at a list apart http://bit.ly/10timP (via @btpstudio)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 00:57:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thought of Italo Calvino today: lightness, quickness, exactitude, visibility, multiplicity. http://bit.ly/6WmMM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 01:20:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Appreciated this visual history of graphic design. http://bit.ly/n2NLB</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 04:03:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When the fan on your laptop unexpectedly comes on in public, you can't help but feel a little bit self conscious.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 04:23:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It's so great to see Ben Fry helping us see healthcare challenges better. http://bit.ly/6xeSv</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 10:40:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art and science. RT There are times when I look at the numbers I get from my experiments and think whether it's data or dada... (via @tijh)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 06 10:44:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I was luckily taught Tschichold early on. RT Jan Tschichold, profiled in the Guardian ... http://bit.ly/PDeYH (via @mehallo)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 06:36:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Anyone can make art. Everyone can't make Art.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 10:35:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An interesting table I saw being moved around #RISD campus. http://bit.ly/7KIBq</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 15:31:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm trying to gather examples of #RISDgrads, their work, and/or specific keywords that epitomize the who/what/how of "RISDness." Thoughts?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 18:37:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @kerfdesign Process integrity is a high priority for us. The most imprtnt thing I learned at #RISD: process shortcuts lead 2 bad design.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 19:20:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @burnto: Turning a Corner? - Interactive Graphic - NYTimes.com http://ff.im/-4VhAi</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 07 19:39:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Perhaps the best way to avoid the unrealistic "grass is greener over there"-syndrome is to always wear green-tinted glasses.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 09 20:15:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@cmartell Thanks! #risdgrads: divergent, curious, adventurous, spirited, emergent</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 00:15:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>With @davos 08 global leadership fellows this week in Geneva teaching creative leadership class developed w/ @bbermont. http://bit.ly/LDh9q</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 00:17:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When trust is broken, you have to start over from the beginning. Like muscle tissue, it can grow back stronger each time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 00:28:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@rlfalerts Yes , it's how I ride.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 00:29:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Follow @risd_edu if you are curious about the latest happenings on #RISD campus.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 00:34:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Social Media ROI RT @gavinbaker http://bit.ly/8T9Aj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 10 06:26:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Life is a series of "if-then" clauses where you can now issue "print" statements like this for debugging purposes.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 11 13:46:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>On a sunny day, nature makes beautiful monochromatic images with Adobe ShadowShop.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 11 14:40:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Pessimism loves company. Optimism makes companies.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 15 02:15:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Selfish makes for poor sashimi. And for keeping friends too.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 15 10:19:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When (not) in Rome ... RT British Museum announces Italian Renaissance drawings exhibition  http://tr.im/sqfc (via @lloydaustins)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 15 13:05:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Clarity in process resolves most issues. Even the difficult ones.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 15 17:51:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard at IDEO at brainstorming group by the moderator, "I love problems. I love ideas even better."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 16 01:55:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Enjoyed IDEO's @cscheffy xfer of wisdom, "Leadership is not what you say or who you are. It's how you are heard."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 16 09:29:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The creative leader always questions authority. Even when it is his own.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 17 11:59:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Integrity is integral.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 01:36:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@superchew Yes that #RISD story is on http://our.RISD.edu, thank you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 01:37:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An undo key would be useful on the dashboard of all automobiles.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 11:32:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Undo and cars: http://bit.ly/4vH0Oo (via @level9ganon)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 12:10:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Invisible remix while u wait. RT @judithd from e-book to unbook - amazon remotely deletes purchased 1984s http://bit.ly/EH0rM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 13:24:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I get confused when people adamantly say they don't watch TV, but visit Hulu all the time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 16:07:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Ethics and the making of Art are tightly coupled because both are not driven by motivation of profit.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 20:09:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks to our friends at @etsy for the 6-minute feature on #RISD's beloved Edna Lawrence Nature Lab. http://bit.ly/VH4qL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 18 23:13:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Asked teen how long Jonas Bros will be popular. Answer was, "Depends upon what they do next." Pop culture is where NEXT&amp;gt;NOW.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 19 16:31:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Comedies are evidence that laughter is a valid form of ROI (Return On Investment). Humor keeps us human.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 19 21:23:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Happy to read on @projo that Cranston mayor Allan Fung is a Family Guy fan. #RISD's Seth MacFarlane: http://bit.ly/eoeC4</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 19 23:49:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Revealing. RT Think You Can Really Text While Driving? Try This Test http://ff.im/-5rl6C (via @steverubel)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 19 23:53:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Upside down V is more visually threatening than right-side up V. http://bit.ly/tkDUV</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 20 00:21:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>You are correct. Thank you. RT actually, the article states 'less' threatening, no? (via @unklewood)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 20 00:26:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Unnecessary conflict is desired by those who have a missing peace.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 20 10:46:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Moving from knowing to being isn't hard. It's just impossible to think about.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 20 18:54:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Will be doing a Webinar tomorrow for @idsa. If you'd like to connect, email tima*at*idsa.org directly. http://bit.ly/71eTw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 20 20:53:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Interactive mathematical forms with no computers harmed at all. #RISD Loeb Collection from Nature Lab. http://bit.ly/mfmGh</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 21 20:20:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Hi Paul, Thanks. Wish I could read Korean :-). RT @paulkim511: Did you ever get this article?  http://bit.ly/2x6699</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 22 01:40:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Sincerity comes from the innocence you've retained in spite of growing up.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 23 02:28:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@mathaix Yes we do. It is called Film, Animation, and Video. Gus Van Sant is an alum from thar program and recently visited.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 23 02:43:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Sentiment is a latent form of excitement that's taken longer than expected to get from your head to your heart.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 23 11:07:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Creativity is an emotion, not a skill.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 23 23:30:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@eringopenha You don't think about it. Just do. Good luck,</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 00:07:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>To dwell in the past is to drive a car using only the rear-view mirror.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 10:15:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A story on not "teaching for the test" but connecting learning to life. RT http://bit.ly/F926J (via @newsycombinator)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 10:52:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The flaws we can see up close remind us to step further back, because life is not to be lived thru a magnifying glass.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 14:21:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Feeling the why is more important than knowing the what.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 14:24:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Sustainability pioneer Amory Lovins:  "87% of the energy expended in a car doesn't make it to the wheels."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 14:37:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Amory Lovins' simple sustainable design heuristic, "It's cheaper to save fuel, than to buy fuel."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 21:25:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Design cannot exist without Art. Engineering cannot exist without Science. Can the opposites be said?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 24 23:56:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Handshake with 1st Lady Michelle Obama's hand today at the White House for @cooperhewitt Natl Design Awards. Wow she's incredible!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 25 15:15:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Funerals grant us a necessary pause to consider what "Game Over" looks like in unsimulated form. Use your quarters wisely.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jul 25 21:20:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Congrats to Anna McCraney! #RISD alum wins Bravo's The Fashion Show. http://bit.ly/AxyoD</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jul 26 16:04:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Shared by a friend at Bravo, "You pick a boss, not a job. Who you work for can matter more than what you do."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 27 16:31:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being helpful is about not being hurtful. It's a fine line sometimes.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jul 27 20:59:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@dr_shelley Useful. Thank you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 00:49:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@Steve_Hayes Thanks. Life isn't completely object-oriented. :-)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 00:50:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@rokali Thanks for the royal quote.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 00:59:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Watching waves break is non-stressful because you know you can look away at any time ... and won't miss a thing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 14:08:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>10 listen
20 speak
30 gosub reflect
40 learn
50 goto 10</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 21:58:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thx @chloes RT @Charles: Ever wonder what #hashtags are all about? Check out @Twitter's help article about them! http://bit.ly/3UCfyy</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jul 28 22:37:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @NoreenMorioka Mobile &amp; video advertising way up...hello! Print, TV, Newpaper get a beep-ing clue! http://ow.ly/irfV</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 29 02:37:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Microsoft Bing&#x2019;s focus on decisions is smart &#x2014; but not a Google killer http://bit.ly/3ka07a (via @Iconic88)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 29 15:15:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Intellectual property is all in the mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jul 29 18:35:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Spoken to me by a #RISD grad, "Ornament is functional."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 30 00:23:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Am enjoying the design of Providence Monthly Magazine. V easy to read.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jul 30 11:24:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Read this with pause, "All measurements come with some degree of uncertainty."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 31 13:43:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In the way that jogging and blogging (= pacing) are similar, meeting and tweeting (= connecting) seem to resonate as well.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 31 14:40:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>We say, "Save the planet (for humans)." Wildlife says, "Save the planet (from humans)."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 31 22:40:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Classic paper by U Warwick Prof Oswald on how $$ != happiness: "Happiness and Economic Performance." http://bit.ly/m71S3</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jul 31 22:42:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Statistics is the science of guessing extraordinarily well.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 01 12:42:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>2 oxymorons: "experience" design &amp; "interactive" art. Design is experienced. Art interacts; no offense to Duchamp intended.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 01 14:43:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm reading a new book, "Never Use White Type on a Black Background." I wonder what color this type appears in ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:24:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>My friend @brucenussbaum poses interesting questions, as usual: http://bit.ly/2A9Fw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:26:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@danielleruckus Just a thought; @DU5TB1N Nice reversal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:28:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@dolphi Yes it is an Ogilvy quote. The whole book is a bunch of cliche quotes. It's so so.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:32:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'm always so behind on lingo. RT @Veronica ... when one half of the couple wants to play COD4, while the other wants to play inFamous ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:34:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @sondernagle #RISD professor Hansy Better won the inaugural Awesome Foundation grant. Giant Hammock! http://bit.ly/tX2Ah</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:46:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@lazarus2000 Yes I googled it. Always glad to learn new things. Thanks.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 00:47:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Those clever Brits. RT Credit-crunch cookery: how to eat better and spend less http://bit.ly/17XsfU (via @steakRIOT)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 03:47:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I'd like to see the natl agenda going beyond STEM (Sci, Tech, Eng, Math) to IDEA (Intuition, Design, Emotion, Art).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 17:12:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Nice infoviz. RT @newsycombinator How Different Groups Use Their Time http://bit.ly/HH8Lg</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 02 23:23:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Consumerism is a treadmill that, by definition, breaks down shortly after the warranty runs out.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 04 10:33:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Told productivity up by 5% with new capital equip; to 15% spending same amtt on training programs. Learning is powerful.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 04 11:27:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD at the White House. http://bit.ly/JIr2c</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 04 12:00:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The arts are about preservation, interpretation, adaptation, innovation, inspiration, and respiration.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 04 15:42:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being well is much more than, well, just being.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 04 22:47:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A Natl Geo photographer once told me the *only* times to take a photo are at sunrise &amp; sunset. Right now, I see why.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 05 11:58:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@johndmitchell Well said.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 05 11:59:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Convenient for photographers. RT Handy: golden hour calculator http://www.golden-hour.com/ (via @Rabourn)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 05 12:04:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Moholy-Nagy was one of those rare artists whose work didn't elicit a "made you look," but certainly a "made you think."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 05 16:55:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Consensus seems to be there is a good  IDEA (Intuition, Design, Emotion, Art) here. And that STEM docks naturally.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 06 00:36:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @loriemerson Paul Chan: New Digital Fonts for New Writing. http://bit.ly/FmxG5</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 06 11:10:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Appreciating one's health and the health of family / friends is an important default alarm clock setting to wake up to.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 06 23:33:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The high road suffers from thin air, low humidity, and ice/snow. That said, it's the only way to touch the sky.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 06 23:36:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When children spin in circles just to get dizzy, we're reminded that play needs no artificial ingredients.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 07 15:28:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Apathy is a passive form of discouragement. Since I've never met an apathetic artist, I find that truly encouraging.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 08 13:01:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The artist does not know what to make until they've made enough to know. Thus an artist's career arc is unusually long.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 08 13:27:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being gracious comes from being grateful to know that your world is more meaningful when shared with others.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 13:19:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Inspiration comes when a reason is not apparent. That's why making  art can feel so irrational but still a raison d'&#xEA;tre.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 19:34:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The Bauhaus taught us that one school in a time of great change can transform how we see and feel. #RISD is certainly the place to be.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 19:45:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Criticism is most difficult to receive from those we truly love. But honesty is the best fertilizer for personal growth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 19:47:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@charmermark we are all now connected, unlike the time of Bauhaus. So indeed 1000X more can happen. Good luck to your good work. JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 20:09:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@nub Wise. Thank you for insight. JM</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 20:11:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It's truly beautiful in RI. RT @designprov "Journey over Rhode Island" Start in a sailboat &amp; glide along Narragansett Bay www.designprov.com</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 20:12:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Not easy. RT @kokoe2 PROGRESS has many meanings http://www.nytimes.com/2009/08/09/weekinreview/09kapur.html</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 20:21:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Artists are hyperaware of their surroundings, making it hard to focus when the noise of the world tastes so delicious.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 09 23:19:06 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>While watching PBS Kids with my kids I caught #RISD grad @hahatango on TV. Always good to see our tango. http://bit.ly/O5wfu</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 00:33:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The pact between mentor and mentee is one of thankful guilt. Thanks for the meal, and guilt for the gift to transfer on.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 01:35:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Useful. RT @DesignNewz: Post:: The Definitive Guide To htaccess Techniques: Do&#x2019;s And Don&#x2019;ts http://bit.ly/BxAZR</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 01:53:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The many aspects of drawing, painting, sculpting are emulated faithfully with a mouse, but carry a lingering aftertaste.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 10:39:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@culturesinbetw Maybe that can happen someday.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 10:44:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Positive. RT @swissmiss: How to Ask Better Questions http://tinyurl.com/nmttf4 (via @theluked)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 10 11:02:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Simple and sweet. RT @db: The LED Spray Can http://bit.ly/pTvbU</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 11 01:25:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Today I learned how much I have to learn. It's convenient that I am at a school as it comes most naturally.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 11 02:08:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Advice needs to be explicitly requested instead of gifted without warning, otherwise it goes straight to DVD.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 11 09:30:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT Facebook | Facebook Search Improved for Everyone http://ff.im/-6rk4c (via @vascellari)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 11 09:54:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Jogging this morning with #RISD colleagues and friends in Providence.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 11 11:41:25 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If you have something nice to say about a colleague today, don't be embarrassed to say so. Acknowledgement is everything.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 12 10:25:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The best way to recover from a visual injury is to draw a bandaid.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 12 18:18:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Great art makes you smile, cry, and frown -- all at the same time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 13 00:14:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Optimism is the soul of education.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 13 10:09:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT I might say that learning is the soul of optimism (via @mikenourse)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 14 05:22:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The US Constitution reminds me of the Mona Lisa -- masterful in expression and inimitably subtle in its poetics.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 14 12:14:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>New self-challenges reveal new self-weaknesses that are worked into new self-strengths when you let go of your self.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 15 15:28:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>At last night's fundraiser for Prov CityArts for Youth was happy to reconnect w Exec Director Barbara Wong, #RISD alum. http://bit.ly/7ay12</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 15 23:33:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Today would have been my mentor Paul Rand's 95th birthday. His vitality is remembered with a smile. http://bit.ly/2GaSp</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 17 23:16:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When kids say "Look! Cloud!" or "Look! Bird!" or "Look! Flower!" they remind us that life is over-Looked from the start.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 18 09:32:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The missing partner to STEM: IDEA. Intuition, Design, Emotion, Art. #RISD</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Aug 18 14:27:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @hjames @johnmaeda: The missing partner to STEM [Sci, Tech, Eng, Math]: IDEA. Intuition, Design, Emotion, Art. #RISD</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 19 10:04:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>w/#RISD RT @vkhosla How would you advise ck12.org to add IDEA to STEM opensource materials? WOW: "Motivated" time for students in a day!</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 19 10:17:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Community and Communication are advanced by simply recognizing what lies in Common (c,o,mm, n).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 19 23:10:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Haven Bros Diner, since 1888. Only 10 years younger than #RISD. Here in Providence, RI. http://bit.ly/QCOrA</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 21 09:50:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The sound of your heart, isn't a sound effect.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Aug 21 11:55:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Openness to possibility comes from listening to students. It was my greatest lesson as a teacher.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 22 04:36:14 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If you're curious how Processing came about. http://bit.ly/1afrlx</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 22 04:38:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Practically everyone needs to express themselves. Artists, however, *live* to express ourselves.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 23 10:55:38 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The cat's curiosity was so great that her other eight lives were lived the same way.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Aug 23 11:04:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The goodness in people comes from the greatness in their teachers. From peers, parents, professionals, and more people.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 24 11:06:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Bravo. RT @Leslie2823 Pardon my liberty: The goodness in people comes from being willing to learn from others, whatever they have to give.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 24 12:21:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The Internet is useful to communicate over distances, but useless when talking with the person right next to you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Aug 26 10:44:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Caring is daring. Feelings can be heroic.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Aug 27 00:15:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard Prof Hermann at #RISD, "As soon as you make something, conversation can happen." Summary: Don't wait -- make.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 29 13:03:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Friends are the fabric softener in an otherrwise heavy-duty wash cycle of life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Aug 29 14:48:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Yesterday, Richard Saul Wurman helped me understand why my 8th grade Language Arts teacher didn't let us use the word "very."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Aug 31 03:33:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Encouragement and discouragement are like salt and pepper. Both sit squarely on the table of life as basic seasonings.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 02 13:55:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being prepared isn't a matter of how much you practice. Its about knowing that even if you fail, you won't give up.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Sep 03 11:16:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The human part of you is the only part of you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Sep 04 00:15:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Learned about #RISD distinction between "chippers" that chip away at a problem v "panickers" that wait to the last minute.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 05 14:04:10 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>We are the media we've been waiting for.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 05 17:39:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Inspired voices and thoughts are the windshield wipers of life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 05 23:37:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@paulkim511 introduced me to an excellent term: "right-brained strategy" -- something that artists and designers live.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 06 00:13:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Herbert Simon likened how we think to a pair of scissors. The brain is one blade, the other is the environment in which the brain operates.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 06 14:35:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>To Incoming frosh: Knock knock. Who's there? Toph. Toph-who? Yep. #RISD Dining's got tons of vegan options like that ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 06 14:48:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I was told by a friend that for all time, "food" and "fire" bring people together. Luckily, I can cook.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 06 15:04:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Twitter, FB, etc are like an endless karaoke night for mini-thoughts, cover quotes, menu choices, and leftover ideas.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 06 19:10:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Although solar energy seems like a high-tech concept, plants and people have always loved their time in the sun.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 07 20:47:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It was a cool but warm day in New England today. The trees were green, the light was perfect, and the mosquitoes ate well.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Sep 08 10:24:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Consistency in a good habit usually requires more skill and effort than a bad one. Thus, nice guys work harder.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 09 09:53:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Listening starts with a quiet mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Sep 11 11:53:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The less time you have, the faster you get things done.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 14 18:17:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Intuition is how a situation smells before you actually taste it. The nose doesn't get it right all the time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Sep 15 22:43:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When the heart puts the mind "on mute" ...  be sure to turn on the speakerphone when ready.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 16 04:37:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Yoda said ,"Do, or do not. There is no try," but doing comes from trying. Trying becomes doing when you don't give up.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Sep 17 12:36:23 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Humbled by the power of a hand-engraved black line in "The Brilliant Line" show at our #RISD Museum. http://bit.ly/3wM3Jm</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 19 03:41:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Time may tick in seconds, but life is lived in years.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 19 21:49:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>I like how Michael Jordan was quoted in TIME this week, "Limits, like fears, are often just an illusion."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 20 20:55:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Played frisbee with #RISD undergrads today at Tillinghast Farms. FYI "RISD" and "frisbee" are a 90% rhyme.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 21 10:27:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A good idea is like peanut butter -- it sticks to the roof of your mind.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 21 22:42:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Contributed this week to the @huffingtonpost about the #RISD IDEA http://bit.ly/31dcw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 23 05:42:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>When the right people are all in the right room with the right timing they can make the right decision ... right now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 23 10:54:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Nature is the universal pronoun.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 23 18:00:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Competency results in success results in complacency results in failure results in learning how to be competent again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Sep 25 10:13:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard #RISD Curator Judith Tannenbaum, "Ceramics is where painting meets sculpture."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 26 13:28:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard at #RISD, "If you can think, you can draw."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Sep 26 19:38:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Time doesn't fly. It travels leisurely by foot.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Sep 27 04:38:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Richard Saul Wurman asked me to name all the teachers that made a difference in my life. He said I'd find only 1 or 2.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 28 00:02:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Working while you are tired is a sign that maybe you're not finished yet, but perhaps really close.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 28 02:52:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If you know a #RISD graduate, please tell them I'm waiting for them back on campus Oct 9-10: http://bit.ly/1NqNcP</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Sep 28 09:58:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Ideas lead to a result; ideals result in a leader.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Sep 30 21:32:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Bill Moggridge (co-founder of IDEO) told me today that, "Good design comes from knowing how stuff works."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 01 10:19:22 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Visionaries wear binoculars instead of contact lenses.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 01 11:36:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Bravo. RT @rymden Visionaries also close their eyes and imagine.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 01 18:17:29 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Problem with drawing a simple explanatory picture is by the time it makes sense, it's too complex to re-use.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 03 11:14:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In address by #RISD student leader Nate Barchus urged us all to get past the *hesitation* to act now.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 05 10:03:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Overheard a good one wrt resting on one's laurels: "Laurels are okay, but rest isn't."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 05 10:24:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being imperfect is being human. I'd hate to be anything else.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 06 10:26:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The sound of laughter is the sound of peace.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 08 03:14:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@brucenussbaum Thanks for the memorable conversation today at #bif5 in Rhode Island. You gave me a lot to think about.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 08 03:50:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Sat with friend of #RISD Paula Granoff this morning, "Artists see things differently. Their work helps you see anew."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 08 10:41:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Projected light makes a wonderfully agile pigment. http://yfrog.com/7hcfurj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 08 11:42:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A chasm to cross, without a bridge, can always be done on tightrope. It's all about balance in life.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Oct 11 21:40:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Artistic integrity is about struggling against the norms upheld by society. But importantly, all norms aren't wrong.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 12 11:03:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>It's important to differentiate between a have-todo, need-todo, and want-todo.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 13 09:57:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @coreybcanada: And add..."don't need to do" -- "It's important to differentiate between a have-todo, need-todo, and want-todo."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 13 10:02:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD Provost Shefrin, "Critique teaches you to listen hard to others' criticism so you can listen hardest to yourself."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 14 10:24:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>What you see, makes you do.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 15 10:49:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Real communication is made by finding the specific part in you that *needs* to join with those same parts in others.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 16 12:40:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>You know where you're going, if you know that you're growing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 16 15:28:28 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Just now Red Burns from NYU ITP, "Passion wins over technique."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 17 17:29:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The turning color of the leaves in New England serves to remind us that life is beautiful http://j.mp/yGXYZ</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Oct 18 13:16:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD Provost Shefrin, "The process of making *has* to include learning."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 19 10:16:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Irony tends to have a metallic aftertaste.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 19 10:18:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The difference between a community and an audience is where you choose to stand on the stage.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 20 11:17:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The computer is now an abacus of many minds.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 22 03:32:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Contributed to a light debate on bento lunch aesthetics for the NYT. http://j.mp/RzlmQ</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 22 10:58:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The skill to improvise is to unhesitatingly realize a desirable accident.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 23 20:30:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Zach Lieberman at #poptech, "I think of being an artist as being a researcher. Art is research and development for humanity."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 26 06:34:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Experiencing a work of art changes when you've experienced the artist, alive or by true story. The connection reveals.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 26 18:21:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD Prof Kyna Leski spoke at #poptech about our unique approach to teaching critical thinking and critical making. http://j.mp/1NjCo4</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Oct 26 19:10:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Subtlety is a kind of dust in the room of life that shouldn't be confused with just  dirt.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Oct 27 04:41:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>3D + 2D critical thinking/making in #RISD Foundation Studies led by Profs Corrado and Mills. http://bit.ly/7ZiYe</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 28 13:07:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>We must all lead right now like we give a d*mn.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Oct 28 13:08:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>W+K's John Jay, "Find the truth. Then show why it matters."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 29 11:57:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Oddly, as an artist, being different means you're being completely normal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Oct 29 18:41:09 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>G O    L E A R N !</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Oct 30 13:05:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Integrity is like a prime number. It's indivisible unto itself.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 31 11:32:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art is about the unexpecte</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 31 12:20:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @Iconic88: Marie Curie, "Be less curious about people and more curious about ideas."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 31 20:58:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>For kids, jumping into a pile of leaves is the autumn edition of the summer pool ritual.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Oct 31 23:39:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The full moon reminds me that circles (vs triangles and squares) are as primal as shapes get. From birth, we seek other circles (eyes).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 01 04:00:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Enjoying @zefrank's videos for TIME this evening. Haven't seen him in a few years but now know he is well.  http://bit.ly/4y9uCb</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 01 17:10:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The leaves of autumn fall by their own volition, but often moreso by suggestion by the wind and rain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 02 00:13:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Cupcakes are the seminar version of a cake otherwise eaten for full-credit.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 02 11:12:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Waiting is the time spent *not* living.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 03 13:26:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Make US Green -- a #RISD alum project to crowdsource awareness of the 2009 UN Cop15 conference. http://bit.ly/4ubvGj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 04 20:22:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>"For example" is an exemplary tool for achieving clarity.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 05 12:07:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A person with highest integrity never  changes with external incentives. They change because it's time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 05 13:36:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @lessig: recruiting &#xA9; skeptics @educause: get yr certificate of entitlement: http://bit.ly/3VXi2A</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 06 12:30:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Leading by doing ceases to be leading when you are doing more than leading.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 06 13:36:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Buy-in can't be bought.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 07 13:51:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>There is tao to a terrific team.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 07 13:56:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A good critique reveals your blind spots.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 07 22:31:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>RT @burnto @scoutlabs: "If your job is based on managing an artificial scarcity of information..." http://bit.ly/3VJgUH</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 07 22:41:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Special thanks to the students from Missouri that came out to hear my talk in St Louis about the #RISD IDEA at @acsaupdate.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 07 23:47:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Digital + Analog at #RISD with Milloff/Valla: http://bit.ly/2PO6ll</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 08 15:20:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The quality of a critique is proportional to the quality of the critic(s).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 08 15:58:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks RT @bwycz That's tautological. By definition a good critic is one that offers good critique.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 08 20:28:43 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Alan Arkin in AARP magazine, "You're as old as your attitude."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 09 04:07:21 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Thanks to #RISD alums and parents in the Chicago area for coming out ! http://bit.ly/4gvAc6</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 09 11:12:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Showing beats telling.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 09 23:13:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Concerning. RT @brucenussbaum @atomiota: http://bit.ly/1502s2 Data visualization of health outcomes. Big surprise.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 10 01:21:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Podcasted veterans' encounter with the art of the art of (recovering from) war. http://bit.ly/1dyCjs</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 10 11:04:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Blame is similar to the game of Twister. In the end, nobody is left standing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 10 11:05:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Atruism is honest work.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 11 04:25:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Like the Prius, the Wii is the thing we all used to want.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 11 12:12:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Work makes things work.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 11 17:04:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Optimism smells better than pessimism.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 13 02:11:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The world is all we have.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 13 11:22:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Finding the right way starts with choosing a way.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 14 16:25:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Learning is learning. RT @pammoran: loved this article on google-proof a ? using Bloom's http://j.mp/1cIwA5</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 14 23:31:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Teenagers often remark, "It just ... does." This phrase is far but close to a more desirable one, "Just do it."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 15 00:13:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Rock - paper - scissors is a carbon neutral game.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 15 00:38:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An athlete friend once told me his reason for doing triathlons, "Pain is the purifier."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 15 13:35:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Design is the act of neatly folding a pile of freshly washed laundry. Art is the freedom to get them all dirty again.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 16 11:55:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The best solution is the one that creates the fewest new problems.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 16 22:42:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Dusted off an old interview with Amanda Koster @salaamgarage to post on Our #RISD. http://bit.ly/gwM1G</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 17 09:16:31 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Someone's having "the last word" paradoxically leads to another.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 17 09:36:18 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Entitlement is the path furthest from enlightenment.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Nov 17 15:35:32 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Art is the splinter in your finger that feels right.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 19 18:41:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Yesterday I learned the acronym "MENA" that describes the "Middle East-North Africa" area. http://bit.ly/uHF0N</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 20 06:54:13 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>@davos, "We need to have a practice- and long term-based view."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 20 07:15:57 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A diverse group generates many conflicting possibilities. A homogeneous group makes a few agreeable ones. More is better.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 20 12:30:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Feeling valued is about knowing how to be helpful without being perceived as just "the help."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 20 12:36:40 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>IDEO's Tim Brown, "The best open source design projects will always include experts (vs solely networks of 'amateurs')."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Nov 20 12:40:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Conventional economics: companies make supply, then advertise to create demand. #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 21 10:51:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>20thC design = convert raw, non-renewable material into stuff that is sexy and instantly obsolete; 21stC design = ? @davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 21 11:36:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Mokena Makeka: "People should be inspired by the consequences of their choices (as a consumer) instead of feeling guilty."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 21 16:56:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Four considered links on sustainability art/design:  http://bit.ly/8CXghs</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 23 08:04:36 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A better world by the world.  Notes from Dubai. http://bit.ly/8I09vO</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 23 08:40:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The art of asking questions, is art.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 23 18:38:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If you are in the Providence area thru Dec 12, check out the neat popup shop by #RISD students: http://bit.ly/4BVVRL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 23 23:02:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Jack DeGoia on world religious faith, "Of the 3 billion people making less than $2 a day, 80%+ are believers." #wefdubai</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 23 23:04:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Slow gets things done faster in the end. Because they get done right the first time.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Nov 25 11:16:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Until you can serve pizza or drinks over the Web, a social media portal to foster true collaboration will be so-so.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 26 15:30:00 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A WIRED Italy writer reminded me of my Do Both http://j.mp/7g3lfx principle. Today, cook and eat. Do both.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 26 16:07:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>From 2005, $cience vs Art. http://j.mp/8eKBHD</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Nov 26 19:39:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Dirty hands making desirably real things. http://j.mp/5vX3nh</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 28 00:06:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Grateful for the brilliance of @henryjenkins and his *living* approach to media theory http://j.mp/6xfxt2</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 28 00:17:59 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Reflecting on @joi's mention at #wefdubai of the "team velocity" concept from agile programming. http://j.mp/7PVseK</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 28 15:58:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In the same way your brain improves with age it would be nice if your kneejoints came along with the upgrade pack.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Nov 28 17:19:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The more you have of something the less you care about it; the less there is, the more the desire. Scarcity is powerful.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 29 02:21:26 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Was glad to read about #RISD grad @nicolemillernyc's foray into social media in the NYT today http://s.nyt.com/u/C5E</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 29 16:17:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Importantly, "ride bike" and "read book" sound the same and get you sane.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Nov 29 18:03:30 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Nature makes art naturally.  http://yfrog.com/33g65j</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 30 02:17:08 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>2D is powerful. RT @Armano @jowyang The Mother of All Diagrams: How To Choose A Chart.  http://i.imgur.com/YjWta.jpg</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 30 03:22:34 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Change. "The skills that once commanded $4 for every shiny new word ..." NYT @Carr2n RT @CodyBrown http://bit.ly/75oHTa</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Nov 30 10:41:55 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>What precedes the word "because" always matters more than what comes after.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 01 13:01:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The grass is always greener on the other side because from faraway you can't see the weeds.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 02 01:48:19 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Why Business Leaders Should Act More like Artists http://bit.ly/6QFVS0</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 02 19:08:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Being unafraid to be different comes from knowing that it is all that you can really be.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 03 13:51:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A quality learning experience is more like a bath than a shower. It's slow, immersive, and really gets to you.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 03 20:51:52 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The value of life increases proportionately to deepening your relationships with real friends.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 04 10:50:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Platonic shapes often lay victim to the "let's just be friends" syndrome but they deserve to be in a real relationship.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 04 10:58:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The most surprising discoveries often result from a deep misunderstanding. That's why you should always remain open.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 04 12:55:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Understanding the relationships is more important than knowing the parts.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 05 02:00:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>#RISD Provost Jessie Shefrin via the I-Ching, "Come at everything in life with fundamental sincerity."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 05 13:25:24 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>One of my favorite kid's book authors #RISD grad Grace Lin on the Today Show intro'ing her new book http://bit.ly/7x6xBP</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 05 15:46:16 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The domain name market is a huge parking lot for some of the world's greatest unfinished "big ideas."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 05 16:14:07 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>In-difference is on the way Out.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 05 16:40:01 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Gratitude gives fortitude.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 07 11:44:42 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Start any meeting with complete strangers, "How do *you* look at something?" The circle will close.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 07 13:21:44 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Enjoyed this bumper sticker: E(ART)H</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 07 16:44:05 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>No sides RT @charmermark Wikipedia's Neutral Point of View (NPOV) guidelines: http://j.mp/4Gqxka</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 09 01:55:27 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Henry Petroski quotes Van Karman, "Scientists seek to understand what is. Engineers seek to create what never was."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 09 02:03:03 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Kurt Andersen refers to the challenge of doing work that is both good *and* popular. They aren't mutually exclusive.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 10 22:49:15 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Boundaries that separate disciplines appear to be solid lines but up close are really dashed, and ready to cross.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 12 13:17:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Gabriel Orozco, "An artist can always entertain or amaze or amuse. Creating something that lasts -- that's not so easy."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 12 14:12:46 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Teaching is a quiet kind of intellectual philanthropy. Our teachers and mentors give so that we (society) can go.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 13 16:13:54 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Interesting reversal. RT @Adam_Cutler The Medium Is No Longer The Message...You Are http://bit.ly/5DekG7</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 13 16:29:50 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>My late mentor Ikko Tanaka once wrote to me, "Every moment you choose, is art." So what you do, is infinitely meaningful.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 15 12:18:20 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Communication bridges the divide between the get-its and the get-nots.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 16 11:39:02 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Doing right matters more than being right.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 19 15:35:12 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Peace is comprised of many definite pieces that have chosen to melt into a greater whole.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 22 10:59:53 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Always ask yourself, "What are the principles?" Say them and simply start from there.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 23 11:47:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>People who try to impress you by putting others down tend to fall short of their goal.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 23 11:47:33 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>A simpler way to describe "the self-fulfilling prophecy" is from drivers ed, "You drive where you look."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Dec 25 15:17:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Fewer words can travel further distances.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Dec 26 17:19:37 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>If all consumer products were as reliable and reusable as trash cans we would have a lot less trash. #irony</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Dec 27 17:55:17 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>The artist always chooses sympathy over apathy because it makes most of the pain go away.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 28 15:05:11 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Still life art meets quid pro quo. http://bit.ly/F2AJI #artonomics</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 28 15:36:39 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Context matters more than form. #art #design</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 28 16:27:48 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Clicking "unsubscribe" for junk mail feels increasingly like clicking "but you can subscribe me to something else."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Dec 28 17:06:41 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Mays' point on competition is spot-on. RT @charmermark J Mays on the Art of Design: http://j.mp/8UVlM3 (via @core77)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 29 15:39:45 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Kids unapologetically make messes because they know it's the fastest path to doing (and there's someone else cleaning).</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Dec 29 15:42:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>An optimist differs from a pessimist in the rose-ish tint of his glasses.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 17:27:49 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Living longer is welcoming seasons, thinking clearer, seeing what counts, and forgetting more. http://j.mp/6RWbHu #eoy</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 18:23:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Sturdy, printed books present the illusion of fact. Weightless, in-the-cloud PDFs present more as fiction.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 18:51:04 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Around this time of year most digital immigrants' Y2K flashbacks start to haunt. My scar itches.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 19:59:51 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Cleaning up the kids' toybin can feel like an archaeological dig when carefully sleuthing which pieces belong to what.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 20:36:56 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Echos disturbing conv w/ Joel Garreau RT @mathewi Depressing visual news about newspapers http://bit.ly/6DYXOC</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 21:04:58 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Clever. RT@jasonfried Novel concept - The Aston Martin Cygnet mini car will only be offered to existing Aston owners: http://bit.ly/70b4HO</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Dec 30 22:47:47 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Good open questions for creatives. RT@HelenWalters The Value of Design http://bit.ly/7JObmZ</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Dec 31 13:35:35 +0000 2009</created_at>
        <text>Although both are $0, free thinking costs significantly less than free speech. #freeisrelative</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 02 02:38:15 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Peter Cho's 2010 greeting is simply elegant. http://bit.ly/4EI8Zv</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 04 01:10:14 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Elise Co and Nik Pashenkov 2010 LED+baby greeting. http://bit.ly/7rurvF</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 04 01:13:49 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The hand is mightier than the mouse sometimes. http://bit.ly/7KlAEo</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 04 04:58:17 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Yellow page phone directories seem to oddly subsist today as free, ergonomic monitor stands. #forgotten-bits</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 04 11:18:38 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Good business = Customer service. Especially in a services economy.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 04 11:18:44 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Happiness is the unconscious decision to be and do so.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 05 11:20:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Illustrators think on paper. Architects think *in* paper.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 07 04:04:34 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Dan Wieden, "Encourage your team to fail (get it wrong) a few times first as the way to get it right sooner."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 08 11:30:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>If they're close to it, they can see it. Question is if they're far from it, can they hear it?</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 09 13:07:43 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Alliances are grounded in reliances.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 09 17:13:39 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>IDEO's Tim Brown, "Design is now too important to be left to designers."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 09 20:54:14 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Tim Brown argues that designers should broaden their roles beyond the studio, and that managers should think like designers. It's happening.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 10 01:03:52 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Logical. RT @newsycombinator Apple Tablet Being Developed For HealthCare Industry http://bit.ly/8DoPOx</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 10 01:39:36 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Bert + Ernie = Science + Art http://j.mp/4BnVEj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 11 11:26:22 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Knowledge can improve one's intuition. The goal is to not let either overpower.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 13 05:03:04 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Relying on each others' strengths starts by knowing and respecting them.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 13 05:03:51 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Polarization goes away thru participation because when the +'s and -'s come together they lose their charge.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 13 13:00:49 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>To expect to fail does not at all bother the artist. It's why they *do* so naturally.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 13 17:07:30 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Faliure is bad by definition http://bit.ly/ecOZU Trying is positive http://bit.ly/71GfCU But trying=failing, then doing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 14 12:57:39 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>There are carrots and sticks, but *tools* are even better.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 15 11:35:53 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Listening is more important than just hearing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 16 15:06:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>RT @gilgul Unlucky #Haiti (1981-2010): visualization by @blprnt using news articles from @nytimes http://bit.ly/6jSTB1</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 16 21:49:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Product design evolution of iTunes. Less to more. http://bit.ly/7gnQFo</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 17 20:39:37 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Art is about work and happiness. RT @DooneyStudio http://tinyurl.com/lesvru</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 17 22:38:26 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>For you, art is driven by http://twtpoll.com/r/aifqjn</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Jan 18 14:57:22 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Remembering that last year's Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Day was the day before the inauguration. http://bit.ly/5RZD2B</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 19 02:10:04 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>But offline? RT @DooneyStudio I don't think 'old school' art dealers will succeed online. http://tinyurl.com/d84ee4</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Jan 19 11:05:07 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>In-NO-vation requires listening to more than one NO.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 23 01:22:22 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>I did. RT @aperryz Participate in visualizing info about Haiti http://bit.ly/8vRoNq</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 24 01:01:37 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Change is managed by change.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 24 15:50:05 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jenova Chen, "There should be videogames that can move you to tears -- not just games that make you sweat and swear."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 27 14:39:13 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jeff Keeney, "Technology craves great content."  #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 27 14:42:50 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Maurizio Seracini, "Scientists can transform art history into the science of seeing."  http://bit.ly/bDSRpK #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Jan 27 17:05:05 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Nicolas Sarkozy, "We must pay the *true* price of scarcity." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 28 16:52:16 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Kigge Hvid, "On sustainability, what do we want to sustain?" #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Jan 28 23:21:33 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Fully automated typography organizer. http://bit.ly/cRz0f8</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 29 10:00:27 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Zainab Salbi, "Stories trump statistics." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 29 10:04:22 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Herminia Ibarra, "We are moving from leadership dev in the individual, to in the team, to now in the network." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Jan 29 22:46:41 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jens Martin, @jmskibsted "A classic is an object with a symbolic value that greatly exceeds the actual value." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 07:32:26 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jens Martin, @jmskibsted "I don't want my bikes to compete with other bikes; I want then to compete with cars." #davos #green</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 07:35:48 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The eyes have it. RT @vickytnz NYT article on the power of museums + user generated content http://bit.ly/7PMqQR</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 07:39:36 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>This is how artists work. RT @DanielPink Are you indispensable? http://bit.ly/7jmRYN</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 07:52:05 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jens Martin, @jmskibsted "A bicycle is a product where the sum of the individ parts matters more than the whole." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 09:49:11 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"If you're employee doesn't surprise you with new ideas, it's a sign that you've failed as a manager." OH at #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 09:52:57 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>CPS scientific method-ish approach to creativity. http://bit.ly/abfmQX #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 09:58:14 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Rational v radical. "Creativity is divergence from executing on task -- resulting in inefficiencies and added cost." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 10:01:24 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Maurizio Seracini, "Art conservation should not be performed like wanton surgery." http://bit.ly/bJIVs4 #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 12:01:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>David Bloom, "FOR profit can be FOR public health." It's not just about the NPOs #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 15:44:15 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Hindi philosophy of ethics, "Your business is with the deed, and not the result." http://j.mp/dl4qPi #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 15:53:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Email makes u delegate decisions up. Msgs 2 Queen once took months by ship. U had 2 decide &amp; get it right." OH @davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 19:15:39 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>RT @jjharrisnumber27 Paolo Coelho, "Art and storytelling are the only bridges we have left in a world that is collapsing." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Jan 30 22:28:53 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Russell Ackoff, "You never learn by doing something right, because you already know how to do it." http://bit.ly/a77s3W</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 31 06:49:41 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Adam Bly, "The world hasn't formally claimed art as a vehicle to advance knowledge. And yet if is art that remains." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 31 06:54:36 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Instead of saying we need to "elevate" art+design's role, we need to instead *reveal* art+design's role. #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 31 17:44:47 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jens Martin Skibsted, "The biggest mistake in product design is to design your product based upon your competitors." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Jan 31 17:45:05 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"When you buy something, what you haven't bought is the right to replicate it. You own only what you see." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 01 14:13:41 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Trust is a delivery on promises -- actual or perceived." OH @davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 03 09:20:32 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Daniel Griffiths (WIRED UK), "Art is an essential luxury."</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 03 09:20:42 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Jomathan Harris, "Being an artist is living with extreme sensitivity. Makes u be a student of ur own experience." #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 04 01:04:51 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Thanks for the Paul Graham link @colm: http://bit.ly/bmzBrH</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 04 10:52:13 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Hans Ulrich Obrist, "The question is how to be aware of your competition while resisting homogenization?" #london</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 05 17:07:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Richard Fishman in answer to the Q of "Do you know what art is?" his response: "I know what art *was*." #brown</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 06 19:43:17 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>My favorite (synthetic) nature film. http://j.mp/cpfXZB by Karl Sims.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 07 16:38:07 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The one research paper I still keep near my desk. http://j.mp/9Z1xL2 #pixar</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 08 10:17:55 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Sophistication is the craft of subtlety that goes noticed.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 08 10:19:16 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Uncertainties impede cooperation. That's why clarity always matters -- even if to be clear on what is less certain.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 08 11:26:29 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The vertical nature of hierarchies runs counter to the increasing flatness of our world.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 09 10:57:19 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Making a situation visible as a diagram is not as good as making it felt through a live experience.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 09 11:00:30 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Complex problems have simple, easy-to-understand *wrong* answers." -H.L. Mencken http://j.mp/bJwfhq</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 09 16:59:33 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Beauty is how it works. Not how it looks." -Megen Lee http://j.mp/c0VxRZ http://yfrog.com/3llueyj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 10 15:30:44 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Clarity is achieved by starting from an outline, whether stroked in words or traced by drawing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 11 05:54:46 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"How do we make things *better* without spending more money." -David Cameron #ted http://j.mp/bAXzkj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 11 05:55:36 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"There's a difference between 'rapid adaptation' and true innovation." -Joe Schoendorf #davos</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 11 17:09:14 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Education is the husband that will never let you down, my child." -Daphne Singo's mom #ted http://j.mp/c6LPjN</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 11 19:38:58 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>These kind of health devices, as I saw designer @ireneau sporting one, are becoming common: http://bit.ly/rTuo #ted</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 11 19:41:53 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"My teachers made me who I am today. It's such an honor to serve as a teacher." -David Kelley #ted</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 12 23:07:48 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Who's it for? What does it say? What does it *do*?" -Marian Bantjes #ted http://www.bantjes.com/</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 13 01:59:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Making space for creative risk and unstructured play." -David Rockwell #ted http://j.mp/cBhFHw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 13 22:35:51 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Rote has nothing to do with creativity." -Gordon Mackenzie #hallmark</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 14 20:11:24 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>High-tech, 3D movie formats add depth to everything but the story.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 15 01:16:48 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Design for Haiti project gaining momentum: http://j.mp/cfVF36</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 18 12:49:41 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Building designs aspire to be timeless for decades, but websites aspire, at best, to stand for a few months.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Feb 18 12:51:34 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Living long: Exercise 1.5 hrs/week, Sun 15 mins/day, Sleep 7 hrs/day, Eat unprocessed foods often. http://bit.ly/bwig7</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 20 12:42:58 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"45. All work and no play is a prescription for low quantity and quality of outputs." -Russell Ackoff http://bit.ly/bODorw</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 20 17:15:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Institutions versus/and Innovation http://j.mp/9vq2iy</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 21 22:11:42 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Snow is nature's blur filter.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 22 10:46:30 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>RT @timkastelle @ralph_ohr: Indifference, Hostility, Isolation vs Innovation http://bit.ly/9m6G62</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 22 10:51:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Effective. RT @newsycombinator The next 50 years are going to be completely unlike the last 20 years. http://bit.ly/bUN7my</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Feb 22 13:24:17 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>From a distance, two-handed typing on a mobile looks strikingly similar to knitting. #coincidence</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Feb 23 08:06:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>With a wristwatch it takes less than a half second to tell the time. With a mobile (grasping time incl) it's about three.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 24 18:55:59 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"How long can the world's biggest borrower be the world's biggest power?" -Niall Ferguson http://j.mp/80HAla</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Feb 24 19:01:42 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>A message needs a recipient that wants it. Otherwise it's completely irrelevant.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 26 05:00:11 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"A spectacular failure is better than a safe success." --from @risd_edu The Musical http://j.mp/d4ImCT</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 26 05:00:25 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>People who need to get in the last word usually finish last.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 26 10:59:15 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>A must-read history of money in the US. http://j.mp/9tdxuP</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Feb 26 12:16:14 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Simplicity is a high risk affair because it means you are betting that fewer features will deliver greatest value.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 27 11:29:53 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>So true. RT @Caterina Paulina Porizkova is now *my* favorite supermodel blogger too @anildash! http://bit.ly/drYhdF</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 27 11:40:55 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Paintings for the ears. ETHEL takes you thru a sophisticated gallery of listening. http://j.mp/bdFdVm</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Feb 27 12:53:58 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Posters from Ikko Tanaka long ago. I think of him daily now. http://j.mp/cQ5BuM http://yfrog.com/3nsfggj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 28 17:23:58 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Studio-style basketball. http://j.mp/cvgESK</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Feb 28 17:24:27 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Visual art requires a specific line of sight. Auditory art (music) enters us freely from all angles.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 01 00:38:33 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Integrty is having a matching interior and exterior.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 01 11:05:46 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The US is unfortunately experiencing NO-mentum. There is still no doubt in my mind, however, that YES we can.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 01 11:06:19 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The tide can sometimes turn in your favor. Rejoice when it happens.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 01 17:09:13 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"A train is only as fast as the one in front of it." OH this morning.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 01 23:24:28 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Micromanaging isn't okay, but having  microinterests is good. http://s.nyt.com/u/h1s</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 04 13:01:47 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Being on a great team means you don't have to be good at absolutely everything -- the team fills in your weaknesses.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 13:27:43 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Comments section is useful too. RT @ralph_ohr Four Fatal Flaws of Strategic Planning http://ow.ly/RHB4</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 13:31:32 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Everything is interconnected. @arttherapycast Bank failures strike a blow to city's art http://bit.ly/aIahOL</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 13:39:12 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>URL is entitled: twitter-is-for-geezers-and-the-man @nanofoo "Why Teens Don't Use Twitter" http://ow.ly/1eA7W</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 13:41:56 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>In praise of clarity @newsycombinator Get To The Point First http://bit.ly/d1NBsa</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 16:12:17 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Making mudpies means spring has come to New England.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 06 16:25:05 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Kids make playful messes because chaos tastes good.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 07 17:49:28 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>You know u've lost ur innocence when the political cartoons in the Sunday paper seem way funnier than the comics insert.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 08 11:15:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>art is a p(art) of every st(art)</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 09 11:34:34 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>There's nothing passive about passive-aggressive behavior.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 09 11:36:49 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Art for art's sake is vital. Art for more than art's sake is vitality.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 09 13:03:45 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Designers are extremely adept at making visual rhymes. Tactile rhymes too.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 11 16:11:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>What you do matters more than who you are.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 12 00:03:23 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>No drinking. No mobiles. No Macs? @museummodernart http://yfrog.com/5ylj4j</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 13 01:18:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Ending the week positively means that skill and luck worked in your favor. #tgif</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 13 15:44:38 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>We live in an age where data matters increasingly more than intuition. But that's just my intuition talking ...</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 14 17:21:47 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Good guys finish first, at last. http://bit.ly/anrSKJ</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 15 23:50:24 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Nothing is equal." -Richard Saul Wurman</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Mar 17 14:41:18 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Sometimes quantity is quality.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 20 17:51:01 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Academia vs war. RT @sugarpoppy In Lebanon, prof is condemned for working with Israeli scholars http://bit.ly/bCQyyu</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 20 17:52:25 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Good news travels slowly by foot. Bad news owns a private jet.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 20 17:52:51 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Eveything doesn't have to get done, but everything needs to get done.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 20 22:11:26 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>New. RT @newsycombinator Prof w/ background in game design abandons grades for experience pts http://bit.ly/a7CwHv</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 21 22:22:45 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>F2F works RT @heif Commons aren't tragic &#x201C;when people can communicate, particularly on a F2F basis" http://j.mp/aXRVtS</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 22 00:48:42 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>@jasonfried has written the perfect "street" design-thinking book  http://j.mp/1u7L68</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 22 10:04:53 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>A leader chooses we over me.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 22 10:05:34 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Art is psychosynthesis.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Mar 22 19:57:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Paintable and printable electronics.  http://bit.ly/bFRAeQ</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 23 09:13:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The effectiveness of an email diminishes by how loooong it might get.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 23 22:13:45 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Variable button sizing seems clever. RT @Folletto @azaaza: Another attempt to type on touchscreens. http://bit.ly/axd1Cv</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Mar 25 12:54:40 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Artist Jeffrey Shaw made cities "legible" when we were still learning how to "read" computers 20 yrs ago http://j.mp/bvd5PW</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 26 10:29:56 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Getting older means getting wiser, and sometimes a little bit wider too.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 26 10:47:42 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Although learning something new can be painful, the value is guaranteed when you get to xlate the lesson into practice.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 26 10:49:12 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Listening is seeing.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Fri Mar 26 13:46:41 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The desire to upgrade to software that is only marginally better is coming to an end. At least for me.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Mar 27 14:46:09 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Play is the highest form of creative reflection.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sun Mar 28 19:25:52 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Origin of KidPix -- it changed how we played with pixels. http://j.mp/bHPIsE</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Tue Mar 30 18:14:51 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"Artists are natural marketers for everyone but themselves." -Oren Sherman</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Mar 31 00:57:33 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>RT @lecoursdesign @DanielPink @CharlieGilkey The Four Essential Drives That Every Creative Needs http://bit.ly/b7th0L</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 01 18:59:32 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>In the old days "location location location" hyped the value of a fixed location. No more. @nyt_tech http://nyti.ms/ceGG5J</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 01 19:05:56 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Letting go is easier when you have something else to firmly hold on to.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 01 19:24:30 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Large can be achieved by many small. #impactofscale http://yfrog.com/6bfizwj</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 01 19:29:15 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Photography is painting at the speed of light.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Sat Apr 03 13:46:38 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The eyes have it. #onmotionstoapprove</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 05 13:52:16 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Had an interesting conv w/ a friend that has gone from .org to .com to .org to .com that next might end up as simply .me</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Mon Apr 05 13:54:11 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>The right brain speaks the truth; the left brain makes the truth. Integrity is when you speak+make the *whole* truth.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Wed Apr 07 12:32:31 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>Think tanks are only useful to society when they spring a leak.</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 08 01:19:52 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>"The best way to build a community is to sit and watch how people come together naturally." -Jaime Jett Walker</text>
    </tweet>
    <tweet>
        <created_at>Thu Apr 08 11:54:49 +0000 2010</created_at>
        <text>History often repeats itself because re-runs are cost-effective.</text>
    </tweet>
</twitter>
